Chapter 1124: Leng Wuyeng’s Shocking Talent

Zhao Hai asked, “Failure? Why would a failure be in the treasury?”

Tao Wang smiled bitterly and said, “Although it is a failure, the person who made it is very famous. He is the most renowned refiner in the Machine Field of all time, Leng Wuyeng.”

Upon hearing the name Leng Wuyeng, Zhao Hai was shocked. Leng Wuyeng was born 35 thousand years ago. He wasn’t an ascender and was a native of the Machine Field. He died 32 thousand years ago, living up to three thousand years old!

Naturally, Leng Wuyeng wasn’t famous because of his longevity. Instead, he was known for his refining ability as well as his contribution to Magic Theory. Leng Wuyeng was a natural genius. He also had a knack for Magic Theory. During his time, the Machine Field still wasn’t an independent existence. Instead it was a territory managed by the Cultivation Realm. It was a piece of wasteland where people that cannot cultivate gather. They could only study lower realm magic and battle qi. Because of this, they had no way to contend against those who use cultivation methods.

Leng Wuyeng was born to an ordinary Mage family. Even if both of his parents were Mages, their status was very low. Their family was pretty much living in hardship.

Because of his background, Leng Wuyeng swore that he would change the status of Mages in the World of Cultivation. He diligently studied Magic while also researching magic formations. During his time, runes were still unknown and the system of creating formations had yet to be made.

Later on, because of his talent, Leng Wuyeng joined a sect called Formation Gate and became a disciple. It was then that he started being in contact with true formations of the Cultivation Realm.

The formation system of the Cultivation Realm was a complete one. Each formation were comprised of runes. This made the formation easier to arrange and even more powerful.

After being introduced to this, Leng Wuyeng started to deconstruct magic formations. Then he used his results to systemize runes. His research was specially aimed towards runes.

When Leng Wuyeng reached the age of 2000, Magic Theory was beginning to take shape. And once Magic Theory was announced to the Machine Field, the entire realm seethed with excitement.

Although Magic Theory was unable to contend with cultivation methods, it was still a huge improvement for Mages. If a Mage was able to use a ten thousand or ten million-layer formations, then they would surely be able to contend with the top experts in the World of Cultivation.

This method didn’t only cause an uproar in the Machine Field. The effects of its creation rippled throughout the six realms. Afraid of losing control over the Machine Field, the Cultivation Realm began suppressing the Mages.

Having just studied Magic Theory, the Mages naturally couldn’t match the cultivators. They were defeated again and again. It didn’t take long before they were driven into a corner.

Leng Wuyeng didn’t expect this outcome since he was so focused on improving the strength of the Mages. He didn’t think that he would bring forth a disaster to his people. In the end, he didn’t hesitate to close up for eight years, resulting in magic formations that were now used inside mechs and battleships. And once the Machine Field began manufacturing mechs and battleships, they started their counterattack. After years of battle, the Machine Field was finally able to carve their own territory in the World of Cultivation. They were finally able to become the sixth realm in the World of Cultivation.

But Leng Wuyeng was still aware of the innate flaw between the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm. The Machine Field didn’t have peak artifacts that major groups in the Cultivation Realm had. With these peak artifacts, a person’s power would equal the might of ten million. They were the true ultimate weapons.

And at the same time, as they were repelling the Cultivation Realm, Leng Wuyeng began to feel the end of his lifespan. Because of this, he used his remaining time to leave a treasure behind. This way, the Machine Field would have a peak artifact capable of resisting the Cultivation Realm.

Leng Wuyeng closed up once more for refining. He used a large number of treasures that he collected his entire life, as well as a powerful technique in order to condense them together and form this liquid sphere. But this sphere was still a half-finished product. This was because it missed the most important step, condensing the formation.

Leng Wuyeng’s refining technique was different from the Cultivation Realm’s. In the Cultivation Realm, the final step of refining was the attachment of an artifact spirit. Only with an artifact spirit would magic treasures display their most formidable might.

However Leng Wuyeng’s method didn’t have spirit attachment. Instead, it was a three-step method divided into smelting, tempering, and condensing formation. Moreover, Leng Wuyeng doesn’t engrave formations from the Cultivation Realm, instead he used those made with Magic Theory.

In the Cultivation Realm, the influence of the first formation was big. The reason for this was because the five elements promotes and restrain each other. Some artifacts only allow a few formations to be engraved on them. Even if the material was good, the most formations one could engrave was 1890 formations. Moreover, this was a number most Cultivators wouldn’t reach.

Leng Wuyeng’s weapon allowed the engraving of 129,600 formations. Moreover, this weapon can be augmented with additional materials. And every material added, one could carve an additional 1890 formations. It was absolutely formidable.

Unfortunately, Leng Wuyeng’s lifespan ran out just as tempering was finished. At this point, it was impossible to engrave it with formations.

And because it was an original artifact, it had special requirements. One needed to engrave the 129,600 formations in one go. If one fails to do this, then engraving would not succeed. Only after the 129,600 formations were finished could one add materials and another 1890 formations.

Leng Wuyeng decided to create the weapon because he thought that he could still engrave formations on it. Since his lifespan was nearing its end, he wanted to squeeze the last part of it in order to engrave the 129,600 formations. As long as he finished engraving this formation, then other formidable Mages would be able to add materials and engrave the succeeding formations. With this setup, the weapon would get stronger and stronger until it would surpass any weapon in the Cultivation Realm. By that time, the Machine Field would no longer be afraid of the Cultivation Realm.

Unfortunately, Leng Wuyeng underestimated the time needed to smelt the materials. When he died, he just barely managed to finish tempering the weapon. He didn’t have time left to engrave the formations.

After Leng Wuyeng, although the Cultivation Realm still accepted disciples from the Machine Field, nobody was able to reach his level. Therefore, Leng Wuyeng’s weapon was never finished. In the end, it can only be placed here.

Zhao Hai wasn’t strange to the name of Leng Wuyeng. Although Leng Wuyeng has been dead for countless years, his position was still irreplaceable in the Machine Field. It can be said that the Machine Field wouldn’t have become this powerful without him. According to legend, Leng Wuyeng can release 50 thousand-layer formations, and maybe even more. Mages from the present Machine Field would find it impossible to reach this level. Only a few could use 1 thousand-layer formations, not to say 50 thousand layers.

But as for Leng Wueyng refining a weapon, Zhao Hai was completely clueless. Now after hearing Tao Wang, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be both shocked and happy.

He was shocked because Leng Wuyeng was actually a talent beyond comparison. By his own ability, he snatched the Machine Field from the hands of the Cultivation Realm. He single handedly gave the Machine Field its independence.

Zhao Hai was happy because Leng Wuyeng actually refined a weapon. Others might not find any use of it, but for Zhao Hai, this weapon was something that he must have.

Tao Wang stood beside the weapon and couldn’t help but sigh. He failed to see Zhao Hai’s eyes burning as they looked at the weapon. After some time, Tao Wang felt that something wasn’t right. Sensing that Zhao Hai was silent, Tao Wang turned and was shocked. Zhao Hai’s eyes were stubbornly stuck on the weapon made by Leng Wuyeng. Tao Wang was scared for a moment, Zhao Hai had the same look as someone who wanted something no matter what.

Tao Wang stared, then he quickly said, “Little Hai, don’t tell me you want this thing? It’s useless. Although its materials are top-ranked, you cannot use it with Magic Theory. It would be a waste if you have this, choose another one.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Tao Wang and said, “Big Brother Tao, can you give this thing to me? I want it.”

Tao Wang sighed and said, “Little Hai, you know that even if this thing can’t be used, it is still a sentimental item. So even if I give it to you, you still wouldn’t be able to take it out. If others see it, then they will certainly grab it. Listen to Big Brother’s words, choose something else.”

Zhao Hai firmly shook his head and said, “Big Brother Tao, I don’t want anything else other than this. I have a strong feeling in my heart that I must have it. Brother Tao, what do I need to do to get it?”

Tao Wang looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but be moved. To be honest, from the establishment of the treasury up to today, there had been a lot of people who had seen this item, but not one of them had the same strong feeling like Zhao Hai. Tao Wang felt that he needed to think about Zhao Hai’s request even more.

Instinct was a strange and mysterious thing. Sometimes, you will have a strong feeling in obtaining something. This item might not be great to others, but when the right one gets it, it would be extremely useful for them. This magical feeling seems to be in Zhao Hai right now.

With this thought in mind, Tao Wang said, “Wait for a moment.” Then after he said that, Tao Wang went to a nearby wall. The wall had a communication device on it. Tao Wang called Desbarres and told him about Zhao Hai’s request. Desbarres didn’t say anything other than to wait for him.

Chapter 1125: Uses of the Liquid Metal Sphere

Desbarres, Zhao Hai, and Tao Wang were standing in front of a sphere of liquid metal. After some time, Desbarres said, “Little Hai, do you really want this thing? Aren’t you afraid of getting just this one  and nothing else?”

Zhao Hai repeatedly nodded, then he turned to Desbarres and said, “Camp Lord, I need to obtain it. As long as I have it, I don’t care about anything else.”

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Can you tell me why you want it? Is it just because of your instinct?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s not just because I feel it. I also want to try and see if I can succeed in engraving the formations. I want to make it a true weapon.”

As soon as he heard Zhao Hai, Desbarres couldn’t help but stare. Then he said, “You really want to try?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’d like to give it a try. This weapons needs 129,600 formations and then another 1890 formations after adding other materials. I think I can do both of it. I also have some materials that can add to it. If I can succeed, then even if I cannot display all of the weapon’s strength, I can still go against experts in the Cultivation Realm.”

When Desbarres and Tao Wang heard Zhao Hai, they let out a sigh. They shook their heads at the same time then Desbarres said, “Little Hai, if this is your reason, then I suggest you just forget it. A lot of people thought about this before but weren’t successful in the end. This is because the weapon has high requirements for added materials. The materials that can be added to it are limited in number. It also needs to be a material that can handle a lot of formations. Even if you can engrave the formations, if the material is not enough, then you still wouldn’t succeed. I tried it before and I failed. You should give up.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, Big Brother Tao, rest assured. I’m not doing this on a whim. I want it.”

Zhao Hai found that the two didn’t want to give him this weapon wasn’t because they were reluctant, they just thought that it wouldn’t have any use for Zhao Hai. And if others know that the weapon was in Zhao Hai’s hands, then he would be in unnecessary danger.

Desbarres and Tao Wang saw Zhao Hai’s conviction, they didn’t say anything and just nodded. Then Desbarres said, “Alright, take it. Take two items for yourself as well. Even if you can complete it, you still can’t use it right now. You need things to protect yourself.”

Zhao Hai smiled at Tao Wang and Desbarres, then he said, “Camp Lord, Big Brother Tao, there’s no need. I’ll use the remaining one month before the family competition to complete this.”

Desbarres stared, then his expression changed as he said, “Little Hai, listen to me, your that wouldn’t be good. You choose two items, one weapon and one defensive item.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord, rest assured, I’m quite confident in this. Actually, in the lower realms, I once took a risk and was able to obtain a treasure. The treasure’s name is measureless golden sand. It is produced from earth fire and can be used for refining. I intend to use it to complete this weapon. I believe I can succeed.”

Desbarres paused after hearing Zhao Hai. They also heard about measureless golden sand. It was a formidable treasure that didn’t only give the metal attribute, it also had space attribute. It’s quite a rare crafting material. If Zhao Hai really has this, then he could certainly try completing the weapon.

Seeing Desbarres and Tao Wang’s appearance, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then waved his hand. He took out a crystal jar. Inside the jar wasn’t wine nor other liquor. Instead, what was inside was a glistening golden sand.

Zhao Hai handed the jar over to Desbarres and said, “Camp Lord, I’m giving this bottle of measureless golden sand to the camp. A refiner in the camp should be able to use it. I don’t have much in my hands and I still need to leave some for the weapon.”

Desbarres’ eyes shone when he heard Zhao Hai. Then upon receiving the bottle of golden sand, he laughed and said, “Kid, you really have a lot of good things on hand. Alright, I’ll accept this. But if you still aren’t able to complete the weapon in one month, then you need to come back here and pick two items.”

Zhao Hai showed a smile and said, “Alright, then I agree. Camp Lord can rest assured.”

Desbarres nodded, then he walked over to the cabinet with the liquid metal sphere. He tapped for a light screen to appear and then entered a passcode. The glass covered opened and the liquid metal sphere was revealed.

It was a sphere a meter in diameter and looked like a huge metal bubble. The metal surface was still flowing. And most importantly, this thing was floating inside the glass cabinet.

Seeing the metal, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone. Then he waved his hand, sending the liquid metal to the Space. After storing the item, he turned to Desbarres and said, “Camp Lord, let’s head back.”

Desbarres nodded and placed the measureless golden sand into the cabinet. Then he turned around and left the treasury along with Tao Wang and Zhao Hai.

Upon leaving the treasury, Zhao Hai immediately returned to his room. He already told Desbarres that he would be closing up. Then he went to the Space.

The moment Zhao Hai introduced the sphere of metal to the Space, a prompt was heard, “Synthesized liquid metal sphere detected. Liquid metal can be used in conjunction with magic formations. Liquid metal can be analyzed through the Universal Scanner. Liquid metal can also be reconstructed through the Universal Processing Machine. Liquid metal can be unified with the Host’s staff. The staff will turn silver and will increase in strength. The staff will then help the Host in using formations and layered formations. The original abilities of the staff will remain unchanged.”

Zhao Hai nodded at the prompt. He understood that the sphere of liquid metal could be joined with his staff. Moreover, since this metal can aid in using magic formations, the staff could also assist him in using Magic Theory.

Zhao Hai’s staff could still assist him in using magic formations before, but not much. This was because even if the staff had a lot of materials, like the 12 ultimate weapons, the Hell King’s ship, as well as its other upgrades, these materials weren’t specially designed for Magic Theory. They were more inclined towards the Cultivation Realm’s formations. Zhao Hai was able to use magic formations with the staff entirely because the staff was able to transform itself and change to suit magic formations.

But now, if the liquid metal was incorporated to the staff, the staff would now have compatibility for formations. It can be said that the staff was now geared for Magic Theory.

It was because he heard this prompt that Zhao Hai quickly returned to the Space. He wanted to see what other pleasant surprises the liquid metal could give gim.

Upon entering the Space, Laura immediately welcomed him. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “What happened to the liquid metal?”

Laura smiled and said, “I’m sorry, Brother Hai. We’ve already fed that thing to the scanner. Once it’s done analyzing, you can have a look.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly and said, “You’re really impatient. If I came later, then would you have already completed it?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “We can’t do that. We know that the process is beneficial to you. We just want to see the item’s composition.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, after the liquid metal is done being analyzed, fuse it to the staff. Also, have the scanner find the most compatible 14,850 formations for the metal. Then add those formations into the staff.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, there’s no need to do that. Even if a compatible set is found, you still wouldn’t be able to find a use for it. After the liquid metal combines with the staff, it would also be integrated to the Space. So as long as a formation is analyzed by the scanner, the staff would have it. However, with Young Master’s current strength, you still wouldn’t be able to use formation sets over a hundred layers. But after your strength is improved, you can even use millions of  layered formation sets. Therefore, there’s really no need for you to analyze formations for the staff.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai’s expression lit up. Then he said, “Really? Will the staff really change that much after adding the liquid metal? Right, the liquid metal hasn’t been combined with the staff, how do you know its effects?”

Cai’er replied, “Young Master, don’t forget that when the liquid metal entered the Space, it has already been branded. Now that the Space is level 150, as long as it brands something, then it will immediately carry on an initial analysis. Therefore, although the liquid metal hasn’t been unified with the staff, the Space can already figure out its future ability.”

Zhao Hai nodded. His face was lit up, he was just too happy. The stronger the staff was, the better it was for him. With his current strength, he could only use thousand-layer formations. And after adding the liquid metal, the staff unexpectedly increased his ability by 100 times. This would allow him to layer about 100 thousand magic formations. This was absolutely good news for Zhao Hai.

According to Leng Wuyeng’s deduction, as long as one could use 100 thousand layer formations, then they could contend with general powerhouses in the Cultivation Realm. This means that as long as the liquid metal merged with Zhao Hai’s staff, then Zhao Hai would have means of protecting himself in the World of Cultivation.

This was what made Zhao Hai glad the most. The reason he flew to the Machine Field was because he had enemies in the Cultivation Realm. If he ascended in the Cultivation Realm, then most experts there would squash him. Because of this, he didn’t dare enter Cultivation Realm.

After knowing the result, Zhao Hai relaxed. He didn’t proceed to condense magic formations. This was because he had already condensed all formations that were made public. After thousands of years of development, the Machine Field made more than 13 million formations. If all of these formations were layered together, then its power was surely hard to imagine. Zhao Hai can be sure that even experts in the Cultivation Realm wouldn’t be able to block formations made with a million layers.

However, with Zhao Hai’s present strength, his limit was only a thousand layers. He has to rely on the staff and liquid metal to use 100 thousand layer formations.[1]

What Zhao Hai must do at this time was to practice the Stellar Tempering Body Technique. This wondrous benefits to the technique seemed infinite. And there was also the fist technique that could be used against the enemy. Zhao Hai believed that as long as he practiced, he will certainly gain great advantages.

In the beginning, Zhao Hai could only practice the tempering technique for two hours each day. But after days of practice, he was able to increase it to three hours. One shouldn’t look down on this one hour of increase. For Zhao Hai, this additional hour can make double the effects of the body tempering technique.

Besides practicing the Stellar Body Tempering Technique and practicing his layered formations, Zhao Hai was also busy with another matter, researching the composition of magic runes.

Actually, Zhao Hai himself couldn’t remember and understand all magic runes. His ability to use magic runes was mainly the Space’s merit, not his own accomplishment. The Space was like an automatic memory storage, recording all of the runes that had been seen. Whenever Zhao Hai saw a rune, the Space would immediately give him the relevant information about it.

However, in the end, these things didn’t belong to Zhao Hai. Because of this, he could only use existing formations, he cannot create new ones. This was also the Space’s biggest weak point. The Space was merely a tool that can help you accomplish tasks. It cannot help you create something new. Without a proper understanding of the core principles, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to create new things.

Therefore, Zhao Hai began studying magic runes by himself. This way, he can create his own formations. And with the Space, he wasn’t afraid of making trash formations. What he needs to do was write magic formations down and analyze them.

* * *

This is the number the raw say.. Been reading forward to know if it is accurate, but there has no sign yet

Chapter 1126: Heading Out

Zhao Hai spent the entire month practicing inside the Space. Ever since the staff and the liquid metal fused together, Zhao Hai gave it the name Liquid Silver. Zhao Hai also took this time to get familiar with Liquid Silver. At this moment Zhao Hai could use 100 thousand-layer formations sets.

Since Zhao hai already told Desbarres that he needed to close up, Desbarres gave the word that nobody should disturb him. Besides hoping Zhao Hai to prepare for the beginner competition’s qualifiers, Desbarres also hoped that Zhao Hai could complete the liquid metal. Not only would this give Zhao Hai benefits, this advantage would also extend to the Machine Field.

In this month, Zhao Hai practiced the Stellar Body Tempering Technique and also familiarize himself with his new staff. At this point, Liquid Silver could no longer be called a magic staff as it was now closer to being a magic artifact. It was more of an item than a weapon.

Liquid Silver didn’t only have the Blood Ghost Staff’s ability, it also gained the liquid metal’s characteristics. The staff can be used both offensively and defensively.

Zhao Hai wanted to see to what extent he could use the weapon. This way, he would know how to use his abilities more effectively.

Zhao hai could now use Liquid Silver to achieve 50 thousand layered formation sets. Even if it was 100 thousand, there wouldn’t be any need to spend too much time.

And just like what he expected, if he only used his spiritual force to use Magic Theory, then he could only use 1 thousand-layer formations. But with Liquid Silver’s support, his formations could reach 100 thousand layers. This strength was increased by nearly a hundred times.

In this one month, the Bone Symbol Camp was quite calm. Everyone did what they needed to do. Some of the less convinced members went to get tested. But after the test, they didn’t mention entering the Six Realm Beginner Competition anymore.

And also during this time, Tao Wang and Desbarres were in agony. Zhao Hai wanted to close up, so they didn’t dare disturb him. They didn’t know anything about the liquid metal’s progress. Without any knowledge about Zhao Hai, the two couldn’t help but get more sleepless as the time limit was approaching.

Unlike the Bone Symbol Camp, the entire Machine Field wasn’t calm. The Bone Symbol Camp didn’t have any competition for their participants. However, the same wasn’t true for the other camps. They could only fight, sometimes kill, their opponents so that they could progress further and be chosen as the representative for their camp.

Every external hall camp in the Machine Field was filled with bloodshed. It was precisely because of the Bone Symbol Camp’s calmness that it was considered unique in the realm!

The newcomers of the Bone Symbol Camp were also paying attention to these competitions. After seeing the number of casualties each camp had, they quickly lost their motivation to join the competition. The rewards might be very good, but you would need to take lives in order to gain it. And once they participate in the qualifiers, if they didn’t win, they would either be injured or dead. If this happened, then they would have lost everything.

The internal competition of the Ashley Family’s camps only lasted for three days. Three days later, the Ashley Family’s eight External Hall’s camps would proceed to compete with each other. Then they would select 10 ascenders to be the Ashley Family’s representatives in the Realm’s qualifiers.

One shouldn’t think that ten people from the Ashley Family was a very small number. Medium-sized influences in the Machine Field numbered several thousand. And if one adds those lower-sized powers, there would be even more participants. The Ashley Family having a quota of ten people was already an evidence of their status in the Machine Field.

The common language of the Six Realms was strength. The more strength you had, the more benefits, advantages, and favors you would gain.

Every time the beginner competition happens, the Machine Field would have a 100 slots. Compared to the thousands of ascenders who want to participate, 100 slots was too small of a number. It was precisely because of this that the three major powers of the Machine Field carried on intense internal assessments for their representatives. In the end, each power was given a quota based on their strength. First-class forces could send 20 people to the qualifiers, second-class could send 15, third-class was 10, fourth-class was five, and then one for fifth-class.

Naturally, this metric wasn’t absolute. But changes to quotas could only decrease, never increase.

With this setup, there would be over ten thousand people participating in each realm qualifier. Selecting 100 people over more than ten thousand meant that the 100 left in the end would be the cream of the crop!

The Bone Symbol Camp didn’t gain any good results the last few times the Bone Symbol Camp participated in the Ashley Family’s qualifiers. In the end, they didn’t get any slots in the realm qualifiers. It was precisely because of this that people thought that the Bone Symbol Camp had fallen.

But in the past few times that the Bone Symbol Camp had attended, they would at least send five people. But this time, Desbarres only listed on person, Zhao Hai!

If the eight camps want to enter the family’s internal competition, then they would have to send their list of participants a month before the event. Moreover, it was prohibited to change this list. This was because once people find out which people were participating, then they might replace their participants.

The Ashley Family decided to do it like this because they want the eight camps to investigate the participants and get familiar with their fighting style. Besides the Bone Symbol Camp, all other camps sent ten participants. Only the Bone Symbol Camp would submit less than the maximum number of people.

In the last competition, the Bone Symbol Camp sent five people to participate, but this time they only sent one. This caused an uproar in the Ashley Family. Not only the Ashley Family, the other people in the Machine Field were also baffled. They didn’t expect the Bone Symbol Camp to only send one person. In their minds, the Bone Symbol Camp has truly fallen.

As the days passed, the day for the family’s competition approached. However, Zhao Hai had yet to come out. Desbarres and Tao Wang couldn’t help but worry even more. They sent people to stroll outside Zhao Hai’s villa every day. They want to see if there were any sounds inside. But to their disappointment, Zhao Hai was completely silent.

On this day, Desbarres was currently sat inside his office, his face showing his anxiety. At this moment, Tao Wang entered the room. Upon seeing his assistant, Desbarres immediately asked, “Did he come out?” Tao Wang smiled and shook his head and said, “The family qualifiers is happening the day after tomorrow. If Little Hai fails to come out, then he would miss his chance for the Six Realms Beginner Competition.”

Desbarres let out a long sigh. He smiled bitterly and said, “If he missed it, then he missed it. It’s also good if he doesn’t join. With the brutality of the competition, he would be safer if he doesn’t join it. Moreover, since he had closed up for one month, then it means that the thing had some use for him. If he can make use of it, then it’s worth it even if he missed the competition.”

Tao Wang nodded, then his eyes shone as he said, “If Little Hai can use that thing, then it wouldn’t only be the luck of the Bone Symbol Camp. It would also be the luck of the Ashley Family and the Machine Field.”

At this time, Desbarres’s computer made a sound. Desbarres looked at his wrist, the name on it made him stare. It was Zhao Hai calling him.

Desbarres stared for a moment before he opened his computer and happily greeted, “Little Hai!” Then Zhao Hai’s image can be seen on the screen.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s face, Desbarres asked, “Little Hai, how is it?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, I’ve completed it. I named it Liquid Silver. Right, Camp Lord, when will the family’s qualifiers start?”

Desbarres immediately replied, “The day after tomorrow. Are you done with everything? Me and Tao Wang want to see it.”

Zhao Hai understood what Desbarres wanted, he wanted to see Liquid SIlver. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright. I’ll prepare some food while waiting for you.” Desbarres nodded, then he closed his computer and turned to Tao Wang, “Let’s go see Little Hai.”

Then he took off with Tao Wang following closely behind.

Tie Shen has been busy doing tasks outside, so he was rarely in the camp. However, he was coming back. After all, the Ashley Family’s internal competition was approaching. For the camps, this event was very important. And now that the Bone Symbol Camp was only sending one participant, this means that this was the most crucial event for the camp in the last 20 years. This was something that Tie Sheng wouldn’t want to miss.

Before long, Desbarres and Tao Wang arrived at Zhao Hai’s villa. Zhao Hai was already waiting for them in the living room. Tinkle was the one offering everyone food, Zhao Hai just sat.

When Desbarrres and Tao Wang entered the room, Zhao Hai smiled at them. He didn’t say anything and just waved his hand, taking his silver staff out. The staff was more than 2 meters long. Its entire body was bright silver and at its head was a nine-layered silver lotus. On each tip of the lotus were small bells.

Liquid Silver’s form didn’t differ too much from the Blood Ghost Staff. However, its aura changed. Now, the staff looked more holy compared to its fierce appearance from before.

Chapter 1127: Life and Death Stage!

Dark Demon Planet, Lofty Demon Island, Life and Death Stage

Normally, only a few people were present in the Life and Death Stage. Only people hostile towards each other would duel there. In the Life and Death stage, injuries and deaths didn’t matter, only enmity was taken into account. Average people wouldn’t use the stage to take care of their enmity.

The Life and Death stage was a huge metal platform with a width and length of 100 meters. Each corner of the stage had a column with crystal stones, covering the stage with a barrier that won’t let energy go through. This way, the spectators on the sides wouldn’t be harmed.

Surrounding the stage were seats that could accommodate thirty thousand people. The VIP seats were based on the north side. People of status would sit in this area. Meanwhile, the other three sides were saved for the civilians. Anyone can sit on these three areas to watch the duels.

Usually, unless it was related to them, normal people wouldn’t come to this place. This was because the killing aura in this place was too heavy.

Lofty Demon Island’s area is huge, but the Life and Death Stage was placed on a small corner of the island. To be exact, the stage can’t be regarded as part of the island. Instead, it was on a huge reef just outside. It was only connected to the island by bridges.

This day, in the normally desolate life and death stage, were a lot of people. There were numerous cards stopped at its parking lot outside. The spectator area was also packed with people. However, the northern area was empty. Naturally, this meant that the Patriarch had yet to arrive.

Then at exactly 9 a.m, melodious bells began ringing. The original bustling life and death stage suddenly turned quiet. The members of the Ashley Family were too familiar with these bells. This was the Ashley Family’s World Bell!

The Ashley Family had plenty of special traditions, for example, there’s the World Bell as well as the Police World Drum!

The World Bell was used whenever people with influence arrive and the area needed to be quiet. As for the Police World Drum, this would be used to issue a warning whenever danger came. Then all of the family’s combatants would have 30 breaths to get ready. If they weren’t ready in 30 breaths, they would be executed.

Along with the Ashley Family’s strong regulations, as soon as the World Bell rung, the audience immediately turned silent. Those who dared deliberately open their mouth would be executed.

The World Bell rang three times and then people began falling straight down from the sky. At the lead of these people was a man wearing a black mage robe and holding a black cane. He already had some white hair, but his face was ruddy, looking stern and defiant.

On his side were people with Mage Robes as well as Warrior Clothing. Desbarres was also among these high-level people.

The person at the lead was the Ashley Family’s current Patriarch, Thunder Ashley. There were eight people around him. Two of them were managers of the internal government, two were external affairs directors, and the other four were managers of various manpower branches. But there was something that was common among these eight people, all of them handled their own camp. They were all Thunder Ashley’s eight most trusted people.

The group stood on the life and death stage. Thunder Ashley looked around him and then announced, “Six Realm Beginner Competition, Ashley Family’s internal qualifiers, officially begins!” Then he moved along with his entourage towards the northern spectator area.

When the group entered their reserved seats, a transparent glass immediately emerged from the ground, separating them from other people. Some of the other core members of the Ashley Family also entered and sat on their own seats.

At this time, a middle-aged man appeared on the stage. This person was also a fatty. But compared to Desbarres’s ferocious face, this man was much more lovable, with a round face and a thick smile. He looked like someone you could fool. However, to those who knew this person, if you dared to make a fool of him, then you would die. This fatty was also quite famous. His name was Cadjo. He was someone Thunder Ashley grew up with. His current position was the Ashley Family’s general manager, he is also the Chief Manager of Desbarres and the others.

With Desbarres’s ferocious face as well as his kill count, he was named as the Killer Fatty. However, in the Ashley Family, there was another fatty with a much higher fame than him. This man was Cadjo. He killed more people than Desbarres, but his face wasn’t as ferocious. He was the type of person who had a smiling face with a terrifying heart. Because of this, he was given the nickname of Smiling Demon Cadjo!

As soon as one hears these nicknames, one would know its meanings. Desbarres was given the name Killer Fatty while Cadjo was named a Demon. From this point, one could see the difference between the two.

At the same time, one shouldn’t look down on Cadjo’s position of General Manager. He was the person Thunder Ashley trusted the most, his relationship with Thunder Ashley’s children was also quite good. Thunder’s children treated him with great respect. It can be said that, in the Ashley Family, Cadjo was the number 2 after the Patriarch.

Cadjo stood on the stage with his big and wide smile. On the other hand, everyone in the Life and Death Stage were giving him their full attention. Nobody dared to look at him in contempt.

Cadjo looked around the stage before he said, “Today is a grand event for our Ashley Family. The Ashley Family’s talented individuals will go on this stage and fight for the family’s honor. I invite the 71 brave individuals from the External Hall’s camps to stand on the stage!”

Just as his voice fell, two teams came out into the Life and Death stage. Some of them wore Mage Robes while the others wore Warrior Clothing. On their bodies were badges with a dark mist skeleton emblem. This was the Ashley Family’s badge. However, there were small differences in their badges. For example, below the dark mist skeleton in Zhao Hai’s badge were two criss-crossed bones, making it look like a pirate flag. This meant that Zhao Hai was from the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp.

After the contestants entered the life and death stage, they quickly stood in groups according to their camps. The other groups had ten people while Zhao Hai stood alone, looking somewhat pitiful.

Cadjo also saw Zhao Hai, but he didn’t say anything and just said, “We’ll have the computer arrange everyone’s numbers.” Then after he said that, a ship appeared on top of the stage which released a light screen that formed a projection in mid-air.

Names began to appear on the screen, from number 1 to 71. Zhao Hai’s number was at the middle, number 36.

After the numbers were shown, Cadjo looked at the projection and said, “For the first battle, we’ll draw two numbers from the list.”

Just as his voice fell, the projection began to roll two numbers. Finally, two numbers appeared, number 2 and number 58. Not only did the names of two participants appear on the screen, their faces and details were also displayed.

Zhao Hai also looked at the screen and saw that both were three-year ascenders and level 2. One was a Mage and the other was a Warrior.

When Cadjo saw that both sides had been decided, he said, “Alright, I’ll have to ask the other participants to leave.” Zhao Hai and the others who were in the life and death stage left and sat on the seats reserved for them.

At this moment, people in the VIP room began discussing the battle. Desbarres was sitting next to Thunder. From this point, one could see Desbarres’s position in Thunder Ashley’s heart. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have sat this close to the Patriarch.

Thunder looked at Zhao Hai through the glass, then he turned to Desbarres and said, “Fatty Des, you’re too stingy in sending fellows. You protect your people too much. That isn’t good. And this time, you only sent one. Do you want to lose sooner to ease your worry? Also, I’ve read reports about this kid. He just ascended four months ago. Are you making it too easy?”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Patriarch, rest assured. I will not disappoint you this time. I might have sent only one person, but I can guarantee that you will be surprised.”

As soon as he heard Desbarres, Thunder couldn’t help but stare. At this time, a nearby person said, “Fatty, there’s no point in bragging. Your camp hasn’t sent more than eight people to participate in the competition. And every time, you’re defeated early. This time, you even sent a young kid. I don’t even believe people who ascended for four months to be able to use spiritual qi.”

Desbarres didn’t need to look to know who was talking. It was one of the four managers, Dia. Dia was brought into the Ashley Family’s management 20 years ago. Him ad Desbarres had always disagreed with each other. The two were always fighting each other in the dark.

Nevertheless, Desbarres wouldn’t fight him too seriously. After all, Dia was also a member of the Ashley Family. If they were to fight for real, then the family would be heavily affected. For someone who grew up in the Ashley Family, this wasn’t something that Desbarres wanted to see.

Since Desbarres didn’t want to fight him head on, Dia began to think that Desbarres was afraid of him. Because of this, he would frequently make a jab at Desbarres during public situations. Seeing that it was difficult for him to retaliate, Desbarres chose to endure.

Thunder also knew about Desbarres thoughts. To be honest, he didn’t like Dia. Thunder and Desbarres grew together, so he understood his friend the most. Thunder was aware that the Bone Symbol Camp was lacking a super expert. But in terms of comprehensive combat power, the other seven camps couldn’t contend with the Bone Symbol Camp. Because of this, Thunder just turned a blind eye at Desbarres’s passiveness.

Upon hearing Dia, Thunder couldn’t help but wrinkle his brows. Desbarres gave Dia a glance before he sneered and said, “Dia, how about we make a bet. I bet ten million that Zhao Hai will take first place in the competition. If he gets first, then you’ll give me ten million. Conversely, if Zhao Hai fails to get first place, then I lose ten million to you. What do you think? Do you dare?”

Chapter 1128: Going on Stage

As soon as Dia heard Desbarres, he couldn’t help but stare. This was the first time Desbarres bet on something. Moreover, Dia was clearly aware of how sly Desbarres was. One shouldn’t look at his ugly and terrifying face as well as his fat build, this fellow wasn’t stupid. Conversely, the way this person plots was truly terrifying.

People who liked to plot would make sure that they won’t suffer losses. And Dia knew that Desbarres was someone who only took profits and not loss. And now, this person actually proposed a bet. There was certainly something going on.

Dia couldn’t help but turn towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was currently on the side of the stage looking at the battle. There was nothing much to look at. Although the Mage was level 2, he was still having problems using Magic Theory. Perhaps he was too used to using his magic in the lower realm. However, this method was no longer powerful in the upper realm.

The Warrior was also having similar problems. Although he can already send out his sword qi, it was obvious that he was burdened every time he used it. Therefore, he wasn’t sending his sword qi out and instead did melee combat with the Mage. The Mage was constantly moving as he shot magic towards the Warrior. It was a common type of Warrior vs Mage combat from the lower realms.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and shook his head. He then closed his eyes. All participants already had information about each other. However, this was the first time they saw each other in battle.

As for Zhao Hai’s information, the only thing people knew was that he had ascended four months ago. He was a complete greenhorn. In their minds, Zhao Hai had offended Desbarres. Because of this, the Camp Lord sent him to this stage. This was basically murder using a borrowed knife.

In fact, after seeing this information, even Thunder had the same idea. But when he heard the bet Desbarres was about to make, he couldn’t help but doubt this thinking. Then he turned to Desbarres in confusion.

Desbarres was intently waiting for Dia’s reply. Dia looked at Desbarres and said, “Desbarres, how are you so sure?”

Desbarres coldly snorted and said, “Why do you care? Will you bet or not?” At the same time he showed glee in his eyes. As soon as he saw Desbarres’s eyes, Dia knew that he was bluffing. Zhao Hai couldn’t be an expert. Desbarres was just using this to make him afraid of doing a bet.

Dia thought himself smart when he deduced this. He immediately felt a great opportunity. He turned to Desbarres and coldly snorted, “Why wouldn’t I? Of course I’ll bet!” Desbarres willed his expression change, but he still said, “Alright, then it’s decided.” He didn’t care about Dia after he said that.

Seeing Desbaress’s appearance, Thunder couldn’t help but feel worried. This fatty just dug a pit, and Dia happily jumped into it.

Thunder grew up with Desbarres. Because of this, he could understand the fatty’s manners. He knew that Desbarres wouldn’t go into matters that he didn’t have control over. Since he made a bet with Dia, then it’s certain that he believed his contestant would win.

With this thought in mind, Thunder couldn’t help but feel more curious about Zhao Hai. He knew that Desbarres wouldn’t lie about the time Zhao Hai ascended. Every ascender was assigned a robot and was managed by the ascender reception tower. These two places were controlled by the three major forces and were not subject to anyone’s jurisdiction. Even the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to touch it. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s basic information should be true.

Since Zhao Hai’s records weren’t a problem, then this meant that Zhao Hai was a true four-month ascender. Moreover, he was invited by Desbarres one month after he ascended. There’s also the ten million machine coin bet that Desbarres made. From this point, Thunder Ashley could gauge Zhao Hai’s strength.

Thunder turned towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was currently closing his eyes. He was motionless, as though he fell asleep.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s state, Thunder couldn’t help but knit his brows. Zhao Hai’s action was unsatisfactory. As a participant who is about to fight, he shouldn’t give up the opportunity to observe his opponents. Generally, two kinds of people do this. The first kind are those who were arrogant. They think that they are invincible and didn’t bother observing their opponents. The other kind are those with absolute strength. They would know at a glance how strong their opponents would be. They don’t care how strong their enemy was as they are confident in winning.

Thunder thought that Zhao Hai should be the latter type. But even so, he still hoped that Zhao Hai would pay attention to the matches. This was because there were experts who lost to opponents weaker than them just because they were uninformed. And those who participate in this competition had one or two tricks up their sleeves. If one doesn’t pay attention, then they would suffer under their opponents.

It didn’t take long before the first battle ended with the Warrior’s win. However, this result didn’t make Thunder happy. This was because the skill of the two combatants wasn’t high, even to the point of being weak. If they participate in the Machine Field’s qualifiers with this strength, then they would come back defeated or even dead.

To any power in the Machine Field, the realm qualifiers was very important. Only through the qualifiers could a family get a lot of benefits. The higher their placement, the more benefits the family would receive. In the past years, the Ashley Family’s talents weren’t too good. They weren’t even able to join the top 100 in the last competition. This made Thunder very disappointed.

It was also for this reason that Thunder turned a blind eye on the camp’s brutal elimination methods.

As battles go on, Thunder’s expression turned more serious. Although the levels of the combatants were quite good, they still fall short compared to the talents from the other powers.

Being the Patriarch of the Ashley Family, Thunder also attached great importance to the talents of the other powers. It was especially true whenever the beginner competition was approaching. With their interests on the line, each power would look into the participants from other groups. It was because of this that Thunder understood how high the average strength of talents were.

Thunder also knew that this didn’t mean that the eight camps weren’t training their newcomers seriously. In fact, the camps from other powers weren’t any better than the Ashley Family’s. There were even some who were much worse than the Ashley Family’s. Other families were just taking a different approach in training their participants.

Actually, this approach wasn’t anything special. The key point to this training were the innately talented ascenders. From the day they entered the camp, all of the camp’s resources would be immediately spent on them. Naturally, a program like this would produce more competitive talents compared to the Ashley Family. However, this also came at a disadvantage. Since most resources were focused on a select few, the cultivation of the other members would lag behind, causing the overall strength of the camp to go down.

Thunder knew what these people were thinking. In their minds, ascenders simply weren’t included in their groups. These ascenders were merely tools in order to further the family’s benefit. This mentality caused their method to be fundamentally different than the Ashley Family.

The Ashley Family attached great importance to their External Hall. And because of this, they were somewhat famous in the Machine Field.

What Zhao Hai didn’t know was the fact that discrimination existed in the Machine Field. However, this discimination didn’t target different races. Instead, its focus was on the lower realm ascenders.

A large part of the World of Cultivation’s natives held a feeling of superiority over lower realm ascenders. In their opinion, those born in the upper realms were a cut above those in the lower realms. Because of this, not a lot of them placed great importance towards ascenders.

Thunder looked at the participants in today’s competition. If compared to other camps, their strength was actually very good. However, when it came to competitions, they fall short. Thunder began to consider reorganizing the family’s camps and carry on targeted training.

The competition carried on, but Zhao Hai had yet to fight. With 71 contestants, there would be 35 battles while one participant would get a bye. Nobody protested this setup, after all, luck was part of one’s strength.

Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious. He just sat there and recalled the runes he studied. At this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but praise magic rune study. Runes could be said to be the essence of magic formations. Only once someone understood runes could they become better at using magic formations.

At this time, 24 battles had already happened. Although the first battle didn’t last long, more than 20 battles lasted quite a long time.

However, the spectators didn’t complain. This was because the battles were becoming more and more intense.

This intensity was caused by both sides becoming more and more ruthless. After 24 battles, three already died while 5 were heavily injured.

Just in the recent 24th battle, a Warrior in the Body Symbol Camp broke the opponent Warrior’s sword and killed them on the spot.

Although Zhao Hai had his eyes closed, he was still aware of the things happening on the stage. He didn’t feel any discomfort from what happened. If he wanted to survive in the Machine Field, then he would have to kill people. Moreover, hadn’t he killed people before?

At this time, the sign for the 25th battle appeared on the huge screen. Then an announcement was heard, “25th battle, Bone Symbol Camp Zhao Hai versus Ghost Symbol Camp Luo Zhi!”

Then after a short pause, another announcement was made, “Zhao Hai from the Bone Symbol Camp is a newcomer that has ascended just four months ago. He was able to gain the recognition of Camp Lord Desbarres a month after his ascension. After closing up for two months, not only did he adapt to the Machine Field’s spiritual qi density, he was also able to break through to level 2 Mage. One couldn’t deny that he is an absolute talent!”

“Ghost Symbol Camp’s Luo Zhi has already ascended for four years. He’s also a rare talent in the Ghost Symbol Camp, being able to succeed in task after task. He is a level 3 Warrior. And because he has killed a lot of people, people outside the family called him Blood Ghost Luo Zhi. This battle is a showdown between two talents!”

When Zhao Hai heard his name, he opened his eyes and slowly walked towards the stage. As for the spectators, they were all humming in discussion. All of them were talking about Zhao Hai as well as his short time in the Machine Field.

Although he was able to hear these discussions, Zhao Hai wasn’t fazed by it. For Zhao Hai, entering this competition was basically him bullying other people.

Before long, Zhao Hai got up the stage. His opponent was already standing there. Blood Ghost Luo Zhi wasn’t tall and didn’t look strong. However, he had an indifferent face. He wore blood red Warrior Clothing while his sword was at his waist. His sword was a little longer than normal. Its length was approaching a small spear’s. It doesn’t seem to look like a sword.

Zhao Hai looked at Luo Zhi and couldn’t help but knit his brows. Although this Luo Zhi didn’t look anything special, his killing aura was very strong. One could see that he was skilled in killing people.

When the stage’s shield was raised, Luo Zhi took his long sword out and waited for the signal. It didn’t take long before Cadjo announced the start of the battle.

Upon hearing the signal, Luo Zhi didn’t immediately charge like the other Warriors to get to the Mage’s side. In Luo Zhi’s mind, he was a level 3 Warrior against a recently ascended rookie. As long as he sent his sword qi flying, the other side would certainly be cut in half.

However, what made Luo Zhi surprised was the fact that his Mage opponent didn’t erect a shield like other Mages. Zhao Hai was just calmly standing there, his expression showing that he seemed to not care about his situation.

Luo Zhi stared, then he sneered and said, “Kid, you’re quite unlucky to run into me in your first battle. You might be a genius before this battle, but after I’m done, you will be a dead genius.”

Zhao Hai just calmly looked at the opposite party. He didn’t take his magic staff nor did he release a protective shield. This caused Luo Zhi to feel that he was being despised!

Chapter 1129: Magnificent Performance

When Luo Zhi saw that Zhao Hai didn’t reply, even set-up any defense, his expression turned ugly. His eyes became cold. Then he directed his killing intent towards Zhao Hai. He knew that Zhao Hai was a newcomer. And for those who killed only a few, being hit with a killing intent as strong as his would certainly make them panic. Then as long as they lost focus, an opportunity would appear.

Zhao Hai continued to look at Luo Zhi despite feeling the killing intent washing over him. He didn’t care about the other party’s killing aura. To Zhao Hai, this kind of pressure was pitifully weak.

Seeing Zhao Hao remain unflinching, Luo Zhi’s heart tightened. Not responding to his killing aura only meant one thing, the other party was also used to killing. Such a person wasn’t easy to deal with. And after remembering Zhao Hai’s ascension, Luo Zhi’s eyes turned murderous.

Luo Zhi was a realistic person. He wasn’t a Warrior in the lower realm, but instead an Assassin. Because of this, he preferred his unusual sword.

Assassins experience a much crueler world than Warriors. In the world of Assassins, failure meant death. And you won’t only need to watch out for your enemy, you also need to watch your back against your allies. This was because if you can’t surpass your peers and become the most powerful person, then you would be left behind at any time. And being abandoned meant death.

Because of this mindset, Luo Zhi had always wanted to be the best. And if someone appears that might surpass him, then his choice was very simple. While the other party was still weak, he would kill them.

It was also because of this mindset that Luo Zhi became famous in the Ghost Symbol Camp. Those talents comparable to him were now dead. And now that Zhao Hai appeared, Luo Zhi began to feel a threat. He felt that Zhao Hai was going to surpass him, becoming a famous genius.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t in the same camp as him, they were in the same family. With the internal competition in the family, Luo Zhi would certainly kill anyone who might become his opponent.

Luo Zhi looked at Zhao Hai and began to feel threatened. He took a deep breath. Although he was threatened by Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai had yet to protect himself. Luo Zhi saw this as the best opportunity for him.

Luo Zhi calmed down his mood and then began to slowly raise his sword. The tip of the sword was aimed at Zhao Hai. Then he exhaled as he gripped the sword with both hands.

The build of the Luo Zhi’s sword was the same build as huge swords in the lower realms. The actual sharp part of the sword was only 30 centimeters from the tip. As for the rest, it was no different as a flattened spear, it didn’t have any cutting power at all.

Luo Zhi grasped his sword with his two hands as though he held a spear. He pointed his weapon at the calmly standing Zhao Hai. Seeing this stance, Zhao Hai finally opened his mouth and asked, “You want to kill me?”

Luo Zhi stared. He thought that Zhao Hai wouldn’t speak to him. But now, Zhao Hai disrupted his rhythm by speaking. Although he had yet to attack, the mental battle had begun. Zhao Hai’s few words just broke Luo Zhi’s momentum.

Luo Zhi’s eyes narrowed. He didn’t know if Zhao Hai deliberately did this, but he didn’t answer. Zhao Hai looked at Luo Zhi’s expression and smiled faintly, “I saw the killing intent in your eyes. So do you want to kill me? Why? We work for the same family, why do we need to kill each other?” Luo Zhi coldly snorted and said, “We work in the same family. But you should know that if I kill you right now, the family will place more importance towards me, giving me more resources to cultivate quicker.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he replied, “So it’s like that. This isn’t the first time you did this? Killing people who seem to get in your way?” Luo Zhi coldly snorted and said, “Less talking, it’s time for you to die!” Before Zhao Hai could move, Luo Zhi’s sword qi was already stabbing towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and whispered, “Shield!” After he said that, a five-layer formation appeared in front of him. Then a giant metal shield flew out of the formation, blocking Luo Zhi’s sword qi.

A sneer appeared in Luo Zhi’s face. He was a level 3 Warrior, so how could a mere five-layer formation stop him? Zhao Hai must be dreaming!

However, something shocking happened. When the sword qi hit the shield, the shield only lightly trembled. Then the sword qi slid from the shield and hit the life and death stage’s barrier.

Luo Zhi stared. He couldn’t believe that his full powered strike was deflected by Zhao Hai’s five-layer formation. How was this possible?

It wasn’t only Luo Zhi, those who knew Luo Zhi were also baffled. They knew that Luo Zhi wasn’t someone who would show mercy. All of his moves were aimed with the intent to kill. He never sparred with another person, and those who asked to fight him were all dead.

After blocking Luo Zhi’s strike, Zhao Hai didn’t stop as he waved his hand, releasing a 10-layer formation. Then he whispered, “Turning Wind, Blade of Ice, Behead!” As his voice fell, a group of tornadoes began to appear. The tornadoes became bigger and bigger until they became 20 meters in diameter.

And inside these tornadoes were an uncountable amount of ice blades, all attacking towards Luo Zhi.

When he saw Zhao Hai’s attack, Luo Zhi’s expression changed. He immediately waved his sword and released sword qi towards Zhao Hai’s tornadoes.

Since Luo Zhi’s attention was on the tornadoes, he failed to notice Zhao Hai casting a 10-layer formation once more. The formation turned golden yellow and then it blinked with red light. Then Zhao Hai whispered, “Fire Arrows, Barrage of Ten Thousand, Release!” Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the magic formation set blasted out and released an uncountable amount of red fiery arrows, blasting towards Luo Zhi.

Luo Zhi had just broken through the ice blade-filled tornadoes. When he saw the arrow rain that Zhao Hai shot out, his expression turned manic. He frantically waved his sword in order to block every attack coming his way. But just as he blocked a red arrow, it suddenly exploded!

This explosion wasn’t just a simple fireball. One should know that the arrow was made out of the metal element. That is to say that when the arrow exploded, shards of metal spread out. One of these shards found their way into Luo Zhi’s eye. Luo Zhi screamed, the sword in his hand forgetting to defend.

What happened next was easy to predict. Arrow after arrow hit Luo Zhi’s body, then they exploded. By the end of the rain of arrows, Luo Zhi’s body could no longer be seen. His long sword left behind lying on the stage.

The area turned silent. Zhao Hai and Luo Zhi’s fight was too short, not taking up even five minutes of time. Luo Zhi attacked first with his sword qi, which Zhao Hai defended and then Zhao Hai retaliated with two spells. And that was the end!

When the two began to move, the audience were loudly clapping. But by the end of the battle, everyone was silent. Nobody made a noise. This was because Zhao Hai’s magic was both mesmerizing and terrifying!

Nobody could deny that Zhao Hai’s magic was enchanting. His metal element shield, the icy tornado, and then the fiery explosive rain of arrows, all three were beautiful to look at.

And these three magics were as terrifying as they were beautiful. The shield was but a 5-layer formation, nevertheless it was able to fend off an attack from the level 3 Warrior. This showed how uncommon the formation set was.

The following two spells weren’t much worse. Although the icy tornadoes were broken by Luo Zhi, the pillars of wind with ice shards in them looked like revolving pillars that seem to turn wild at any time.

Normal people might praise the spell for its beauty, but for Desbarres and the others, what they saw was the terror behind the spell. If anyone was surrounded by the magic, then they would be shredded as though they had been sent into a meat grinder. Upon thinking about the outcome, anyone would feel chills crawling up their body.

As for the rain of ten thousand arrows, once one was overwhelmed, their outcome wouldn’t be good. This was especially true after the arrows exploded. The fire mixed with the fragments of metal looked much like fireworks.

And in the midst of these arrows was Luo Zhi, a level 3 Warrior. Upon receiving these spells, not even his body was left behind. Such spells were more than scary, they were terrifying!

I was a magnificent and terrifying display!

All those who understood what was going on couldn’t help but think of Zhao Hai’s spells as both magnificent and terrifying. It was like a beauty with a hidden terrifying trait. It was too scary!

The everlasting smile on Cadjo’s face vanished. He heard the conversation between Zhao Hai and Luo Zhi. To be honest, he wasn’t against Luo Zhi’s procedure. Those who wanted to raise their head above others needed to tread on top of countless corpses. Cadjo just didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this powerful.

If Cadjo didn’t know Desbarres, then he would’ve suspected Desbarres of bringing a level 5 Mage pretending to be level 1 for the competition. Those who can instacast ten-layered formations only belong to level 5.

Everyone inside the VIP room were also stunned. They didn’t expect Luo Zhi and Zhao Hai’s battle to end so fast. When Zhao Hai stepped down from the stage, Thunder turned towards Desbarres and said, “Desbarres, are you sure that he ascended four months ago?”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Of course. When he ascended, he was assigned to room number 2046. He memorized magic runes on his first day in the academy and then reached level 1 a month after. After that, he was sent for an exam to Tyro Planet. Patriarch should already know about all of these matters.”

Chapter 1130: Have Him Join the Ashley Family

Thunder Ashley nodded. Naturally, he knew about these matters. After all, they were related to his daughter. He just paid little attention to Zhao Hai in the past. And after Zhao Hai closed up, his name was never heard of again.

At this time, an Internal Hall manager asked with curiosity, “Desbarres. I know that the level of your Bone Symbol Camp isn’t good. Those spells used by the kid, I haven’t seen them before.”

Desbarres smiled bitterly and said, “Alright, are you mocking me or praising me? And what do you know about the strength of the Bone Symbol Camp? I can only say that Zhao Hai is a genius. He has a lot of formation sets in his hands, and all of it were created by him. The formations he used already existed, but the sets were all made by him. I have seen some of his creations and to be honest, they are really really strong.”

As soon as those present heard Desbarres, they couldn’t help but stare. Then all of them looked at Desbarres with shining eyes. Desbarres saw their reactions and he bitterly smiled as he said, “I know what you are thinking. You want other Mages to learn Zhao Hai’s formation sets? Forget about it. Zhao Hai is indeed willing to hand over his formation sets, but only a few individuals can study them. Don’t forget, Zhao Hai is an all-element Mage. His formation sets have two or three elements in them. Their might  is certainly huge, but if you’re not an all-element Mage, then those formations are useless.”

Everyone nodded upon hearing Desbarres. The formation sets Zhao Hai used were indeed from multiple departments. The power was great, but most Mages couldn’t use it.

Everyone couldn’t help but sigh. Thunder turned towards Desbarres and whispered, “Desbarres, tell me the truth. What is the kid’s strength?”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “He should be level 4. But even I won’t dare to fight him. I reckon I could lose to him.”

Desbarres was a level 6 Mage. When Thunder heard this, his eyes couldn’t help but narrow. Then he chuckled and said, “It seems like luck has finally come to you. You actually gained a treasure.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Right, I really picked up a treasure. In fact, he has more than you think. Patriarch, I’ll report something to you later.” Thunder blinked when he heard Desbarres. But he nodded and turned to look back at the stage. Thunder now wanted to know what Zhao Hai had that made Desbarres value him highly.

Before long, the 35 battles ended. The competition’s first day had ended. All victors will rest for two days before competing again.

After the competition ended, Zhao Hai returned to his room to rest. Desbarres also issued a strict order stating that Zhao Hai shouldn’t be disturbed.

Desbarres didn’t return to the Bone Symbol Camp, instead he followed Thunder back into the family. Desbarres and Cadjo entered the study with Thunder. After Thunder waved his hand to invite everyone to sit down, he turned to Desbarres and said, “Fatty Des, tell me. There’s no need to be mysterious.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Young Master, it’s good news. It is about Zhao Hai.” When outside, Desbarres would call Thunder ‘Patriarch’. However, when they were alone, he would call him ‘Young Master’.

Thunder nodded and said, “This Zhao Hai is very good.”

Cadjo also nodded and said, “He’s calm. And not too forgiving either. He’s a skilled kid.”

Desbarres looked at the two and smiled, “Young Master, Smiling Demon. Remember the thing I have in the treasury? The item a Machine Field legend left behind?”

When Thunder heard Desbarres, his brows couldn’t help but raise. Then he asked, “You mean the failed product? You still have it? I thought you sold it because you lacked money.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “It’s more useful to keep it. Young Master, that thing has been completed by Zhao Hai. He’s currently using it.”

Boom! Desbarres’s words were like a huge bomb exploding inside Thunder and Cadjo’s minds. Since the two knew what the item was, they also knew the conditions of completing it. They thought that nobody in the Machine Field could complete it. And now, Desbarres told them that it had been formed. It was no wonder that they were surprised.

Desbarres saw their reactions and laughed, “What? You might not know, but Zhao Hai already completed it and is now using it as his staff.”

Thunder stood up, he stared deeply into Desbarres and said, “Datty Des, don’t joke with me. Did Zhao Hai really complete it? How did he do it? You should know that a lot of people worked together in the past, but they still weren’t able to complete it.”

Desbarres nodded and said, “Zhao Hai has done it. But he took the clever route. He added a material in the production and engraved 131,490 formations in one go. This caused the final stage to succeed. Now, he called the thing Liquid Silver.”

Thunder gawked, “It really succeeded? People thought of this method before, but they haven’t found the appropriate material. What did he use?”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Measureless Golden Sand!”

“Measureless Golden Sand! So it’s measureless golden sand? No wonder.” Cadjo called out in alarm. One must know that measureless golden sand was a very precious material. Who thought Zhao Hai actually had it.

Desbarres nodded, “Little Hai also gave me a bottle of it. I already stored it inside the treasury. But Liquid Silver is truly evil. After Little Hai completed it, it became his exclusive item. No matter what method we try, that thing is only a hunk of silver metal in our hands. But in Zhao Hai’s hands, it became ever changing. It can turn into all kinds of weapons, it’s godly.”

Thunder nodded and said, “Divine Artifacts always recognize their owners, that’s normal. Also, that thing had always been useless in our hands, it’s good if it can be used by Zhao Hai. This way, he could give benefits to the Ashley Family. But Fatty Des, is Zhao Hai loyal to the Ashley Family? Won’t he run to other groups?”

Desbarres shook his head and said, “Young Master, you can rest assured. After observing him for the past few days, I discovered that Zhao Hai is very sentimental. Since we’ve been treating him properly, he will not betray us. You don’t need to worry.”

Thunder nodded, “I have tried the refining method you brought back last time. Did you send a reward Zhao Hai? Right, I heard that he’s still living inside the camp’s building?”

Desbarres smiled bitterly and said, “Forget it, that kid is a training madman. I’ve already sent his reward over, but he had yet to move to his villa. He’s inside the camp every day, training. I don’t know how to handle him.”

As soon as Thunder heard Desbarres, he nodded and said, “So it’s like this. But I still think he needed to be rewarded. Fatty Des, we need to make him satisfied with the Ashley Family. We can’t afford to have him leave.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Young Master, I have something in mind. But I’m afraid you won’t agree.” When he heard Desbarres, Thunder stared. Then he waved his hand and said, “Tell me. He has limitless future. I’m willing to pay anything as long as we get to keep him.”

Desbarres replied, “I don’t want to restrain him. Instead, I want to have him join the Ashley Family. Only once he becomes one of us would he never leave.”

As soon as Thunder heard Desbarres, he paused for a moment. Then his expression changed as he said, “You mean Margaret?”

Thunder and Margaret’s relationship wasn’t good. Of course, this issue was with Margaret. But even if Margaret wasn’t intimate with Thunder, Thunder still placed Margaret next to his heart.

Thunder had five sons and three daughters in his entire lifetime; with Margaret being the youngest. His two other daughters had already married while Margaret stayed single. Margaret was Zhao Hai’s instructor and had already experienced difficulties with him. This was the reason for Desbarres’s suggestion.

Cadjo knit his brows and said, “Fatty Des, your idea is good. But with Miss Margaret’s temper, I’m afraid she wouldn’t agree.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Of course I know about that. But I wasn’t thinking of matching them immediately. Instead, we should let them develop feelings for each other. Also, the last time I saw them together, Miss Margaret already had little thoughts about Zhao Hai. Let’s have them meet more often and see what happens.”

When Thunder heard this, he relaxed. He always felt that he had been lacking towards Margaret. Because of this, he didn’t want to force Margaret into things for the sake of the family. So after he heard Desbarres, he nodded and said, “Alright, then let’s have them meet more often. Right, Fatty Des, don’t tell anyone else about Zhao Hai’s matter. We don’t want him to suffer any accidents.”

Desbarres nodded. To be honest, Thunder was being seen as a tyrant in the family. There are only a few people who he would listen to, among these were Desbarres and Cadjo. As for the others, he wouldn’t even hear them out.

Thunder stood up and said, “The Ashley Family had always been lacking during the past beginner competitions. With Zhao Hai, I hope that we can reach greater heights.”

All great families give priority to their benefits. If a person was useful for them, then they would give them importance. If they couldn’t be used, then they wouldn’t place them in their eyes. Thunder was the same person. If Zhao Hai cannot give him a satisfactory result, then he would deal with him with no hesitation. Then he would snatch Liquid Silver away.

Chapter 1131: Kill Ruthlessly For Fame!

Desbarres completely understood Thunder’s character. The reason why he told Thunder about Zhao Hai’s Liquid Silver was because he knew that as long as Zhao Hai strives for the Ashley Family, then Thunder wouldn’t take Liquid Silver back. Conversely, if he didn’t tell Thunder about this matter, then once Thunder found out about it, the situation would become complicated. Not only would Zhao Hai not be spared, even the Bone Symbol Camp might experience bad luck.

At the same time, he also proposed the plan for Margaret. Since Thunder doesn’t want to have any conflict with Margaret, then he wouldn’t make a move on Zhao Hai.

It was strange to say that even if Thunder was very overbearing, he had an unusual preference for Margaret. Thunder would pay attention to any matter that involved his daughter. Because of this, Desbarres wished Margaret to be with Zhao Hai. This way, Thunder would never become Zhao Hai’s enemy.

………………

Desbarres’s mood wasn’t very good when he returned to the Bone Symbol Camp. He was very exhausted. In the past, although Thunder’s temperament wasn’t good and was sometimes overbearing, he still loosened up when it came to Desbarres and Cadjo. There were even times where they would joke around.

But recently it was different. Thunder was becoming more and more moody. Desbarres found himself watching his words more. And even if he made a joke, it was deliberately thought through.

This feeling caused Desbarres to become exhausted. It was because of this exhaustion that he meddled in the family’s matter less and less. Instead, he focused more on the Bone Symbol Camp.

Although the External Hall was something that the family needed, this requirement didn’t mean that it was crucial. In the eyes of a great family like the Ashley Family, the function of External Halls was to work for the family’s benefits. It can be said that ships and mechs were the family’s core power. Mages and Warriors weren’t included in this list.

Desbarres was clear about this point. Because of this, he made sure that nobody would look at the External Hall. And also to not incur Thunder’s doubt.

Upon returning to the camp, Desbarres directly went to Zhao Hai’s villa. He was aware that Zhao Hai was currently in a bottleneck on his cultivation. Becoming stronger in a short time was impossible. Therefore, Zhao Hai wasn’t closing up like before.

When he arrived outside Zhao Hai’s villa, Desbarres heard voices coming from inside. In addition to Zhao Hai’s voice, Tao Wang and Tie Sheng’s voices were heard.

Upon hearing the voices of these three, Desbarres couldn’t help but smile. Tie Sheng and Tao Wang were people loyal to him. Moreover, their abilities were very good. And there was no need to say about Zhao Hai’s talent. Because of this, Desbarres favored him. It can be said that these people had become important for Desbarres.

Desbarres pushed the door open and saw the three already in the dining room and drinking. Upon entering the room, Desbarres loudly said, “Good, good. It seems like you didn’t wait for me before you start drinking.”

The three immediately turned to look at Desbarres. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, if you came back later, then we might have to drink until late at night.”

Desbarres ignored the three’s greetings as he sat on the table and poured himself a drink. After taking a sip and savoring the fragrance of the alcohol, he said, “Little Hai, you’ve performed magnificently today. You don’t know this, but I made a ten million coin bet with Camp Lord Dia of the Ghost Symbol Camp. If you don’t get first place in the family competition, then I will have to pay him ten million coins. So make sure that you don’t lose.”

Tao Wang stared, then he said, “Ten million machine coins? Camp Lord, where did you get that much money? Don’t tell me you’ve been embezzling family funds?”

Desbarres slapped Tao Wang’s side and said, “What nonsense. You think you know more than me about the camp’s finances? Why do I need to embezzle funds? From what I can see, you’re the one cheating us money. Tie Sheng, don’t come here tomorrow. Instead, let’s go to Tao Wang’s. Let’s freeload off of him for one month for speaking nonsense.”

Tie Sheng looked at Tao Wang and smiled, “Good. I wanted to do this for so long, Camp Lord. However, this fellow doesn’t treat anyone. This is a good opportunity to freeload.”

Tao Wang looked pitiful as he answered, “Camp Lord, you can’t do this to me. I’m really poor. I even need to eat Little Hai’s food because I can’t buy for myself. How about we wait for Little Hai to win the competition and then we have a meal with your winnings from the bet.”

Almost at the same time, Desbarres and Tie Sheng gave Tao Wang a despising look. This fellow Tao Wang was a good person, but he was extremely stingy. However, nobody really took this banter seriously. Everyone present weren’t short of money, they were just teasing Tao Wang.

After joking around, Desbarres’s face turned serious as he said, “Alright, let’s talk about proper business. Little Hai, I’ve informed the Patriarch about Little Silver. He didn’t say anything about it and just hoped that you can gain good achievements. The Patriarch has become more and more obstinate in the past few years. He doesn’t listen to any criticism. If you don’t give good results, then he definitely won’t let you off.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Camp Lord, rest assured. I know what to do.”

Desbarres nodded, then he sighed and said, “Little Hai, I hope you don’t blame me for revealing this matter to the Patriarch.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I won’t. I know that Camp Lord might feel embarrassed about this. However, it’s impossible to hide this matter from the Patriarch. If the Patriarch is late in finding out about this matter, then he might suspect that something is going on.”

Desbarres sighed once more, then he said, “The Patriarch might be unaware of this, but his temperament has become more and more erratic. Even someone like me who grew up with him has to be more careful when in his audience.”

Desbarres was currently trusting Zhao Hai because he saw that his origins were very clean. Zhao Hai hardly interacted with other people. And although Zhao Hai had killed a lot of people in the lower realms, he was good to people around him, which was similar to Desbarres’s manner. Because of this, Desbarres’s impression of Zhao Hai was very good.

Tie Sheng and Tao Wang didn’t say anything. Their situations were also similar to Zhao Hai. After being chosen by Desbarres and introduced into the Bone Symbol Camp, they were trained and gained his absolute trust. This was also the reason why Desbarres was able to say these words to the three of them.

Zhao Hai was silent like the two. But Tie Sheng and Tao Wang’s expressions were somewhat difficult. The two of them knew that the only reason why the Bone Symbol Camp can still make their money was Desbarres. If Desbarres was gone, then the Bone Symbol Camp would find it hard to keep their businesses.

Outsiders might be clueless, but the others in the External Halls weren’t. They could see that the members of the Bone Symbol Camp were living more comfortable lives than them. Because of this, all of them cast envious eyes towards the camp. But because of Desbarres, nobody dared to make a move.

However, it was impossible for Desbarres to protect the Bone Symbol Camp his entire life. And without Desbarres, what would the Bone Symbol Camp do? Because of this, Desbarres settled on Zhao Hai. He was hoping that Zhao Hai could become a powerful expert as soon as possible so that he could protect the Camp. With his presence, other people would think twice before making a move on the camp.

Desbarres took his glass and drank the liquor in one go. Then he turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do you have a wife in the lower realms? What do you think about Margaret?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. He wasn’t a beginner that he was completely clueless about what was going on. However, he already had Laura and the others. And he didn’t want to get a new wife soon.

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction and sighed, “I really feel pity for Miss Margaret. Her relationship with the family isn’t very good because of her mother’s death. Actually, the family really cared about Miss Margaret, but she didn’t want to be cared for by the family. And there was also her marriage with the Fire Temple, making her unhappy. I told the Patriarch that Miss Margaret seems to be interested in you. The Patriarch didn’t oppose and he even hoped that Miss Margaret would be associated with you. Little Hai, this is your opportunity to join the Ashley Family. Only by becoming a member of the Ashley Family would the Patriarch let you keep Liquid Silver. Otherwise, the family might want to reclaim it in the future. When the time comes, your situation will be complicated.”

Zhao Hai’s expression changed. Desbarres drank another glass before continuing, “I handed Liquid Silver over to you because I didn’t expect that you would actually complete it. Now that you have completed it, Liquid Silver has recognized you as its owner. If one wanted to get Liquid Silver, then they would have to kill you. Liquid Silver’s power has never been seen before. Ever since it has been passed down, there were a lot of people in the Machine Field that were looking at its progress. Once people know that you have completed Liquid Silver, your well-being will be placed in chaos. Trouble will constantly chase you.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes narrowed. To be honest, he hadn’t thought through this point. In his mind, although Liquid Silver was very good, it was still on level with artifacts in the Cultivation Realm. However, he failed to think about the Machine Field.

A weapon like Liquid Silver had never appeared in the realm before. For powerful experts in the Machine Field, the allure of Liquid Silver would be difficult to suppress. Liquid Silver was basically the ultimate weapon for Magic Theory. It was the realm’s first divine weapon. Everyone would want to obtain it.

In the past, nobody was able to complete Liquid Silver, so nobody really cared about it. But now that it has been formed, people would desperately fight for it!

The worth of owning formidable weapons depended on its user. In the hands of powerful experts, only a few people would want to steal it. This was because a lot of people were afraid of offending a huge power. But if it was in the hands of a person with no identity, then the weapon would be a curse!

Although Zhao Hai was regarded as important by Desbarres, his present status was only a member of the Ashley Family’s External Hall. Such status would without a doubt be seen as unworthy of Liquid Silver. People would certainly chase him to steal the weapon.

But if Zhao Hai married Margaret, he would become a member of the Ashley Family. At that time, people would have to think hard if they wanted to steal Liquid Silver.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of being chased down. However, this matter would still bring him endless troubles. Zhao Hai hated trouble, but he hated relying on women even more.

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance and sighed, “Little Hai, I want you to associate with Miss Margaret for three reasons. First, it would benefit you. Second, it would be good for Miss Margaret. And third, it would be good for the Bone Symbol Camp. In the past few years, my involvement with family matters decreased. Although I still have some influence in the family, my power is becoming smaller and smaller. At this time, I can still support the Bone Symbol Camp. But what if an accident happens one day? Who would support the Bone Symbol Camp? Once you become a powerful expert, you will have to become the camp’s leader. But before you become strong, you would need an identity to support the camp. This way, the Bone Symbol Camp wouldn’t be touched by the other camps. Do you understand what I mean?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I understand. Camp Lord, I will consider what you said. To be honest, until now, I only have a sense of belonging to the Bone Symbol Camp. As for the Ashley Family, I still feel a distance between us. Also, I don’t want to bring Miss Margaret into his matter. It would be disrespectful to her. In the meantime, I’ll just make sure that people don’t find out about Liquid Silver.”

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai, then he suddenly laughed and said, “Alright, good. Little Hai, I haven’t misread you. I can see your virtue by hearing your words. It seems like Miss Margaret’s eyes are also good. Alright, I won’t barge into this matter anymore. But when the time comes, I hope that you won’t reject Miss Margaret outright. Try to know her a bit more.’

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t speak anymore. Desbarres poured himself another glass of liquor. Tie Sheng and Tao Wang did the same. Then Desbarres lifted his glass and said, “Let’s celebrate Little Hai’s win today with this glass. Little Hai, always remember, in the Six Realm Beginner Competition, there’s no need to hold back. Kill ruthlessly to gain reputation. You should know that other participants aren’t saints either. Only by being ruthless would you be safe. Understood?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Camp Lord, rest assured. I have never been lenient towards my enemy.”

Desbarres laughed and said, “Alright. Hahaha. Let’s drink!”

Chapter 1132: A Positive Worry

The day after Zhao Hai’s first battle, Margaret went to visit Zhao Hai. To be honest, Zhao Hai was currently feeling a headache.

After Desbarres and the others left yesterday, Zhao Hai returned to the Space. Laura and the others then discussed with him about the current matter. Zhao Hai didn’t know whether to laugh or cry after hearing the result. Laura and the others actually encouraged him to pursue Margaret.

If other men came across this matter, then they might feel heavenly. However, Zhao Hai was different. He already has Laura and the others. He still can’t believe that they urged him to pursue another woman.

And now, Margaret actually came looking for him. Zhao Hai sighed before opening the door and inviting Margaret in. After Margaret sat down, a robot immediately offered her tea. Then Zhao Hai opened his mouth and asked, “Instructor, do you need me for anything?”

Hearing Zhao Hai call her by her title, Margaret couldn’t help but feel slightly disappointed. She let out a long breath and said, “Camp Lord allowed you to join the qualifiers, it seems like he’s confident in your strength. However, you still need to be careful against those from the Ghost Symbol Camp. Camp Lord Dia doesn’t have a good relationship with our Camp Lord. Moreover, I heard about the 10 million coin bet. That isn’t a small number. Although Camp Lord Dia still had good income, 10 million will certainly cut through his wallet. And with the strength you showed yesterday, Camp Lord Dia will surely be vigilant. He will certainly arrange something.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I thought the same. The Camp Lord already reminded me of this yesterday. There’s no need to worry. I will certainly win.”

Margaret smiled faintly and said, “I don’t doubt your strength. But I think you should still make preparations. And I think you shouldn’t use your Undead on the stage. It will only reveal your cards. When the realm qualifiers start, others would know about your ability.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He could hear that Margaret cared about him. But he let out and sigh and said, “Instructor, feel relieved, I’ll be careful.”

Margaret nodded, then she stood up and said, “Alright, then I’ll believe you. Dins and the others will be safe in the academy. I will look after them.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Thank you, Instructor.” Margaret gave a nod, then she turned around and left.

After escorting Margaret to the door, Zhao Hai returned to his room. Then he heard Laura and the others complaining about how he called Margaret by her title. They were telling him about how big of an idiot he was.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. Other’s wives would scold their husbands if they were to see other women outside. On the other hand, his wives were offering him advice to pursue another woman.

While thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s body flashed and entered the Space. Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Laura and the others immediately surrounded him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, why did you call Margaret by her title? I can’t believe you. You could clearly see that she is interested in you.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and asked, “Laura, aren’t you jealous? Actually, I don’t have to do anything since I’m already strong. As long as I reveal my true strength, I don’t believe the Ashley Family would dare to do anything to me.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you’re too relaxed. The Ashley Family might not dare to touch you if you reveal your strength, but the family is just a medium-ranked power in the Machine Field. Not to say the Machine Field, if you reveal your strength, the World of Cultivation would get word of it. When that time comes, you won’t be able to seek shelter.”

Lizzy nodded and added, “Big Brother Hai, you should also know about Margaret’s situation. She’s engaged to the Zhang Family. However, the Zhang Family actually wanted to kill her. If she marries into the Zhang Family, then her situation certainly wouldn’t be good. Are you that cruel to leave her alone? After your last meeting, it is clear that Margaret has some feelings towards you. You should pursue her. There’s no need to worry about us, Big Brother. I know you love us, we love you as well. And for our family, we wouldn’t oppose you pursuing Margaret.”

Meg smiled and said, “Young Master, don’t forget your duty. You need to make the Buda Clan grow and expand.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Alright. I’m just worried about all of you, so I didn’t want to pursue Margaret.”

Lizzy and the others spat out their tongues and didn’t talk about the topic anymore. Zhao Hai inwardly sighed. This was because he wasn’t sure if this was really what Laura and the others wanted or if they were influenced by the Space. This was also the most annoying aspect about the Space.

Zhao Hai had no worries about using the Space to subdue his enemies. However, the Space seems to be influencing Laura and the others as well. This wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to happen. However, he has no ability to stop it right now. This was the reason why he could only sigh.

Zhao Hai clearly knew that the Space would always place his benefits first. Therefore, the current program was inevitable.

Whether it was influenced by the Space or not, Laura and the others wanted him to pursue Margaret. In this case, Zhao Hai didn’t want to betray their expectations.

After sighing once more, Zhao Hai finally allowed nature to take its course. Actually, he really didn’t have such thoughts about Margaret. But now that Laura and the others said it, Zhao Hai began to think about the situation. It seems like Laura and the others had already weighed the pros and cons of this action.

Zhao Hai returned to his room and started to study magic runes. Since there were a lot of magic runes present, Zhao Hai’s research started very slow.

Fortunately, after multiple breakthroughs, Zhao Hai’s spiritual force had become more formidable, allowing him things like an eidetic memory. Naturally, this eased his progress.

The day unconsciously passed by. Zhao Hai went out of the Space and returned to the villa. Then he sat down and prepared for the competition.

Desbarres and Tao Wang came in the morning along with Tie Sheng. Tie Sheng had already finished his tasks and had some free time. Naturally, he wanted to see Zhao Hai’s battle.

When Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the life and death stage, the place was already filled with people. Zhao Hai went to his seat and then closed his eyes.

The other contestants also arrived. The other 35 looked at Zhao Hai with difficult expressions. They saw how formidable Zhao Hai’s strength was. Among them, the strongest was only able to instacast five-layer formations. Moreover, after doing so, their spiritual force would be used up. But last time, not only did Zhao Hai instacast a 5-layer formation, he also followed up with two 10-layer formations. Such strength was terrifying for the other contestants.

Zhao Hai was aware that the others were looking at him, but he didn’t care. His attention was on the Ghost Symbol Camp’s participants. It must be said that the Ghost Symbol Camp was quite good. Of the 36 contestants left, 8 of them were from the camp. Besides Luo Zhi who Zhao Hai killed, only one other person was eliminated.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also discovered that their equipment seem to be different from before. Their armors and staffs were exchanged.

The eight looked at Zhao Hai with bad expressions. Naturally, Camp Lord Dia had already talked to them.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t care about them anymore. No matter how strong the equipment they were given, everything still depended on the user. Strong weapons could only be strong in the hands of the powerful.

At this time, Cadjo announced the beginning of the competition. The computer then began to cycle through the participants. The first battle of the day would be between a Mage of the Ghost Symbol Camp and a Mage from the Upright Symbol Camp.

The Mage of the Ghost Symbol Camp went on to the stage and completely crushed his opponent. The equipment of the enemy simply couldn’t catch up.

The staff used by the Mage from the Ghost Symbol Camp was a high-level item. It had a ten-layer formation inside. Even before the battle started, Zhao Hai knew that the Mage’s staff wasn’t inferior to the high-level goods he had in his hand.

After clashing for two rounds, the Mage from the Upright Symbol Camp finally admitted defeat. The Mage from the Ghost Symbol Camp proudly smiled before turning his head and glared at Zha Hai. The provocation could be clearly seen. However, Zhao Hai was just sitting there with his eyes closed, as though he was asleep.

Desbarres had an ugly face on. After the battle, he turned to Dia and said, “Dia, it seems like you really went all out. You even took out some new weapons. What? Afraid to lose 10 million?”

Dia snorted and said, “Of course I can afford to lose 10 million. I just don’t want to lose to you. I don’t believe Zhao Hai doesn’t have a special item on him. If he doesn’t have anything, he wouldn’t have been this strong just four months after ascending. Even if you deny it, nobody would believe you.”

Desbarres coldly snorted and said, “Don’t think that changing equipment will make you win. Let me tell you, Zhao Hai being first is already set in stone.”

At this time, the Upright Symbol Camp’s Camp Lord grunted, “Although your bet has nothing to do with us, we still got affected. At least our contestants relied on their own means.” Naturally, he was reluctant to accept the Ghost Symbol Camp’s win by having superior equipment.

In fact, it wasn’t only the Upright Symbol Camp, the other Camp Lords were also having difficult expression on their faces. Dia just gave his contestants an unfair advantage, causing their members to lose.

Chapter 1133: Testing Margaret

A light sigh was heard, making the VIP room quiet. Everyone who heard it couldn’t help but lightly cough. It was the Patriarch, it was clear that he wasn’t amused at what happened.

Thunder looked at those present and said, “What is going on with all of you? This is a place to fight for the family’s honor. Naturally, you need to use whatever means you could. Alright, we’ll postpone today’s battle. All of you have one day to prepare. Today’s first battle will not be counted. Now, go.” After he said that, he stood up and left.

Desbarres and the others stood up and gave him a bow. They all knew that Thunder was dissatisfied with the squabble. However, they were also dissatisfied with the situation. Therefore, they agreed to the postponing of the competition.

After Thunder left, Desbares turned to Dia and said, “You fool. Then next time you want to die, don’t pull us over.”

The others were also looking at Dia in contempt. Dia knew that he was in the wrong, but he still snorted and said, “Fatty, if it weren’t for your bet, I wouldn’t have done this. Don’t you want to flaunt that you are a rich old man?”

Desbarres smiled bitterly, then he looked at Dia and said, “Alright, I’ll let you off this time. However, everyone needs to go all out now. Let’s also dissolve the bet. If you weren’t willing to show-off that time, then I wouldn’t have proposed it. But whatever you do, Little Hai’s strength would still flatten you. Lister properly, make sure to tell your people to rein in their murderous intent. Or else, Little Hai might not show mercy.” After he said that, Desbarres turned and left.

Dia looked at the departing Desbarres and said, “Bah, what dogshit luck did this fatty have to find an expert like that.”

The other Camp Lords were also giving dark sighs. Not to mention being the External Hall manager, the fatty also had a good position in the family. On the other hand, even if they lorded over the camps, the family’s main strength lied on the battleship fleet. Desbarres grew up together with the Patriarch. Therefore, he had the Patriarch’s deep trust. Desbarres’s privilege of going out with ten ships without authorization was something that they didn’t have.

Because of this, the Camp Lord attached great importance to the Camps they were assigned to. They weren’t like Desbarres who grew up with the Patriarch. Desbarres took care of the Bone Symbol Camp because he held sentiment to the camp. Because of this, he protected the camp, not allowing any danger befall it. And because of his unique situation, Desbarres could afford to not care about the camp’s standing. Even if the Bone Symbol Camp did badly, the family won’t care about it.

But as for the other camps, the Patriarch always monitored the way they operate. If they cannot come up with results that can satisfy the family, then the Patriarch would not let them off easily.

It was also for this reason that the other camps employed brutal selection methods. It was only through this way that they could provide good results.

Although the other Camp Lords were in a dark mood, they quickly calmed themselves down. Then all of them left the stage in order to switch the equipment of their participants.

When the others heard that the competition was postponed, they obediently left, even those who were feeling vengeful.

Zhao Hai returned to the Bone Symbol Camp with Desbarres. Then the group went to Zhao Hai’s villa. After they sat down, Zhao Hai asked, “Camp Lord, why was the competition postponed?”

Desbarres smiled bitterly and explained the situation. Zhao Hai began to understand what was wrong. But then he smiled and said, “So all of them want to make more preparations. Hehe. In any case, the end result would still be the same.”

When he saw Zhao Hai’s reaction, Desbarres couldn’t help but remind him, “Little Hai, you can’t be negligent. Now that those fellows were given time to prepare, they would certainly arrange powerful items to support their participants. You can’t be so relaxed in your next battles.’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, you can rest assured. Even if I don’t use Liquid SIlver and my Undead, they are still not a match against me.”

Desbarres’s two eyes shone as he said, “You’re really that confident?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord, don’t underestimate my fighting strength. If I use Liquid Silver, even you are not my match.”

Desbarres nodded and said, “Alright, but things have changed. Make sure to have killing be the least priority. The Camp Lords have made an agreement. As long as their participants aren’t murderous, then don’t kill them. After all, nobody will benefit if people die. Also, the ten million bet has been cancelled.”

“What? How can this be? That 10 million is enough for me to eat in Little Hai’s until I die!” Without even waiting for Zhao Hai to comment, Tao Wang interjected.

Desbarres slapped Tao Wang before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “The External Hall’s eight camps might be in a competitive relationship, but we are also interdependent on each other. The eight camps aren’t treated as very important by the family. So if we always fight, then we would be finished. The Patriarch also knows this, so he allowed us to compete with each other. This way, the External Hall wouldn’t unite and become a threat to the family. Naturally, the Camp Lords also understand this. So even if there was fighting, nobody would go all out. At the same time, we make sure that we don’t show any sign of unity. This way, the Patriarch wouldn’t feel pressured. Everybody is in agreement with this aspect. Of course, if someone dared to resort to extreme methods, there’s no need to be polite.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He didn’t expect this competition to have this much strings connected to it. However, he decided to place it in the back of his mind. Then he ordered his two robots to prepare meals before asking Desbarres and the others to share a meal with him.

While everyone was happily eating, Margaret unexpectedly came. Everyone in the villa stared. Then Desbarres and the others gave a strange smile before quickly leaving the area. This caused Margaret’s face to turn red.

Seeing Margaret arrive, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Even blind people could see that Margaret was interested in him. Zhao Hai asked Margaret to sit down and then poured her some tea before saying, “Instructor, is there anything I can do for you?”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I heard that the competition was cancelled so that the other camps could return and exchange their equipment. I expected Uncle to give you some equipment, but I think that all of you would be drinking here. Sigh, Zhao Hai, don’t treat this competition lightly. It’s possible for you to die here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Instructor, you can rest assured. I have this matter completely in control. Moreover, the Camp Lords have already reached an agreement. As long as nobody goes to extreme methods to deal with me, then I cannot kill them. I’m not in any danger.”

Margaret frowned, then she said, “That’s no good. It’s too dangerous. This, take this. I’ll tell Uncle Des to prepare you a set of defensive equipment.” After she said that, Margaret took out a Mage Staff from her spatial equipment.

Zhao Hai looked at the staff and couldn’t help but gawk. This staff was very high-level. It was unexpectedly engraved with a 100-layer formation set. It was suited for level 4 Mages to use. He didn’t expect Margaret to lend him this staff.

Zhao Hai didn’t take the staff, instead he shook his head and said, “I can’t use that. And the Camp Lord has already given me something. It’s the best weapon in the Machine Field.”

Margaret couldn’t help but be curious, “Strongest weapon in the Machine Field?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You don’t know? It’s the failed item Leng Wuyeng left behind. It’s now mine, I call him Liquid Silver.” Then he waved his hand, making Liquid Silver appear.

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai decided to tell Margaret about Liquid Silver. Margaret had been good to him, so he couldn’t be indifferent to her. He also wanted to see her reaction upon seeing it.

Zhao Hai had too many secrets. Therefore, he would need to choose a woman who was virtuous. Laura and the others were also accepted by Zhao Hai with this method. Now, it was Margaret’s turn to be tested.

To be honest, if Margaret didn’t come and remind him today, then it might be hard for Zhao Hai to accept her. Now, Margaret’s worry touched Zhao Hai. Because of this, he decided to give her a chance.

Margaret knew about Leng Wuyeng’s failed weapon. Seeing Zhao Hai wave Leng Wuyeng’s weapon caused her to be shocked. She stared at the staff in Zhao Hai’s hand for a long time. She didn’t know what to say.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret’s expression and couldn’t help but smile. Then waved his hand, causing the staff to turn into liquid and then bind into his body, turning itself into a full body armor.

Margaret finally believed Zhao Hai’s words. She excitedly stood up and said, “This is fantastic. I didn’t expect you to complete the item left behind by Grandmaster Leng Wuyeng. Right, you cannot tell anyone about this matter or else you’ll suffer bad luck. Zhao Hai, does anyone else know about this?”

Zhao Hai smiled, then the armor reformed back into a staff. After that, he said, “Rest assured, not a lot of people know about this matter. Only you, the Camp Lord, Tie Sheng, Tao Wang, and the Patriarch.”

Margaret’s complexion changed, then she said, “You told him?”

Zhao Hai knew that she was referring to the Patriarch. He nodded and said, “Right. The Camp Lord was the one who informed the Patriarch.”

Margaret’s expression turned difficult. Then she said, “Why did you tell him? Fat Uncle, sigh. Now that he knows, he will certainly find ways to snatch Liquid Silver away from you. Not good, Zhao Hai, you’re in danger. You need to leave the Ashley Family as soon as possible.”

Chapter 1134: Challenge Tournament

Seeing Margaret being anxious, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. Margaret’s performance made Zhao Hai glad. However, he didn’t say anything about it. Instead he smiled and said, “Alright, there’s no need to worry about it. The Camp Lord has reached an agreement with the Patriarch. And the Patriarch already agreed for me to use Liquid Silver.”

When Margaret saw Zhao Hai’s confidence, she calmed down. But then her face turned red. She knew clearly that she had been naive. Since that person now knew that Zhao Hai had Liquid Silver, then it was already too late for Zhao Hai to walk away.

Moreover, her words looked like she cared for Zhao Hai. This caused her to blush. Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Margaret, thank you. Can I call you Margaret?”

Margaret discovered that she couldn’t bear to look at Zhao Hai in the eye. She lowered her head and gently nodded her head. Then she turned and ran out of the villa, not even saying goodbye.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret’s appearance and smiled. Then his body flashed and entered the Space. Upon entering the Space, Laura and the others immediately walked over, grinning. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai is truly fierce. You actually managed to make Margaret flee with a few words.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “I think its been a long time since I’ve dealt with all of you. And I’m feeling quite evil today.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, releasing metallic ropes from Liquid Silver to tie up Laura and the others. The women screamed and seem to resist. However, they had smiles on their faces.

…………….

The next day, the stage was filled with people once more. Zhao Hai was also in his seat. With Cadjo’s command, the computer began to roll for the participants in the first battle.

Zhao Hai just glanced at the battle and was quickly disinterested. On the other hand, the two contestants began to turn hectic. Their weapons and protective gear were swapped for better ones, causing the battle to be more dazzling.

The audience cheered for the battle. At this time, Zhao Hai also discovered that even if the battle had gone hectic, the two participants were holding back. The Camp Lords seem to have already told their members about not going extreme. The crowd’s excitement was great, but the battle was measured.

Zhao Hai saw this situation and began to feel relieved. In fact, even he didn’t want to kill people. If Luo Zhi didn’t want to take his life, then Zhao Hai might have spared him.

Battle after battle quickly went by. Zhao Hai was chosen to fight in the ninth battle. His opponent was someone from the Ghost symbol Camp. But it seems like this person had already been talked to. His gaze towards Zhao Hai didn’t have any killing intent, only a bit of provocation. Even if Dia told them to hold back, it seems like they were still not convinced.

Zhao Hai didn’t care, he looked at his opponent and then gave him a short bow as he said, “Please.”

Zhao Hai’s opponent couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this polite. He returned the gesture and then quickly took his magic staff out.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then waved his hand to release a formation. Then Zhao Hai said, “Concealing Fog!” The formation proceeded to blow up, covering the entire life and death stage with a dark mist.

Right after the dark mist covered the life and death stage, explosions began to be heard. However, those outside the stage were unable to see what was going on. The audience began to drink and scold. Naturally, the target of their scolding was Zhao Hai and his opponent.

After some time, the fog on the stage dispersed, revealing the stage. The two participants were still standing. However, the person from the Ghost Symbol Camp was now wearing his protective armor. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I admit defeat!” After declaring his surrender, he turned around and faced Cadjo, “I surrender.” Cadjo nodded, then he opened the barrier and let the two exit the stage.

The others were very dissatisfied. However, they knew that it was useless to complain right now. They only grumbled for a few moments before proceeding to watch the next fight. Fortunately, this time, there was no such thing like Zhao Hai’s dark mist.

After this day’s battles, there would only be 18 people left. Then tomorrow, these 18 participants will be reduced to nine. The day after that, the position for tenth place would be decided. Then after the tenth position was decided, the first place would be decided by a challenge tournament!

A challenge tournament was different from a normal tournament. Normal tournaments would have its combatants decided by a computer. On the other hand, in a challenge tournament, the computer would randomly select one person. Then that person would then accept challenges from the other nine. If nobody challenges this person, then he would be crowned first place and would claim the reward for being the champion. If people challenge him and he was defeated, then the winner would replace him on the stage. This cycle would continue until 9 people are defeated and one was left.

In such a competition, only the first place would be decided. The second, third, fourth place and so on weren’t chosen. In other words, besides the first place, the other nine would have equal placement.

Desbarres and the others have also briefed the participants of this arrangement beforehand. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. He was already settled on becoming first in this competition so that the Bone Symbol Camp would rise.

The next days, the 18 participants were reduced to 9. Naturally, Zhao Hai smoothly progressed. Although the others had their equipment changed, their strength still couldn’t match up to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t use too powerful formations. At most, he would use ten-layer formation sets. However, Zhao Hai’s formation sets were very powerful. Moreover, they were interchangeable. Up until this point, Zhao Hai had already used dozens of unique formation sets. This caused everyone to be startled.

One must know that the oldest ascender in this competition had ascended three years ago. At most, they could cast one or two formation sets. But now, there was Zhao Hai who showed dozens of formation sets. It was terrifying to think about.

Moreover, Zhao Hai just ascended four months ago. How was he able to get dozens of formation sets in that short time? Even those who ascended for a year would find it hard to do so!

Although the challenge tournament had yet to happen, everyone present knew that the first place holder could only be Zhao Hai. It would be impossible for the others to snatch this position.

In the past few days of battles, Zhao Hai didn’t use any weapon. He didn’t even show his magic staff nor his protective gear. He defeated everyone with his own strength. Not to say about the Ashley Family, even in the entire Machine Field, Zhao Hai should be the most powerful beginner present.

The days quickly flew past and it was finally the last day. It was the last day for the family qualifiers and the most exciting one, it was the challenge tournament!

Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the life and death stage. Besides Zhao Hai, there were two from the Ghost Symbol Camp, two from Wicked Character Camp, then the other camps had one participant each. One could see from this point how close the strength of the Ashley Family’s External Hall’s camps was.

The day of the challenge tournament was also the day where the stage had the most people. Not only did Desbarres and the others came, Margaret also went to watch. However, Margaret didn’t sit in the VIP room. Instead, she sat behind Zhao Hai’s seat where she could speak directly to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Margaret to come. When he saw here arrive, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he asked, “Why are you here?”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “I want to see you compete. You need to get first place.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry.”

Those who knew Margaret couldn’t help but be shocked upon seeing her interaction with Zhao Hai. Margaret’s relationship with Thunder wasn’t a secret matter in the Ashley Family. Because of this, people were clear about Margaret’s situation.

Due to how Thunder acted, Margaret had a certain resentment towards other men. She barely spoke to the opposite sex other than her elders. But now, she approached Zhao Hai. Who knew how many men threw their glasses down in sadness.

Zhao Hai also felt people’s gazes on him, but he didn’t care. He already expected this to happen.

Naturally, being in the VIP seats, Thunder was able to see everything. His eyes couldn’t help but shake as he turned to Desbarres and said, “It seems like what you said was true. Margaret indeed has a favorable impression towards Zhao Hai. Have you checked his background in the lower realms?”

It was clear that Thunder cared about Margaret. Therefore, he needed to investigate Zhao Hai’s status in the lower realm. Desbarres hastily nodded and said, “I have checked it. But Patriarch, you should know that these things aren’t necessarily accurate. What I know is that Zhao Hai is a Patriarch back in the lower realms. His clan is also a Dark Mage family. He’s also known to specialize in Dark Magic. However, he is also an all-element Mage as well as a Warrior. He’s both vicious and merciless. He uses his refining technique on people he killed. I’m afraid he had killed over a million people. Also, he has multiple wives in the lower realms. And it seems like he had a good relationship with his wives. The last time him and Margaret met, he still called her instructor. As for how it developed into this, I really don’t know.”

Desbarres didn’t boast too much about Zhao Hai and just told what he found. He knew that Thunder hated being deceived. And if Desbarres lied, then Zhao Hai and Margaret’s development would be cut short. Zhao Hai’s merciless and vicious manner as well as his multiple wives might be a weak point to others, but this wasn’t the case for Thunder.

This was especially true for Zhao Hai’s vicious attribute. In Thunder’s eyes, this wasn’t a negative, instead it was a strong point. As for Zhao Hai’s wives, Thunder didn’t say anything. Instead, in the eyes of Thunder and Desbarres, Zhao Hai left his wives behind in the lower realms. Him getting another wife in the Machine Field wouldn’t be an issue.

Thunder nodded and said, “I didn’t expect this kid to be that kind of person. More than a million people? Hehe, great. This is the kind of person the Ashley Family needs.”

Desbarres smiled and didn’t say anything. Thunder turned to Desbarres and said, “Take him to me later, I want to see him personally.” Desbarres nodded.

At this time, Cadjo arrived at the stage. He looked at everyone present before he smiled and said, “After several rounds of fighting, the Ashley Family’s ten brave combatants have finally been elected. And today will be their most decisive battle, the challenge tournament! Select the first person receiving the challenge!”

The computer rolled through the participants before settling on one. Upon seeing the person chosen, Cadjo couldn’t help but stare. His smile seemed to turn wider as he announced, “The first person on stage today shall be Bone Symbol Camp’s Zhao Hai! I ask Zhao Hai to come to the stage!”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect himself to be the first person on the stage as well. However, he just nodded towards Margaret before heading to the stage.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive on the stage, Cadjo immediately said, “Good. Now, the challenge tournament begins!” Then he proceeded to leave the stage.

Zhao Hai calmly stood on the stage. Meanwhile, the other participants couldn’t help but look at each other in dismay. They were clear about Zhao Hai’s strength, and they already knew that they cannot win against him. Because of this, the one who went first on the stage would only consume Zhao Hai’s spiritual force, making it easier for those following him.

Because the others knew about this, nobody wanted to be the first to issue the challenge. Cadjo didn’t care about this as he looked at the other participants and said, “According to the family’s rules, once a person stands on the stage for 1000 breaths then they would win. If nobody challenges Zhao Hai in 1000 breaths of time, then he will immediately claim victory. The timer starts now.” After he said that, a timer appeared on the computer screen. It started from 1000 and slowly counted down.

The other nine knew that this wasn’t Cadjo pushing them to fight. This was a well known rule of the Ashley Family. 1000 breaths of time was neither long nor short for these people to decide. The nine had ugly expressions after seeing the number on the screen counting down. They wanted to challenge Zhao Hai, after all their equipment has been upgraded. And these people were talents in their respective camps. They weren’t afraid of Zhao Hai, they just want to fight him.

When the number on the screen reached 300. One person could no longer keep calm. He stood up and said, “I’ll go.” Then he stood up and went towards the stage.

Zhao Hai looked at the man and identified him as a Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp. His strength was at level 3 and his fighting prowess was very good. His weapon wasn’t a sword and instead it was a spear. This spear was long at three meters in length. If others used this kind of spear, then they might find it hard to fight. However, this person was clearly talented judging by the fact that he was able to place in the top ten.

Chapter 1135: Flawless

After the Warrior got on the stage, he looked at Zhao Hai quietly for a while. Then he said, “Zhao Hai, you’re strong, very strong. But I’m not weak either. You’ve gotten arrogant. Refusing to use any weapon will be your biggest undoing. You should know that this is no longer the lower realms. Mages who don’t use weapons will not have any achievements, even if you are a genius.”

Zhao Hai just listened to the Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp. Then after the Warrior stopped talking, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m not refusing to use my weapon. But your strength is not enough for me to take it out.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Warrior couldn’t help but stare. His expression sunk, then he said, “Well then, let me make my move!” He raised his spear up and readied to attack.

When he saw this, Zhao Hai calmly waved his hand and muttered, “Shield” Along with his words, a shield appeared in front of him. This shield wasn’t as thick as a five-layer formation shield, but it still didn’t look weak.

The Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp sneered, then he thrust his spear forward, aiming towards Zhao Hai’s shield. What he released was still sword qi. Sword Qi was just a general description, therefore it was used whenever a Warrior in the Machine Field released an attack.

Zhao Hai just stood behind his shield and greeted the attack with a smile. The attack didn’t even budge the shield, there was no movement at all. When the Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp saw this, he couldn’t help but stare. At this time, he suddenly heard a voice coming from behind him, “Spear!” He turned around since he felt a sharp chill behind his neck. He knew very well that the opponent had a weapon pointed at his back. If he dared to move, then the other side wouldn’t mind attacking.

The Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp immediately held his hands up and said, “Alright, I admit defeat.” When he said that, Zhao Hai withdrew his magic. Then his body flashed back to the front of the Warrior “I accept.”

The Warrior from the Wicked Character camp muttered, “So this is Zhao Hai.” As he said that, he proceeded to head down from the stage.

Zhao Hai stayed on the stage and didn’t say anything. At this time, the eight remaining participants looked at each other. They seem to not know what to do.

Those watching at the side could see everything that happened. Zhao Hai just used two ordinary spells. One was a metal element shield while the other was actually a dark element spell.

Zhao Hai used his shield in order to distract his opponent. Then he used dark magic to attack the enemy with a spear from behind.

The entire process could be said to be very simple. However, this was the hardest thing a Mage could do when fighting.

All battles couldn’t last for too long. Even warships have reactor furnaces that needed fuel. And this fuel was limited, placing a time limit on how long a warship could fight.

Experts were the same. Whether they be Mages or Warriors, their battle qi and spiritual force could run out. Because of this, they couldn’t fight for a long time. A good example of this was Zhao Hai and Addison’s fight, both of them almost killed themselves from exhaustion.

When the Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp left the stage, the others were at a loss for a while. Although the fight wasn’t short, it wasn’t as long as they expected either.

They already knew that Zhao Hai was strong, so they intend to have the first person consume his spiritual force. But now, it seems like this plan was useless. This caused the other challengers to be clueless about what to do.

Even if the challengers were stunned, this didn’t mean that time wasn’t counting down. The computer began to count down from 1000 once more. If nobody issued a challenge by the time the computer finished counting down, then Zhao Hai would be the champion.

The timer continued to count down. However, the eight challengers below the stage were still looking at each other in dismay, which was the same situation they were in at the beginning.

Cadjo couldn’t help but commend Zhao Hai in his mind. Zhao Hai’s first victory was so flawless. Not only had it ended swiftly, it was also so clean and neat which caused a lot of pressure on the other challengers. Now, they need to think deeply about challenging Zhao Hai.

Ii can be said that Zhao Hai used this tactic to gain time for himself. It could also be a tactic to put pressure on the next challenger.

Calm! Terrifying calmness! This was Cadjo’s appraisal of Zhao Hai. Although the fight looked simple, Cadjo saw something different.

The challenge tournament could be said to be an unfair competition. The person on the stage would be repeatedly challenged by multiple people, wearing him out in the process. Therefore, the first person on the stage would generally be in the worst situation while the last man would benefit from it all.

However, Zhao Hai had been too calm in his first challenge battle. In turn, this created a huge pressure on the next challengers, causing them to hesitate. This allowed Zhao Hai more time to himself. This was the best method for someone who wanted to survive a situation that was designed to wear them down.

Finally, when the computer counted down to 200, the second challenger went up on stage. This person was also from the Wicked Symbol Camp. The Ghost Symbol Camp and the Wicked Symbol Camp both had two contestants in the challenge tournament. Now, both of the Wicked Symbol Camp’s participants have gone to the stage.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t dislike the people from the Wicked Symbol Camp. In fact, he didn’t care about the people from the other camps. He wasn’t even resentful towards the Ghost Symbol Camp. It was only those who wanted to kill him that he needed to kill.

The person from the wicked Symbol Camp was also a Warrior. His weapon was a normal two-handed broadsword. When he got up on the stage, he pulled his sword out and calmly looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai saw that the other party seems to be disinterested in talking, so he decided to stay silent. He just gave the other person a bow and then gestured to begin.

The Warrior was still intently looking at Zhao Hai and didn’t issue any response. When he saw this, Zhao Hai decided to make the first move. He waved his hand and released a magic formation. A spear began to depart from the formation and went directly towards the enemy.

The Warrior just stood there and didn’t have any intention to escape. When the spear was close to hitting him, his swung his sword and sent a sword qi out.

Zhao Hai has to recognize that the Machine Field’s metal element magic had very strong attacking strength. Although his spear couldn’t compare to the enemy Warrior’s sword qi, its might was equivalent to a level 1 Warrior. Seeing the enemy parry the spear effortlessly, Zhao Hai knew that the other was certainly an expert.

Zhao Hai’s two eyes narrowed. He knew what the other party was planning to do. They were planning to hold on as long as possible to consume Zhao Hai’s energy. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, he just waved his hand and released a fireball towards the Warrior.

The Warrior lit up with earth yellow battle qi. His broadsword also turned earth yellow before it sliced a fireball. But at the same time, Zhao Hai released a five-layer formation. However, this formation wasn’t like other attacking formations.

Most attacking formations would release an attack towards the enemy. On the other hand, this formation would make the Warrior from the Wicked Symbol Camp sink into the stage.

When the Warrior saw this formation, he couldn’t help but stare. He could identify that this was an earth element formation. However, the life and death stage was made out of metal. How could this earth element magic be useful?

When while he was puzzled, the Warrior suddenly felt the iron underneath his foot turn into quicksand, making his body sink down.

The Warrior was startled. He couldn’t understand how Zhao Hai’s spell could turn the metal stage into quicksand. However, he wasn’t given time to think about this. The Warrior exerted his energy to fly out. But at this moment, the quicksand suddenly turned into a bed of thorns. It was actually a combined formation.

Just after the Warrior managed to fly out, the earth below him began to rumble. Then a huge metal thorn began to fly out, shooting towards the Warrior.

The Warrior was greatly surprised. But just as he was about to take action, he discovered that it was already too late. Zhao Hai just released a 10-layer formation, the fiery arrow rain!

This arrow rain was the same formation Zhao Hai used against Luo Zhi. Because of this, the Warrior was aware of its might. Seeing that Zhao Hai was about to activate the formation, the Warrior quickly raised his hand and said, “I admit defeat!”

Just as the Warrior’s voice fell, Zhao Hai withdrew the formation. The life and death arena returned to its calm. The Warrior bowed to Zhao Hai and proceeded to get down from the arena.

Zhao Hai just stood there waiting for the next match. But this time, he didn’t need to wait too long. The other participants seem to realize that waiting too long would only be beneficial to Zhao Hai. Because of this, another challenger immediately jumped on the stage. This time, it was a Mage from the Ghost Symbol Camp.

The proceeding battle didn’t have any suspense. Although the Mage had a staff with a 10-layer formation inside, it still wasn’t a threat to Zhao Hai. After all, a recorded formation wasn’t part of a Mage’s strength. Everything still depended on a person’s combat ability!

Chapter 1136: Not Too Difficult

No accidents happened in the challenge tournament. With Zhao Hai’s overwhelming strength, he was able to become the last person up on the stage.

The challenge tournament allowed the Ashley Family’s External Hall Camps to see Zhao Hai’s strength. Without using any weapons nor supporting items, he was able to win against nine challengers. This was a first time for the Ashley Family’s qualifiers.

Right after the tournament was the awarding ceremony, held on the life and death stage. Thunder personally gave the prize to Zhao Hai. Actually, the prize was just a formality. Zhao Hai already had Liquid Silver, so he really didn’t need anything. However, it can be seen the Margaret had some influence on Thunder. Therefore, Thunder decided to give something to Zhao Hai. And the prize was also somewhat special. The first part of the prize was a sizeable bonus. While the second part wasn’t actually an item. Instead, it was a chip that recorded the Ashley Family’s secret formation sets.

This reward was proposed by Desbarres. And Thunder didn’t have any problem with it. In Thunder’s mind, Zhao Hai was already set to be a person of the Ashley Family. Zhao Hai was a member of the Bone Symbol Camp. At the same time, he had his relationship with Margaret.

Besides these two things, there was another reason for Thunder to give Zhao Hai the family’s formation sets. Since he was given the family’s formation sets, Zhao Hai could no longer think about leaving the Ashley Family. If he did, whether it be for Liquid Silver or the formation sets, Thunder would use the Ashley Family’s entire strength to destroy him.

Zhao Hai also understood Thunder’s message. Therefore, he wasn’t too polite and happily accepted the chip. And thus, the Ashley Family’s qualifiers was done.

As soon as the ceremony ended, instead of returning to the Bone Symbol Camp to celebrate with Tao Wang and Tie Sheng, Zhao Hai went with Desbarres to see Thunder.

Thunder received Zhao Hai inside his study. After Zhao Hai and Desbarres entered the room, they quickly gave Thunder a salute. Thunder nodded, then he waved his hand and said, “Sit.” Desbarres allowed Zhao Hai to sit. Thunder stood there and sized Zhao Hai up. After some time, he opened his mouth and said, “I heard that you’ve been very close with Margaret?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t expect Thunder to be this direct. But he still nodded and said, “I am. Miss Margaret is my Instructor, and our relationship is very good.”

Thunder raised his brows and asked, “Just your instructor?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Not just an instructor. I’ve come to care about Miss Margaret, she’s a precious friend.”

Thunder’s eyes sparkled for a moment and asked, “So just a friend?”

Zhao Hao smiled bitterly and said, “She’s just a friend now. But as for later on, who knows.”

Thunder looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and couldn’t help but laugh, “Good. Kid, I didn’t expect you to say that. Hahaha. Good.”

Zhao Hai didn’t make any noise. Desbarres turned to Thunder and said, “Young Master” Thunder looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I’ll allow you to be close with Margaret. However, I have a request.”

As he said that, Thunder’s gaze went cold, then he continued, “You got your hands on Grandmaster Leng Wuyeng’s ultimate weapon. And at the same time, you have the secret formation sets that the family collected for many years. You should understand that you’re now one with the Ashley Family. If you dared to betray the Ashley Family, then I will do what I can to take your life!”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he didn’t say anything. Thunder continued, “Recently, our Ashley Family hasn’t been getting good results in the Six Realm Beginner Competition’s realm qualifiers. I want to leave this matter for you to solve. From the 100 people that will qualify for the realm, I want you to place in the top 10.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows. Seeing Zhao Hai frown, Desbarres’s heart couldn’t help but thump. He knew that Thunder didn’t want people to disappoint him. If Zhao Hai couldn’t achieve this, then Thunder would certainly be furious.

When he saw Zhao Hai knit his brows, Thunder couldn’t help but feel his anger rising. But at this time, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “Top ten in the qualifiers? That’s easy, I will take top then in the Six Realm Beginner Competition!”

Thunder and Desbarres were stunned. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have such huge ambitions. Desbarres quickly said, “Little Hai, you know how powerful the guys from the other realms are, right? Are you that confident in Liquid Silver?”

With Liquid Silver, Zhao Hai could now use 100 thousand-layer formations at will. However, what Zhao Hai told Desbarres and the others was that he could use 10 thousand-layer formations. One must know that this ability was at the top of the Machine Field.

However, Desbarres understood that even if Zhao Hai could use a 10 thousand-layer formation, fighting people from the Cultivation Realm would still be hard.

The people from the Cultivation Realm also regarded the beginner competition as a very important matter. They would deliberately train new ascenders just for the competition. They would select the participants the moment they ascend. Then they would train and provide them with countless pills, techniques, and resources. All of this just so that they could achieve a good result in the beginner competition. With this setup, Desbarres believed that Zhao Hai would still be defeated no matter how many layers his Magic Theory formations had.

After he heard Desbarres, Zhao Hai shook his head, then he replied, “Even if I can’t cast that many layers of formations, I am still confident. I will try my best to win. I also want to see how Magic Theory fares against the other realms.”

Thunder looked at Zhao Hai, then he laughed and said, “Good, that’s what I want to hear. My request for you is the same. As long as you get top ten in the realm qualifiers, I won’t put myself between you and Margaret. And if you can really place top ten in the beginner competition, then not only the Ashley Family, the entire Machine Field would give you a huge gift.”

Zhao Hao nodded, then Thunder said, “Also, the realm qualifiers isn’t a joke. There are more than ten million participants. If you don’t take care, then you would certainly suffer a loss.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Thunder waved his hand and said, “Alright, you can go back.” Zhao Hai and Desbarres stood up and left after they gave Thunder a salute.

Once Zhao Hai and Desbarres were inside the car, Desbarres turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you’re too reckless. If you don’t reach the top ten in the beginner competition, then what would I do? You need to watch your promises next time.”

Zhao Hai knew that Desbarres had good intentions, so he didn’t refute his words. However, he was already settled on his decision. When the two arrived at the Bone Symbol Camp, they discovered that everyone was in a festive mood.

Everyone was so happy that one might think that it was themselves who won first place. Desbarres and Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle. However, Desbarres’s smile was bittersweet.

Desbarres had done too much for the Bone Symbol Camp. But even so, the Camp was still doing badly in the past few years. Being suppressed by other people made him really uncomfortable.

Now, with Zhao Hai here, the Bone Symbol Camp was starting to go above other camps. This caused everyone in the came to feel both proud and elated.

Seeing that Zhao Hai and Desbarres had come back, everyone in the Bone Symbol Camp cheered and welcomed them. Zhao Hai could not hear anyone. With too many people present, everyone sounded like they were mumbling.

Desbarres smiled upon seeing everyone. Then he loudly said, “Alright, everyone go to the dining hall. We’re drinking until we pass out!” Everyone cheered. The Warriors came over and lifted Zhao Hai and Desbarres before carrying them towards the dining hall.

Tao Wang and Tie Sheng were already inside the dining hall. Moreover, the food had been prepared.

Besides Tao Wang and Tie Sheng, Margaret was also inside the dining hall. Naturally, the reason Margaret was here was Zhao Hai.

When he saw Margaret, Desbarres smiled faintly and then turned to Zhao Hai, he said, “Little Hai, go accompany Miss Margaret. Tao Wang, Tie Sheng, you’re with me.” Then the three proceeded to leave the area.

Margaret was somewhat embarrassed. But she still sat on the table with Zhao Hai. When everyone saw Zhao Hai and Margaret together, they didn’t dare barge in.

After sitting down, Margaret turned her head to Zhao hai and said, “Did that person meet you?”

Zhao Hai knew that Margaret was talking about Patriarch Thunder. He nodded and said, “Yes, the Patriarch asked to meet me.”

Margaret turned anxious, she asked, “What did you talk about?”

When he saw Margaret’s tense expression, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile as he gave his answer, “Not really that much. But the Patriarch gave me a task. He wants me to get top ten in the realm qualifiers.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but relax. But she was still unconvinced, “Only that?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, it’s only that. But he said that if I get top ten in the qualifier, he wouldn’t go in between us two.” Zhao Hai’s words made Margaret stare. Then her face turned red as she lowered her head and asked, “Did he really say that?”

Zhao Hai chuckled, “He did, you can ask the Camp Lord.” Margaret just nodded and didn’t make any noise. Zhao Hai looked at Margaret, then he smiled bitterly and said, “Margaret, I need to be honest with you. I have wives that I love in the lower realms. If you like me, then you need to prepare sharing me with them.” Margaret nodded and said, “I understand.” Her voice was very low, but it was firm.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He knew that Margaret was certainly thinking that Laura and the others were left behind in the lower realms. She might be thinking that he meant sharing spiritually. She wouldn’t expect that Zhao Hai actually brought Laura and the others with him!

Chapter 1137: Doing a mission

Three days have passed since the end of the Ashley Family’s qualifiers. At this time, Zhao Hai was already a celebrity in the family. He was called the strongest beginner in the External Hall.

The reason why everyone added ‘beginner’ was because the External Hall’s camps also had old ascenders who were very strong. Everyone thought that it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to defeat them. Therefore, they only gave him the title of strongest beginner.

It was only Desbarres and a few people who understood that not only the entire External Hall, but Zhao Hai would be one of the strongest experts in the Machine Field if he used Liquid Silver.

However, this matter was a secret; nobody would dare reveal it. Also, in the past few days, the Bone Symbol Camp was immersed in an endless mood of festivity. Of course, the most enviable thing in the Bone Symbol Camp was Zhao Hai’s relationship with Margaret. By this point, everyone had regarded Zhao Hai and Margaret to be together. Everyone could see the both of them together almost every day.

The Machine Field’s realm qualifiers would be held in two month’s time. In these two months, the Ashley Family as well as the other families would collect information about the other contestants for the competition.

And in these two months, the family had limited Zhao Hai’s activity. If Zhao Hai wanted to do something, then it needed to be approved by the family. In essence, Zhao Hai’s life had turned back to normal.

Zhao Hai also found the chance to return to the academy to see Dins and the others. Dins and the others were also aware of Zhao Hai’s achievements. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be this strong just a few months after ascending. Their friend’s progress naturally made them very happy.

Dins and the others were also doing very well lately. They already reached a state of being able to outdo others. Moreover, with how Zhao Hai was taking care of them, they had already regarded him as a friend and family member. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s progress made them glad.

After a short reunion with Dins and the others, Zhao Hai returned to the Bone Symbol Camp to resume his training. However, Zhao Hai knew that closing up at this point would be useless. And now that he had become a member of the Bone Symbol Camp, he wanted to do something.

It was impossible for the Bone Symbol Camp to develop if they just relied on money. They still needed to do missions. And through these missions, they would slowly gain reputation. So when a special mission comes up, then someone might come and approach the camp.

After the family’s internal qualifiers, the Bone Symbol Camp experienced a low-point in doing missions. Even Tie Sheng, the person in charge of missions in the Bone Symbol Camp, took a rest.

With the realm qualifiers happening in two months, Zhao Hai didn’t want to spend the entire time practicing. Practicing wasn’t productive to him. What’s productive was doing missions and making contributions to the Bone Symbol Camp.

Because of this, when Zhao Hai returned from the Academy, he immediately went to look for Desbarres. Since Desbarres was the External Hall’s manager and the Bone Symbol Camp’s lord, it was enough for Zhao Hai to approach him.

Seeing Zhao Hai looking for him, Desbarres stared for a moment before he said, “Little Hai, why are you here? Do you need anything?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, I have something to discuss.”

Desbarres frowned, “What is it? I’ll do my best to help you.”

Seeing Desbarres’s reaction, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord, ever since I entered the camp, I have yet to do a mission. I couldn’t justify this. Since the Machine Field qualifiers isn’t happening soon, I’d like to use this opportunity to do a mission.”

When he heard this, Desbarres thought that he misunderstood. He frowned and said, “You want to do a mission? Don’t you have to prepare for getting top ten in the realm qualifiers two months from now?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That isn’t an issue. I’m currently on a bottleneck. Even if I close up, it would be useless. It’s better for me to do missions and experience actual combat. This way, I can also get more familiar with Little Silver.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Desbarres nodded and said, “Alright, I agree. But you need to consult Tie Sheng. The camp’s missions are being managed by him.” Zhao Hai nodded and went to find Tie Sheng.

Tie Sheng’s office was also inside the camp’s headquarters. He was tasked with picking and handing missions to the camp. There were also particularly important missions that needed to be personally managed by him.

Tie Sheng’s missions weren’t too crucial. Generally, he would handle group missions, taken in the name of the Bone Symbol Camp. He wouldn’t participate in missions that were taken in his own name.

At this time, Tie Sheng was processing documents in his office. Then suddenly, the door opened and a person walked in. Tie Sheng looked up and gawked. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to come looking for him.

However, Tie Sheng quickly recovered. He looked at Zhao Hai in confusion and said, “Little Hai, what brings you to my office? You want to drink? Let me finish this first.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Tie Sheng, do I need to ask you for a drink whenever I see you? This time I didn’t come for a drink, I want to ask for a mission.”

Tie Sheng stared, he was puzzled so he asked, “You want a mission? The realm qualifiers is happening soon. It would be better for you to stay in the camp.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Brother Tie Sheng, at this point, practicing is useless for me. Therefore, I want to do missions in order to gain battle experience. This would also allow me to be more familiar with Liquid Silver.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Alright. After all, with Liquid Silver, it wouldn’t be a problem for you to survive in the beginner competition. I can give you a mission. What type of mission do you want?”

Naturally, Tie Sheng’s confidence in Liquid Silver was much greater than his confidence of Zhao Hai. However, he still wasn’t confident in the Machine Field’s performance at the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything about it and just smiled faintly and said, “I haven’t taken any missions before, so I’ll leave the choice to you. A group mission would be good. However, it needs to be a bit difficult. Or else I won’t be able to familiarize myself with Liquid Silver.”

Tie Sheng thought for a moment and said, “A group mission would be good, this way you can have people taking care of you. I’ll see what missions we have available.”

Tie Sheng opened his computer and searched for a while. Then his eyes suddenly shone. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this mission is very suitable for you. You can finally take revenge.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Revenge? Does it involve the Zhang Family?”

Tie Sheng nodded, “Right. It’s an internal mission of the Zhang Family. They need to escort a fleet of ten medium freighters to Luke Planet from their headquarters in Adam Planet. They would send people from their External Hall for this mission. What we need to do is to disguise as pirates to attack their fleet. There’s no other purpose for this mission other than striking the Zhang Family. So are you interested? This will make you go against a battleship. Moreover, it’s a group mission.”

Zhao Hai’s two eyes shone, he said, “Good, I’m interested. Right, who else will take this mission?”

Tie Sheng smiled faintly and said, “I’ll be going. And besides the Bone Symbol Camp, other camps would also send their own people. The commander for this mission is a core member of the family. But the people from the Bone Symbol Camp will act together. Will you join?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Of course I’ll join. I wouldn’t want to miss this opportunity. But if we take a battleship down, how will the accomplishment be handled?”

Tie Sheng looked strangely at Zhao Hai and said, “Good. It seems like you’re prepared to go to extremes. Rest assured, as long as you’re able to take a battleship down, everything left behind will be handed over to the Bone Symbol Camp. You might not know, but modified battleships can fetch a good price. And even if we don’t sell it, we can still make use of it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then it’s settled, I’ll participate. When do we start?”

Tie Sheng smiled faintly and said, “We depart five days later.”

Zhao Hao nodded, “Alright, then I’ll be waiting.” Then he turned around and left.

As soon as he got back to his room, Zhao Hai found that Margaret was already waiting for him. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Margaret stood up and said, “Where did you go? Why didn’t I find you?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I went to see the Camp Lord. Since the qualifiers is still two months away, I decided to do some missions. I just met with Brother Tie Sheng, we’ll be departing five days later.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but say, “What mission is it? And the Camp Lord agreed?” Margaret already knew about Liquid Silver, so after thinking about it for some time, she said, “I’ll take the mission as well.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly said, “Why do you want to take the mission, what if something happens? And even if you want to, the Camp Lord might not agree.”

Margaret snorted and said, “Don’t underestimate me. I’m a level 4 Mage. I’ll go see Uncle right now.” Then she turned around and left. Zhao Hai initially wanted to stop her but he decided to give up.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly before his body flashed into space. Laura and the others immediately welcomed him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, why don’t you find an opportunity to take her to the Space?”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and couldn’t help but force a smile, “Let’s wait. She’s not suitable for the Space right now. Are you getting more anxious than me?”

Laura smiled and said, “We just want to see her reaction upon seeing the Space.” Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he didn’t know how to respond.

Zhao Hai chatted with Laura and the others before going back outside. He knew that Margaret should be coming back by now. And just as Zhao Hai came out, Margaret knocked on his door with a smile on her face. Upon seeing Zhao Hai she said, “I’ll be going with you five days later. It’s time for me to take my revenge.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. From what he saw during the Zhang Family’s attack last time, he knew that Margaret’s experience was still too low. She was dreaming if she really wanted to take revenge against the Zhang family.

However, Zhao Hai wouldn’t tell her this. Instead he smiled and said, “Alright. We only need to follow Brother Tie Sheng’s lead. He’s quite strong and has a lot of experience in command. There shouldn’t be any problems.”

Margaret actually looked both excited and nervous. She was like a child that was waiting to do something evil. With her excited face, Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Hey, what if we take a ship by force? Do we sell it or use it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Relax. These things will be handed over to the camp to manage.” Margaret’s excitement didn’t reduce at all. She kept discussing to Zhao Hai about keeping it.

Five days quickly passed by. This mission was kept in deep secrecy. Only a small number of people in the Ashley Family knew about it. Even those who accepted the mission were still unaware about what they would do.

This time, 200 members from the Bone Symbol Camp joined. The weakest of them was at level 3. After all, those less than level 3 couldn’t survive going in outer space.

Although there were a lot of people from the Bone Symbol Camp, two people became the center of attention. They were Zhao Hai and Margaret.

Margaret’s status in the Ashley Family wasn’t a secret. Additionally, she had been visiting Zhao Hai recently. Because of this, the people from the Bone Symbol Camp knew about her. They just didn’t expect Zhao Hai and Margaret to participate in the mission.

All those who participated in the mission were sent out to outer space by a small spaceship. Then they transferred to a bigger ship before heading to their destination.

Since this mission was kept secret, all camps involved would gather at the outer space base and take a medium-sized battleship.

For this mission, the External Hall dispatched more than 1700 people altogether. With so many people and only one ship, the rooms were very packed. Rooms originally for one person now had six people squeezed inside.

The room that Zhao Hai was in had the same situation, but fortunately he was grouped up with those from the Bone Symbol Camp. As for Margaret, since she had special status, she was allocated a room for herself.

After everyone had arrived at the outer space base, the spaceship immediately took off. Their destination was a place called Rainbow Meteor Field.

Chapter 1138: Ambush

The Rainbow Meteor Field, what a beautiful name! However, just like in the forests, the most beautiful things are the most dangerous. The Rainbow Meteorite Field might be beautiful, but it was extremely lethal towards fleets.

The Rainbow Meteor Field was an extremely huge zone. The countless meteorites here were magnetic and at the same time chaotic. Nobody would survive a journey to the middle of this zone. Even if a powerful Expert goes in alone, he still wouldn’t be able to penetrate the meteor field.

The entire field had a radiance surrounding it. It looks beautiful and dazzling, but all fleets chose to stay away from it.

And don’t think that it was safe to hide inside the meteorite field. In this area, meteorites would occasionally crash against each other and split. Then this would cause a chain reaction where more and more meteorites explode. The irregularity of this event made it dangerous to stay on the edge of the field.

However, this meteorite field was actually in the path between Adam Planet and Luke Planet. It was also impossible for the Zhang Family to go around it. There is only a small opening in the meteorite field that allowed for a fairly safer route. Zhao Hai and the others would stage an ambush in this place.

The Ashley Family’s ship arrived at the area ahead of time. Then Zhao Hai and the others left the ship and went into groups to hide behind meteors. On the other hand, the battleship went to find a proper place to hide.

Because of the magnetic field as well as the energy storms present, most electronic equipment couldn’t be used here. Ships would need to rely on the pilot’s driving experience so that the ship could safely pass through. It can be said that this meteor field was the best place for staging an ambush.

Zhao Hai and the other people from the Bone Symbol Camp hid on a piece of meteorite. This meteorite wasn’t far from the route. It was quite huge, to the point of reaching the size of a planetoid.

After Zhao Hai and the others arrived on the meteorite, they immediately dug open a cavern on it. Then they dug smaller caves inside. It didn’t take long before it turned into a temporary base.

Besides staying in the temporary base, after discussions with Tie Sheng, Zhao Hai also made a small cave on a meteorite behind the base. This would be a key factor in their ambush.

After constructing the temporary base, Tie Sheng would regularly send people to monitor the situation of the passage. This way, they could immediately move once the Zhang Family fleet was discovered.

Although this mission was being headed by a core member of the family, the commander allowed each camp to move independently due to the mission’s nature. Each group leader could make moves on their own discretion.

The Bone Symbol Camo’s leader was Tie Sheng. And since these missions were the type he took more often, he was quite experienced about what to do. Because of this, he was able to command the group better.

However, very few people knew that Zhao Hai was also offering ideas about how to deal with the Zhang Family’s fleet. Although Zhao Hai presented a lot of ideas, he didn’t claim them for his own. Everything was seen as Tie Sheng’s contributions.

Zhao Hai knew that even if he was very famous in the Bone Symbol Camp, this was only because he managed to bring honor to the camp. His reputation was still less than Tie Sheng’s. If people from the Bone Symbol Camp knew that these ideas have been presented by Zhao Hai, then they might not be convinced about their effectiveness.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to step aside and credit his ideas to Tie Sheng. He would just offer ideas while Tie Sheng would make the final decision.

Days flew past as everyone cemented their plans. It was decided that the attack would happen ten days later once the Zhang Family’s fleet enters the passage. The reason for this was because they were afraid that the Zhang Family might have made some preparations.

To be honest, there were a lot of people who felt uncomfortable about this mission. But the Bone Symbol Camp were able to endure since they knew that this was a family mission.

Most people from the Bone Symbol Camp didn’t know about the hidden matter between the Ashley Family and the Zhang Family. What they knew was that the two families were allies. Because of this, they couldn’t understand this action.

But after Tie Sheng told them about the reward for the mission, they easily forgot about these matters. For the External Hall, nothing was better than a solid reward. For them alliances between families were worth a fart. Only solid money can move their hearts.

People from the External Hall were mostly ascenders from the lower realms. They were prideful beings in their respective realms, but after arriving at the Machine Field, they found that their identity changed from a heaven’s son to an inferior being. The natives in the Machine Field looked down on ascenders. Some ascenders found it hard to adapt to this change in status.

Ascenders who had talent were able to slowly adjust their mentality. With their hearts still resolute, with enough effort, they were able to become experts in the realm. However, for most people, this spirit vanished. As they became members of External Halls, their pursuit changed from becoming strong to acquiring machine coins.

It can be said that these people had lost their ideals and were now chasing after money, which was sad.

Ambitious people would set goals, and those with enough talent would become strong. If you only live for money, then your life would be pitiful. However, the majority of people from External Halls were doing this exact same thing, living for the sake of money.

The Chinese used to say that poverty inhibits one’s ambitions. This sentence can also be applied to the people in the Machine Field’s External Halls. Mages and Warriors who didn’t have enough income to support their lifestyle would end up chasing after money.

As the days went past, the Bone Symbol Camp also made exchanges with the other camps. Under the commander’s orders, everyone made attack calculations from time to time.

The Bone Symbol Camp held a key position in this ambush as they would be the first group to launch the attack. However, their position was at the innermost part of the route. As soon as they attack, the other camps would follow after. This was because the Bone Symbol Camp was tasked with attacking the lead battleship of the Zhang Family’s fleet. Doing so would force the other ships to stop.

It can be said that the Bone Symbol Camp’s task was very heavy. Their attack on the lead ship would affect the outcome of the succeeding attacks.

Ten days went by in a flash. The people from the Bone Symbol Camp were tensed. They knew that the fight was coming soon. Sure enough, the Zhang Family didn’t disappoint them. They arrived right on time.

The fleet comprised of ten shps. These ten ships weren’t true battleships. Instead, they were merchant ships that were armed with weapons. They weren’t combat-oriented and mainly served as transport. They were armed with a simple weapons system as well as a limited number of mechs. There were also Mages and Warriors on the ships to serve as guards.

Commanding the Zhang Family’s ship was a man named Adams. He’s a merchant captain with a lot of experience and had already made multiple trips safely through the Rainbow Meteor Field. Because of this history, the Zhang Family felt relieved leaving this matter to him.

Even with his status, Adams was still wary every time he went through the meteorite field. Adams knew clearly that the Rainbow Meteor Field was extremely random. It was a very dangerous zone that could randomly destroy ships.

Once the fleet entered the meteor field, Adams’s relaxed expression turned stern. His two eyes were focused on the path.

This passage wasn’t very long. Spaceships could pass through it in one hour with full speed. However, ships wouldn’t dare traverse this passage in their full speed. This was because meteors would sometimes wander through the passage. If a ship manages to hit these meteorites, then a chain reaction would certainly occur.

Because of this, even if speed was crucial in passing through this region, haste was heavily discouraged. One couldn’t go too fast nor too slow. With his experience, Adams clearly knew how to traverse this passage.

Adams was currently inside the ship right behind the lead ship. If the lead ship met an attack, then he could use the second ship to help.

After eyeing the passage for some time, Adams quickly said, “All ships slow down to twenty knots. Ready your system weapons and keep a steady communication with other ships.”

The order was quickly passed down. Before long, the entire fleet slowed down. Then the lead ship began to enter the passage.

One by one, the fleet entered the meteor field. Adams was anxiously staring at the computer. At this point, the communication was beginning to be affected. Conversations were beginning to crack. However, Adams didn’t panic. This was to be expected judging by the meteorite field’s characteristics.

The fleet slowly advanced. Oftentimes, a ship would shoot some smaller meteorites that were on their way. But generally speaking, they were still safe.

Even if the fleet was halfway through the passage, Adams still didn’t relax. As long as the fleet was still inside the passage, he couldn’t lower his guard.

At this time, Adams’s expression sank, then he yelled out, “Ship number 1, pay attention. Ship number 1, pay attention. Immediately descend, immediately descend!”

Adams’s eyes was stuck on the computer. He could clearly see a meteorite not far away from ship number 1 suddenly moving. Then that meteorite hit a bigger meteorite, causing the latter to move towards the passage!

Chapter 1139: A Bait!

Adams always felt that the huge meteorite was very weird. It was massive, and yet it was able to be moved by a small meteorite. Why was this the case?

Just as Adams was puzzled, the back of the huge meteorite suddenly lit up like a rocket as it sped up and quickly hit the lead ship.

When he saw this, alarms began blaring up inside Adams’s head. He suddenly thought of something as he ran to a table and looked at the red displays. At the same time, he yelled, “Enemy ambush! All personnel prepare for battle!”

As Adams shouted, the lead ship already shot at the huge meteorite. However, the meteorite was just too big. Although the energy beams hit the meteorite, the only thing it did was bore two holes on its surface. There was no change to the meteorite’s trajectory.

The meteorite continued on before directly hitting the lead ship. Moreover, the meteorite hit the ship’s bow. As soon as he saw this happen, Adams knew that the ship was finished.

Whether it be combat ships or commercial ships, their command room was placed at the same location, the front of the ship. This wasn’t only for looks. Installed in each command room were tempered glass windows that allowed firsthand vision towards the outside of the ship. This was very beneficial to maneuvering.

But now that it was hit by a meteorite, this design became the ship’s most fatal point. Although tempered glass was made with resilience in mind, it still couldn’t block against a direct strike of a meteorite.

Generally, ship commanders would erect a metal plate outside the glass. However, this was only done during battles. In any other situation, the metal plate was hidden from sight.

It was obvious that the lead ship’s commander didn’t expect an assault. Because of this, he failed to put up the metal barrier beforehand. Once the meteorite hit the tempered glass, the ship was finished.

And just like what Adams thought, when the meteorite hit the tempered glass, it shattered instantaneously. And then the meteorite changed direction and flew to the opposite side.

And then from the meteorite, a large quantity of human shadows came out and flew towards the ship. But Adams didn’t have the mood to ask who those people were. He just immediately said, “Erect the metal barriers. Mechs, Mages, Warriors, prepare to attack. Prime the weapon systems. Reduce speed to ten knots. Move slowly forward and attempt to push ship number 1 away. We’re making an avenue for escape.” The people in the ship immediately got busy. All of them saw the figures coming out of the meteorite. It was clear that they were being ambushed.

At this time, a large number of Mages and Warriors rushed out from both sides of the fleet. A lot of these people also used meteorites to approach the ships. However, these meteorites weren’t as big as the one used by the Bone Symbol Camp. In the end, these meteorites were destroyed by the ship’s weapons. There were even people who died from the attacks.

Meanwhile, after Zhao Hai and the others broke through ship number 1’s tempered glass, they quickly boarded the ship. The command room had been completely abandoned. The instruments inside were on fire, rendering them useless. All of the staff in the command room were dead, their corpses littered across the room.

Tie Sheng looked all around and said, “Little Hai, you lead the way. Break through the cabin doors. Be sure to leave no survivors behind. We need to quickly eliminate everyone.”

Zhao Hao nodded before flying towards the room’s door. Then a 5-layer formation appeared, banging through the door. It didn’t take long before the door got crushed. Then Zhao Hai led the people forward through the destroyed cabin door.

As Zhao Hai flew into the ship, he also used his spiritual force to scan the surrounding area. He was paying full attention to any enemies.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai felt two people in a cabin in front of him. It was two warriors, they already had their weapons out as they nervously stared at the door.

Zhao Hai waved his hand to stop the people behind him. These people have witnessed Zhao Hai’s strength, so they couldn’t help but look at what’s in front.

Zhao Hai turned to look at the others, then he gestured towards the door and said, “There are two people in the cabin up front, two Warriors. Once I open the door, immediately attack.” Everyone nodded. Then Zhao Hai floated towards the cabin door. He waved his hand, making a 10-layer formation appear. When the cabin door was destroyed, the two Warriors inside couldn’t help but let out a strange cry. As they were blocking against the broken shrapnels, one of them yelled, “Surrender, we surrender!” However, the people from the Bone Symbol Camp weren’t polite. It didn’t matter if they surrendered or not, the two Warriors were quickly eliminated.

The people from the Bone Symbol Camp knew that they couldn’t leave any survivors due to the nature of their mission. Otherwise, the people from the Zhang Family would know who was behind the attack.

After the two Warriors were eliminated, Zhao Hai didn’t care about them anymore. He flew forward and swept cabin after cabin. Mages and Warriors who weren’t able to leave were immediately killed by Zhao Hai inside their rooms. Then Zhao Hai took them into the Space to be turned into Undead.

This merchant ship wasn’t small, so there were quite a lot of cabins inside it. Under Zhao Hai’s lead, they were able to clean the entire spaceship. Besides a little trouble in the room for mechs, the entire operation went with almost no resistance.

Before long, the entire spaceship went into their control. Then Zhao Hai and the others returned to the command room. Upon arriving at the room, Zhao Hai saw that the metal barriers of the ship had been forcefully taken out. Even if it was deformed, the Mages and Warriors could still make use of it.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s group, Tie Sheng looked at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s done. Brother Tie Sheng, do we leave and help the others?”

Tie Sheng shook his head and said, “There’s no use. Besides this ship, all others were prepared for the attack. The commander of this fleet is experienced. He used his own ship to push our ship away and then open a passage for escape.’

When he heard Tie Sheng, Zhao Hai nodded. But then he couldn’t bear but ask, “So what do we do now? Do we stay here?” Tie Sheng shook his head and said, “We’re leaving. Since the ship’s engine had stopped working, we’ll go behind and push it using magic. We need to leave this place as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then let’s go now.” After he said that, Zhao Hai led a group of Mages outside. When Tie Sheng saw that Margaret was about to leave, he quickly said, “Miss Margaret, you need to stay here. Since the battle is over, there shouldn’t be any danger outside. Let Zhao Hai handle this.” Margaret thought about it and decided to remain. She knew about the difference between her and Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was merciless when the situation calls for it. And if any danger emerges, he could deal with it in less than ten minutes.

Zhao Hai led the Mages of the Bone Symbol Camp to the stern of the ship. All of them were wearing specially-made masks to hide their appearance from others.

When everyone got out of the ship, they saw that the ship was already pushed to the side of the passage. There were also a lot of mech fragments and dead bodies floating in space. Meanwhile the fleet had already disappeared.

By this time, there were a lot of Mages and Warriors around the ship. Naturally, these people were from the other camps.

Zhao Hai glanced at these people and whispered, “Everyone, let’s get this ship out quick. We need to avoid any attacks as soon as possible.”

The Mages and Warriors who surrounded the ship didn’t have any identity on them. They were also wearing masks. As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, these people couldn’t help but hesitate. This mission was a joint task between multiple camps. Normally, they would compete with each other and made sure that the Bone Symbol Camp gets the least benefit. However, a core member of the family was overseeing this operation. If they were caught causing problems, then their camps would be punished.

Seeing the Mages hesitate, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Everyone, let’s move the ship so we don’t have to deal with any counter-attacks.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, those present couldn’t help but stare. In this situation, most people would keep everything for themselves. People like Zhao Hai who allowed sharing the merit were too rare.

Not only the other camps, even those from the Bone Symbol Camp were shocked. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to ask others for help. Does he want to share the reward with the others?

Just as everyone was about to move, Zhao Hai’s expression suddenly changed. Then his figure flashed and appeared inside the command room. Tie Sheng was currently busy commanding everyone to make repairs. When he saw Zhao Hai appear, Tie Sheng couldn’t help but stare. Then he immediately asked, “What happened? Are the other camps making trouble?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, we need to leave immediately. Both sides of the passage have been blocked by warships. It seems like the Zhang Family is already aware of this mission. They allowed the fleet to come here so that we could attack it. This way, they could find a reason to openly declare war on the family. They’ve already began sending people in. We don’t have enough time.” When he heard this, Tie Sheng’s expression changed, he said, “Are you sure?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’m sure. And we’re going to be surrounded in about 20 minutes!”

Chapter 1140: Withdrawing from the Meteorite Field

When Tie Sheng heard Zhao Hai, he immediately shouted, “Everyone gather around. We need to escape, leave everything behind!”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but insert himself upon hearing Tie Sheng, “Brother Tie Sheng, there are a lot of good things in this ship including metals and some special products. How about I open the doors and we store those items in our spatial items. After that, we can leave this place and attempt to break through.”

Tie Shen stared, then he shook his head and said, “We can’t do that. We don’t have enough time.” But this time, Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, don’t forget that we’re here as pirates. So we need to steal some things before entering the meteorite field. Even if we can’t return to the family’s ship in a short time, we can still be safe. After all, they cannot chase us deep into the meteorite field.”

Tie Sheng thought about it for a moment before he said, “It’s too risky. But we can’t leave empty-handed. Alright, I’ll go organize a group.” Zhao Hai nodded before he turned and left the room. Margaret quickly followed behind him.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything upon seeing Margaret following behind. The group quickly flew throughout the ship, ransacking every room they could find.

And upon opening these cabins, Zhao Hai discovered that the ship contained more things than he imagined. There were some metal bars inside as well as specialties from Adam Planet. Most importantly, it had a stock of the latest models of cars and mechs.

However, these weren’t Zhao Hai’s priority right now. After opening the doors, Zhao Hai pulled Margaret over and entered another room. Then Zhao Hai didn’t waste any time as he stored everything inside that room into the Space.

Margaret thought that Zhao Hai would take precious items. However, upon seeing Zhao Hai’s actions, she found out that she was wrong. Zhao Hai didn’t take precious items. Instead, he took all the food and water inside the ship. He also took the wine and other daily necessities.

After taking those things, only then did Zhao Hai and Margaret leave. Zhao Hai didn’t take the metals and mechs. He didn’t want to let others know that he had a lot of storage capacity inside his Space. Naturally, he took these things in preparation for later on. Since they had been surrounded, Zhao Hai knew that they wouldn’t be able to escape the meteorite field in a short time. He didn’t know how long it would take before they could return back to the family. In this case, they needed to stock up on food and drinks. Although the Space could provide food, Zhao Hai didn’t want to raise any suspicion. Now that he showed that he took food from the ship, nobody would suspect him.

When Zhao Hai and Margaret returned, Tie Sheng and the others already ransacked the surrounding cabins. Seeing that everyone was here, Zhao Hai turned to Tie Sheng and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, let’s go. We don’t have much time left.” Tie Sheng nodded. Then he waved his hand, commanding everyone to leave the ship. Then he greeted the other camps before he retreated into the meteorite zone.

While Zhao Hai and the others were ransacking the ship, Tie Sheng already informed the other camps about the situation. The other camp commanders were also aware that if they don’t quickly escape to the meteorite zone, they would not be able to escape. Therefore, everyone followed Tie Sheng.

Not long after everyone entered entered the meteorite zone, about twenty thousand people comprised of Mages, Warriors, and Mechs arrived at the now empty ship.

There were two teams sent by the Zhang Family. The leaders of these teams were a Mage and a Warrior. While looking at the ship, the Mage opened his mouth and said, “It seems like they discovered us ahead of time.”

The Warrior nodded and said, “Those fellows are truly sly. Since this is the case, make the mechs retreat first. Then we go and take a look at the nearby meteorites. They certainly haven’t gone far.” The Mage was in agreement, he said, “Right, with our fleets outside, they would certainly be courting death if they decide to leave the passage. Let’s go into the direction the ship has floated to, then we’ll slowly branch out.”

The Warrior nodded. Then they walked towards the mechs and had them retreat. It can be said that mechs had much greater combat power than Mages and Warriors. However, their ability to stay in combat wasn’t very good. Even if they can fight for two days straight, once their energy reserves were used up, they were no greater than scrap iron. And if there were any high-intensity fights, their operating time would be reduced further. This task couldn’t be completed within a day or two. Because of this, it was best if the mechs retreat and save their energy.

Due to the nature of the area, most communication devices were rendered useless. Because of this, communication became a major problem. Otherwise, Zhao Hai and the others would’ve already informed the Ashley Family’s ship to run on its own.

As soon as Zhao Hai and the others entered the meteorite field, they immediately went further inside. However, they didn’t go too deep into the zone. Even almighty Experts from the Cultivation Realm wouldn’t dare enter that area.

After Zhao Hai’s group entered the field, they immediately turned towards the family ship. The ship had yet to leave the meteorite field but instead found a place to hide in. Zhao Hai and the others wanted to know how the ship was currently doing.

Tie Sheng and Zhao Hai took the lead. After flying for a while, Tie Sheng turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I’m almost certain that a spy has infiltrated the family. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have known about this mission.”

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “Not only an ordinary spy, but someone who managed to penetrate deep. It seems like the Zhang Family really had no consideration for the family’s face. This is a dangerous time for the Ashley Family.”

Tie Sheng knit his brows. This mission was considered top secret within the family. Even people from the Bone Symbol Camp didn’t know about its contents up until the operation began.

Only the high-level members of the family knew about the time and scale of the mission. And even in such a case, the Zhang Family was still able to lay down a trap.

Also, the Ashley Family wasn’t aiming to wage war with the Zhang Family with this retaliation. They just want to teach a lesson to the other side. But judging by the current situation, it seems like the Zhang Family was prepared for war.

One side was deliberately planning while the other had no preparations whatsoever. In this case, if war happened between the two families, then the Ashley Family would certainly suffer a loss.

Tie Sheng sighed and said, “Alright, even if something is happening to the family, we cannot do anything about it at this time. What we need to do is protect our lives. Let’s hope that nothing happened to the ship, or else our lives wouldn’t be good.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to look at the others before saying, “Brother Tie Sheng, it would be best if you organize a group to clear out our traces. Otherwise, the enemies would quickly find us and give chase. I’ll head out front first and explore the area.”

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “I’ll choose two people to go with you. It’s better for your safety.” Zhao Hai didn’t object. Then Tie Sheng chose two people to go with Zhao Hai before he stayed behind.

Tie Sheng’s status was quite substantial among the External Hall’s camps. And with his position as the commander of the Bone Symbol Camp, the other camps began unconsciously to listen to his words.

Tie Sheng looked at everyone and said, “This time, we’ve been snared in the enemy’s trap. Also, the outside passage has been blocked. Some of you might have already known this, but we might have to stay away from the family for a long time. We have people currently chasing behind us, so I ask each camp commander to work together and clean all of our traces. We cannot be discovered. This isn’t the time to act on our own. If we are separated, then we’ll all be captured.” Nobody objected. They knew that what Tie Sheng said was correct. If they don’t work together, then they would have no chance to fight back against the Zhang Family.

Seeing everyone agree, Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Then I ask every commander for a meeting. We need to discuss our further actions.” After he said that, every commander went forward for the meeting.

Tie Sheng looked at the commanders and said, “The core member of the family is currently in the ship. I’m afraid we’ll have to temporarily take responsibility for everyone. We’ve brought our elites to this mission, so if we all perish here, then the External Hall will be finished. What we need to do now is to survive. I’ve already sent people ahead to scout and look for the ship. If the ship is fine, then we can tell them about what happened. But if there’s something wrong with the ship, then I’m afraid we’ll have to stay inside this meteorite field for a while.”

The camp commanders nodded. Just after the battle ended, the core member of the family returned to the ship along with some Mages and Warriors. Therefore, they weren’t here now. Because of this, the people in charge could only be the commanders from the eight camps.

Seeing everyone nod, Tie Sheng said, “I suggest that we send people out to scout the nearby area and clean up any traces we might have left behind. After the person I’ve sent forward comes back, we’ll discuss what to do once more.”

Everyone nodded, then a Mage asked, “Tie Sheng, who did you send ahead? Is he good?”

Tie Sheng looked at the Mage and identified him as the Ghost Symbol Camp’s commander. He’s also the person responsible for their camp’s missions, Charles.

Tie Sheng looked at Charles and said, “Of course. Zhao Hai personally went out. If he can’t do it, then I’m afraid nobody else can.”

When he heard Tie Sheng’s answer, Charles couldn’t help but stare. Then he nodded and said, “Right, if it’s Zhao Hai, then he could certainly do it.”

Tie Sheng agreed. Then he said, “Alright, then everyone, let’s begin. Pay attention to the direction we came from. There may be troops chasing us. And make sure that no camp is left alone.”

As soon as they heard Tie Sheng, the commanders couldn’t help but stare. Charles looked at Tie Sheng and said, “No camp is left alone? What do you mean?”

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “It’s possible that someone from the Zhang Family is with us. Therefore, it would be best if no camp goes on their own. Otherwise, the spy might use this opportunity to send word back to the Zhang Family.”

The commander of the Upright Symbol Camp, Leo, looked at Tie Sheng and said, “Impossible. You’re being unfair. My men will never betray the family.”

Tie Sheng turned his head to Leo and said, “Don’t talk about fairness. This mission is a family secret. However, it was still known by the Zhang Family, they even set up a trap. This only means that there are traitors among is. And how can you guarantee that your people are completely loyal?”

Leo couldn’t answer. Charles nodded and said, “Tie Sheng is correct. Let’s organize 50-people teams and disperse out. Nobody is permitted to be left alone.” Everyone nodded.

While the camps were getting people ready, Zhao Hai continued flying forward. Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was suppressed in outer space. Because of this, he only discovered the Zhang Family’s fleet when they surrounded the passage.

Nevertheless, Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was still the most powerful in the Ashley Family’s External Hall. This was also a reason why he volunteered to investigate.

Following behind Zhao Hai were senior members of the Bone Symbol Camp. In the beginning, they weren’t convinced of Zhao Hai. But after seeing Zhao Hai’s strength, they couldn’t help but get surprised. The power that pushed the meteorite towards the ship belonged to Zhao Hai. Additionally, Zhao Hai’s early detection of the enemy ships saved them.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly stopped. Then he waved his hand, stopping those who were following him. One of them went to Zhao Hai’s side and asked, “Little Hai, what’s wrong?”

Zhao Hai turned to the man. He identified this person was one of Tie Sheng’s aides. He also had some reputation in the family. He’s a level 5 Warrior who had two blades as his weapons. His name was Richard.

Zhao Hai replied, “Brother Richard, it’s no use. Let’s head back. The ship has been occupied by the Zhang Family. If we go back, then we’ll be ambushed.”

Richard stared, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How did you find out?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “My spiritual force is not a joke. Although the ship is quite a distance away, I could still see its current situation. Let’s head back to report to Brother Tie Sheng. We’ll have to make another plan.”

Richard didn’t doubt Zhao Hai. He just whispered and said, “Is the core member of the family fine? If anything happens to him, then we’ll be in trouble.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Let’s go back.” After turning around, Zhao Hai flew back the way they came.

Chapter 1141: Intelligent Spy

Zhao Hai slowly led everyone back to the main army. They couldn’t fly too fast since dangers were ever present in the meteorite field. It was very likely that they couldn’t avoid pieces of meteorites if they went too fast. In this field, a shard of meteor was more lethal than a bullet.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s group noticed a group of 50 scouting in all directions. Zhao Hai knew that these people were from the Ashley Family, so he wasn’t startled at the sight of them. He immediately led his group towards them.

The group also noticed Zhao Hai’s team. But since the other party was wearing similar masks, they knew that they were in the same team.

Zhao Hai nodded to them and said, “This one is Bone Symbol Camp’s Zhao Hai. May I ask where Commander Tie Sheng is?” It was clear that the opposite party wasn’t from the Bone Symbol Camp. Upon hearing that it was Zhao Hai, they curiously sized him up. Zhao Hai was currently famous in the Ashley Family’s External Hall.

The man in front of Zhao Hai pointed behind him and said, “The commanders are currently inside the base. They’re waiting for you.” Zhao Hai nodded and expressed his thanks. Then he lead his team towards the direction the man pointed.

Before long, Zhao Hai felt Tie Sheng and the others’s presence. Zhao Hai quickly flew over and then bowed and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, I’m back. I have also seen the commanders.”

Naturally, the other commanders knew about Zhao Hai. They looked at him curiously. But since Zhao Hai was wearing a mask, they couldn’t see much.

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “How is it? Did you find the ship?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I found it. However, the situation isn’t very good. The ship has already fallen under the Zhang Family’s control. Moreover, they’ve set up a trap to ensnare us there.” Tie Sheng and the others’s faces turned ugly. This was the worst result, this was the last thing they wanted to hear. However, those present here were mentally strong, so they immediately roused their spirits. Tie Sheng said, “It seems like we can’t count on it anymore. Right, is the core family member inside the ship?”

Zhao Hai replied, “That person is alright. However, he’s already in the Zhang Family’s control. It’s possible that they’re just waiting to capture us. Then they’ll use us as evidence to make war against the family.”

Tie Sheng nodded, “If they can’t catch us, then there won’t be sufficient evidence. Therefore, we cannot get caught. Everyone, what do we do now?” The commanders looked at each other, they didn’t know what to do. Tie Sheng turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do you have any ideas?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment, then he said, “I think we should stay here for now. The Zhang Family had sent out a large army in order to catch us. Even if we managed to escape the meteorite field, we would still be overtaken if we don’t have a ship. If we stay here, then the Zhang Family wouldn’t be able to send their ships in. Even if they have Warriors and Mages, or even mechs, we still don’t need to be afraid since this zone is simply too big. It would be impossible for them to do a comprehensive search of this place. Moreover, the meteors could become our natural shields. Although the Zhang Family has great strength, they still wouldn’t be able to surround us. And they couldn’t afford to stay here for long either. Therefore, as long as we stay here, we could go home once the Zhang Family retreats.”

Tie Sheng turned to the others and said, “What do you think?”

Charles nodded and said, “I agree with Zhao Hai. If we leave the meteorite field now, then we’ll just be feeding ourselves to the tiger’s mouth. It’s best if we endure here.”

At this time, Leo opened his mouth and said, “That might be easy to say, but haven’t you noticed a problem? We didn’t take a lot of food with us. And after the last ten days of waiting, we’ve already consumed a lot of our stock. If we don’t escape this time, the Zhang Family could just starve us here.”

Upon hearing this, Charles and Tie Sheng were immediately reminded of this problem. Although their cultivation levels weren’t low, they still need to eat in order to maintain their energy levels. Most of their food stocks were inside the ship. And the supply they brought with them during the ambush wasn’t much. If they don’t solve the food problem, they will definitely starve.

If they don’t want to die of hunger, then their only choice was to exit the meteorite field. But if they go out, they would get captured by the Zhang Family. All of a sudden, Tie Sheng and the others were caught in a dilemma.

Margaret, who was beside Tie Sheng, didn’t speak this entire time. But when she heard Leo, her eyes turned towards Zhao Hai. She couldn’t help but admire Zhao Hai. While others were searching for valuable things inside the ship, Zhao Hai was scraping up all of the food. And now, food became the most valuable commodity.

When he saw Margaret looking at him, Zhao Hai immediately understood what she was thinking about. He smiled faintly and nodded. Then Margaret turned to Tie Sheng and the others and said, “Big Brother Tie Sheng, there’s no need to worry about food.” Tie Sheng and the others stared. Then then turned to look at Margaret. They didn’t know what she was talking about. Margaret smiled and said, “Before we left the ship, Brother Hai took all of the ship’s rations. It should be enough for us to last for some time.”

Tie Sheng and the others stared for a moment before their faces turned happy. Tie Sheng looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, is this true?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ve taken all of the food inside the ship. It should be enough for us to last a long time. Moreover, I brought a lot of food before we left the family. Rest assured, even if we stayed here for several months, we still have enough to eat.”

Tie Sheng laughed and said, “Good, then our biggest problem is solved. Right, Little Hai, why did you bring so much food before leaving the family?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “It’s because of my experience in the lower realms. I was chased down and could only hide. And because I didn’t have enough food to eat, I wasn’t able to fight properly. Therefore, no matter where I go, I will always bring a lot of food. Just in case I need it.”

When they heard this, Tie Sheng and the others laughed. They were relieved. As long as they have food, then there’s no problem staying in this meteorite belt.

At this time, an explosion suddenly happened in the distance. Everyone’s expression changed. This might mean that the scouts had discovered the enemy and were currently in combat.

Tie Sheng looked at the commanders and said, “Immediately recall all the other scouts. Little Hai, I’ll have to trouble you to take a look at the situation. Zhao Hai complied and then turned around and left. Richard and the others were still following behind him.

When Zhao Hai left, Charles turned to look at Tie Sheng and said, “You made Zhao Hai go? He’s a treasure of the Bone Symbol Camp. Aren’t you afraid that he’ll suffer an accident?”

Tie Sheng forced a smile and said, “I wanted to send other people, but nobody has stronger spiritual force than Little Hai. He can get there without being discovered. In our current situation, he’s the only one I can trust to go.”

Charles smiled bitterly. They’ve just began understanding Zhao Hai’s strength. Although some people in the family think that Zhao Hai was still far from being considered an expert in the External Hall, those present here knew that his strength wasn’t simple. The commanders began thinking that they might even fall behind.

Zhao Hai led Richard and the others towards the explosion. Before long, Zhao Hai discovered the scene. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that there weren’t any enemies at all. Instead, the explosion was caused by a fight between two groups from the Ashley Family’s scouts. They were divided into two, killing each other.

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows. Then he sped up towards the fight. When he arrived at the scene, he immediately shouted, “Stop!”

When the two sides saw someone coming, one of them smiled while the other’s expression changed. One group had 15 while the other had 35.

Someone from the outnumbered side quickly said, “Brothers, quick, these people are Zhang Family spies. They want to kill us before going to the Zhang Family.”

“Nonsense!” A person from the other side shouted, then he said, “Brother, don’t listen to his nonsense. They’re the ones from the Zhang Family. We caught them trying to catch the Zhang Family’s attention. If brother doesn’t want to help the Zhang Family, then please help us deal with them.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. It’s possible that one of them was telling the truth, but this wasn’t the time to fight. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “I don’t care who is from the Zhang Family. You need to stop. Otherwise, you can’t blame me for being impolite.” However, the two sides didn’t stop. They kept attacking each other.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Then forgive me for not giving you face.” He waved his hand, making a 100-layer formation appear. Then he declared, “Darkness, capture!!”

Along with Zhao Hai’s voice, the 100-layer formation changed into multitudes of long ropes. Then the ropes caught the two groups. No matter how much they struggled, nobody was able to break away.

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Now, follow me. I’ll take you to see the commanders. If you still struggle, then it means that you’re from the Zhang Family.”

Zhao Hai’s words were very effective. In no time, the captured stopped struggling. Zhao Hai looked at them and coldly smiled. Some of these people are truly sly. They want to disturb the water. But this time, they were mistaken.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Richard and said, “Let’s go back to see Brother Tie Sheng.” Richard nodded. Then he looked at the people captured by Zhao Hai in a cold gaze.

Chapter 1142: Point To Me Your Allies

Richard was very clear about their current situation. And now, these two groups were making such a huge fuss. This could allow the Zhang Family to find them. And once they were located, they’re finished.

Therefore, Richard wished that he could kill these fellows. However, he knew that this wasn’t the time to do that. Catching these people and seeing if they had accomplices was the most important thing right now.

Zhao Hai and his group quickly returned to where Tie Sheng and the others were. At this point, all of the scouts had returned. All of them were nervously looking at the commanders.

Zhao Hai quickly went to Tie Sheng’s side and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, the problem lies with these fellows. They divided into two groups and declared that the other party are the Zhang Family spies. Since I don’t want to attract the Zhang Family, I decided to capture them all.”

As soon as Tie Sheng and the others heard this, they couldn’t help but stare. Several commanders looked at these people with cold gazes. They looked like they were prepared to eat these people up.

Seeing the current situation, Zhao Hai turned to Tie Sheng and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, they made quite a noise when they fought. I think the Zhang Family might have heard it. We should escape in the meantime. Let’s deal with them once we arrive at a safe place.”

Tie Sheng nodded, then he turned to the other commanders and said, “Just like Little Hai said, they’ve made quite a lot of noise. We need to leave this area. Only when we’re safe can we deal with these fellows. The Bone Symbol Camp shall take the lead and the last group shall take the responsibility of clearing our traces.”

This time, they didn’t move in their original direction. Since they would stay inside the meteorite field for some time, then they decided to take more risks and go deeper into the meteorite field. The more secure their location, the safer they would be.

Not even an hour after Tie Sheng and the others left, the Zhang Family’s pursuing troops arrived at the location. Seeing the scene of battle, the Mage said, “It seems like they wanted to return to their ship. But why did a fight happen here?” The Warrior smiled faintly and said, “Don’t forget, we have quite a lot of spies inside the Ashley Family. This scene should be caused by our spies.”

The Mage nodded, “That’s possible. But in this case, the spies that caused trouble had lost their value.”

The Warrior shook his head and said, “As long as we manage to capture the Ashley Family, then those people had shown their worth. The family wouldn’t just use this matter to wage war against the Ashley Family, it is also a good opportunity to get rid of their little genius.” The Mage stared, then he said, “You mean Zhao Hai? He’s here?”

The Warrior nodded and said, “Right, Zhao Hai took the mission. I had the chance to read the family’s recent reports. Only four months after he ascended, Zhao Hai was already able to become an unprecedented champion in the Ashley Family’s internal qualifiers. If he gets to join the realm qualifiers and gain good accomplishments, then it would be very disadvantageous for us. Therefore, he needs to be destroyed.”

The Mage nodded, “That would be the best outcome. Then let’s go.” The Warrior nodded. Then they led their army of 5000 Mage and Warriors towards the Ashley Family’s ship.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others were already deep into the meteorite zone. But before heading this direction, they took a few circles and then went back to the area where they fought with the Zhang Family fleet. Then they proceeded to go deeper into the zone.

The group settled inside a huge meteorite to take a temporary rest. Mages opened a cave inside the meteorite using magic. After everyone entered, they began to relax. At this time, Tie Sheng and the others convened once more to deal with the scout troop that caused trouble.

Tie Sheng and the others were coldly looking at the troublemakers. They lost a few people along the way because they had been forced to evacuate.

These people were tied by Zhao Hai’s magic, so they were still unable to move. Tie Sheng looked at them and said, “So who wants to speak first.”

A Mage from one side immediately said, “Commander Tie Sheng, let me speak first. We’re just doing our scouting tasks. But then we’re suddenly attacked by them. If it weren’t for this, then we wouldn’t have fought back.”

“Nonsense!” A Mage from the other side shouted. “It’s clear that you’re the ones who attacked first. You actually dared to blame us.”

Tie Sheng looked at the two sides, then he said, “Remove their masks. I want to see if they are indeed members of our army.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he waved his hand, removing the masks on the scouts. When the masks were removed, the commanders of the Ghost Symbol Camp and the Upright Symbol Camp couldn’t help coldly snort. This was because these 50 people were comprised of people from both camps. Moreover, each side had members from both camps.

The expressions of the two commanders weren’t attractive to look at. This means that no matter which side has the spy, their camps would still be related to them.

Tie Sheng looked at Charles and Leo and said, “How do you want to deal with this?”

Leo coldly snorted and said, “In my opinion, all of them should be killed.” When he said this, both sides began shouting and blaming the other side.

Charles looked at them and said, “I’ll have them killed as well. However, they need to go through my method first. I want to see if they have something to spill.”

Tie Sheng looked at the two. Then he knit his brows and said, “Charles, are you confident?”

Charles snorted and said, “You should already know about my methods. Under my technique, they wouldn’t be able to tell a lie.”

Tie Sheng and the others didn’t say anything. Charles was telling the truth. His savagery was quite famous in the Ashley Family’s External Hall. This fellow could use all kinds of torture to affect the enemy’s mind. Therefore, he was best at interrogation. Those who had been sentenced by him were all dead.

At this time, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “I also heard about Commander Charles’s methods. However, these people are sent by the Zhang Family. And since they decided to turn violent, it seems like they have already been psychologically altered. I’m afraid that even if you torture them, they would still talk nonsense. I have a way to solve this. I don’t know if you would accept?”

With the strength Zhao Hai showed along the way, the various commanders have already treated him as an equal. So when they heard him, they nodded. Then Tie Sheng said, “Tell us your method.”

Zhao Hai looked at the commanders, then he smiled faintly and said, “As you already know, even if I can use all the elements, I’m mainly a Dark Mage in the lower realms. I can turn people into Undead and make them confess everything they know. Moreover, the Undead couldn’t lie. Even if I commanded them to kill their wife and children, they wouldn’t hesitate to do so. So having them confess their allies wouldn’t be difficult. As long as we choose one person from the two sides and then turn them into Undead, everything will become clear!”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Tie Sheng and the others couldn’t help but be surprised. Their impression of Zhao Hai was of a temperate and calm person. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have a method much worse than Charles’s. In their minds, turning a living person directly into an Undead was truly evil.

Not to say the commanders, those present in the cave couldn’t help but feel a chill when they heard Zhao Hai’s words. It was at this point that they discovered that Zhao Hai wasn’t someone they should annoy.

As for the troublemakers below, their expressions turned for the worse. When they heard that Zhao Hai was going to pick one person from each side, they began praying that they weren’t the ones to be picked.

Similarly, Margaret was shocked at Zhao Hai. However, after she thought about Zhao Hai’s accomplishments in the lower realms, she couldn’t help but nod.

In the Machine Field, killing people wasn’t a major matter. All those who wanted to be strong would need to walk through a pile of corpses.

Tie Sheng took a deep breath to calm down his mood. Then he turned to the others and said, “What do you think?”

The others nodded. Then Tie Sheng looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you can proceed.” Zhao Hai nodded before turning his head towards the two groups. As Zhao Hai swept his gaze towards these people, they couldn’t help but feel like a pig for slaughter.

At this time, someone from the team with 15 people suddenly said, “Don’t kill me. Please. I’ll talk. As long as you keep me alive, I’ll tell you everything I know.”

Upon hearing these words, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh and said, “There’s no use bargaining with me. It’s no longer possible for you to preserve your life. I won’t believe a single word you say.” Then he waved his hand, wrapping that person in a dark mist. The man screamed for some time before his aura vanished.

Once the dark mist disappeared, a pale white skeleton began to stand up from the ground. Naturally, this was an Undead. All those present couldn’t help but feel their backs turn cold. The scream was still echoing inside their heads.

Zhao Hai looked at the skeleton and said, “Point out your allies.” The skeleton proceeded to point towards the side with fewer numbers. But then he also pointed towards the side with the greater number.

Seeing this result, Tie Sheng and the others couldn’t help but gawk!

Chapter 1143: Returning to Dark Demon Planet

Among the people the skeleton pointed to was the Mage who was the most vocal towards the other side. Seeing this situation, Tie Sheng and the others couldn’t help but stare.

Immediately after that, Leo angrily cursed, “Good, good. You snakes. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then we would’ve been caught. Now die!” Then he waved his hand, sending a sword qi towards the Mage that was pointed out.

Tie Sheng and the others didn’t stop him. They also wanted to kill these people off. It was obvious that these people wanted to use the confusion to attract the Zhang Family. But it has to be said, this method was really effective and it almost succeeded.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, placing those pointed out by the skeleton on one side. As for the innocent, he let them go.

After completing this action, Zhao Hai turned to Tie Sheng and the others and said, “Brother Tie Sheng. How about we turn these people into Undead? Then we’ll let them identify their other allies inside the other camps.”

Tie Sheng looked at the other commanders and said, “What do you think? If you agree, then we’ll let Little Hai continue. The earlier we get rid of the snakes, the safer we will be.”

When he heard this, Charles’s expression sank, then he said, “I agree. If we don’t deal with this matter, then we’ll continue being in danger.” The other commanders agreed as well. Zhao Hai nodded and immediately released his dark mist to surround the identified spies.

But all of a sudden, Zhao Hai waved his hand and released a whip to bind someone from the crowd.

Tie Sheng and the others stared. When they were able to see what was in the person’s hand, they were shocked. The person actually had a miniature nuclear bomb!

Now that the person was unable to move, ZHao Hai took the miniature nuclear bomb from his hand. After taking a look at the bomb, Zhao Hai handed it over to Tie Sheng. Then he turned his head to everyone and said, “I advise you all to be honest. If you’re not from the Zhang family, then there’s no need to worry. If you’re from the Zhang Family, then I’ll let you live if you confess. After all, we still need some proof that there are spies from the Zhang Family. If you don’t confess now and the Undead points you out, then I’ll have to apologize, you will be killed.”

Tie Sheng couldn’t help but wipe a cold sweat after storing the miniature nuclear bomb inside his spatial item. Then he nodded and said, “Right, if you confess now, we’ll let you keep your life!”

The crowd began to move, then several people stood up and bowed. Then they said, “I hope Tie Sheng and Zhao Hai could keep their word.”

Zhao Hao looked at them and said, “Of course we’ll keep our word. However, I need to suppress you.” He waved his hand, restraining those who surrendered early. Although these people could still move, they could no longer use spiritual qi.

After Zhao Hai suppressed these people, he said, “Go to the side.” Those who surrendered obediently walked to the side. At this time, the Undead had already finished forming. But Zhao Hai didn’t immediately command them to point their allies. Instead, Zhao Hai looked at those left and said, “This is your last chance to surrender. After this, I’ll be impolite.”

Nobody else moved. Zhao Hai was too lazy to talk anymore. He just waved towards the Undead and had them point out the spies. At the same time, Zhao Hai concentrated at the crowd, just in case another person decided to make a move.

Everyone anxiously waited as the Undead walked among the crowd. Then suddenly, an Undead pointed at one person. That man immediately shouted before trying to escape. However, because he was surrounded, it didn’t take long before he was captured.

Now, as the Undead approached a group, those present began to prepare their magic and skills, guarded against those around them. They were afraid that the spies would suddenly lash out. Therefore, those who were pointed out by the Undead were immediately besieged.

As the Undead continued to point people out, the spies began defending while some tried to escape. But no matter what they did, they were all captured. Naturally, Zhao Hai was impolite and immediately turned them into Undead. Then he commanded these Undead to point out more people. This went on until the Undead could no longer point anyone out.

Once everything was over, Zhao Hai received the Undead. At the same time, those inside the cave began to relax.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Tie Sheng and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, we should be safe now.”

Tie Sheng nodded, then he pat Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Good job. Alright, everyone take a rest while we discuss what we’ll do from now on.”

Everyone nodded. At this time, Margaret suddenly said, “Big Brother Tie Sheng, it’s best if we return to the family as soon as possible. Otherwise, Brother Hai wouldn’t be able to join the realm qualifiers.”

Upon hearing Margaret, the expression on Tie Sheng and the others’s face changed. Then they turned to look at Zhao Hai. If it weren’t for Margaret, then they would’ve forgotten that Zhao Hai needed to attend the realm qualifiers.

The realm qualifiers will happen one month from now. If Zhao Hai cannot return, then he wouldn’t be able to participate.

Zhao Hai was the family’s strongest newcomer. If he cannot participate in the realm qualifiers, then not only the External Hall, the whole Ashley Family would suffer a huge loss. When the time comes, the Patriarch would certainly not let everyone off.

On the other hand, what Margaret was thinking about was Zhao Hai and Thunder’s agreement. If Zhao Hai cannot attend the realm qualifiers, then he wouldn’t be able to reach the top ten. And in turn, Thunder wouldn’t allow Margaret and Zhao Hai to be together.

Since she was worried about this, Margaret took the chance to remind Tie Sheng and the others. Tie Sheng knew how serious this matter was, so his expression couldn’t help but change.

To a family, the External Hall was an organization that fought for the family’s benefit. Everyone saw Zhao Hai’s strength. Because of this, they knew that he could place highly in the realm qualifiers. Additionally, it was possible for him to be in the top one hundred in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. In this case, how much benefit could he bring to the Ashley Family? If Zhao Hai fails to come back in time, then it would be beyond unfortunate.

With this thought in mind, Tie Sheng and the others began to the pressure. Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled, then he said, “Everyone, there’s no need to worry. There is still one month, I can certainly find a solution.” When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but blink. Then she thought about the fact that Zhao Hai was also use space magic. Maybe he could use a spatial rift to return back to Dark Demon Planet.

When Tie Sheng heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but ask, “Do you have a way?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I can also use space magic. But since my ability is still not enough, I cannot return directly to Dark Demon Planet. As long as I’m given time, I’ll be able to do so.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai wanting some time, Tie Sheng knew that Zhao Hai wanted to train himself in using Liquid Silver. When he thought of this, Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Alright. But you need to make sure that you’ll be on time for the realm qualifiers.”

At this time, Charles asked, “Zhao Hai, if you can return to Dark Demon Planet, then does that mean that we could return as well?”

Charles asked the question on everyone’s mind. When he asked this, everyone turned their vision towards Zhao Hai.

Tie Sheng’s expression changed, then he sneaked a look at Charles. Taking all of them back to Dark Demon Planet wasn’t a simple matter. Was he planning to set Zhao Hai on fire? If Zhao Hai said that he couldn’t, then wouldn’t he disappoint everyone here? Even the people from the Bone Symbol Camp might look disapprovingly of Zhao Hai.

But Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course I can take everyone. We’ll leave this place together. Everyone can rest assured.”

Charles’s expression loosened up. However, a deep dread began to appear in his eyes. Actually, he hoped that Zhao Hai couldn’t send everyone back. Therefore he deliberately asked this question so that people would feel discontent towards Zhao Hai.

The one who would lose the most face if this mission failed would be Zhao Hai. Because of the recent events, everyone undertaking the mission were beginning to admire him. And with Zhao Hai’s increasing fame in the External Hall, his reputation would increase once more when they return. This outcome wasn’t beneficial to the Ghost Symbol Camp.

But who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai was unexpectedly this strong. He could actually send everyone back to Dark Demon Planet. In the future, Zhao Hai would certainly be able to suppress everyone in the External Hall.

When everyone heard Zhao Hai, they all cheered, causing Zhao Hai to smile. He knew what Charles wanted to do, but he didn’t care much about it. Of course, he can send everyone back to Dark Demon Planet right now. The reason he delayed was because he didn’t want everyone to be terrified about his strength.

At the same time, now that the Zhang Family fully intends on becoming his enemy, he planned to make things very hard for them. The Zhang Family were now scouring the meteorite field in order to look for the Ashley Family. Zhao Hai wanted to use this opportunity to hunt them down.

Due to Zhao Hai’s assurance, the atmosphere inside the temporary base lightened up. The giant rock pressing down on their hearts disappeared and everyone began to relax.

At this time, Tie Sheng arrived by Zhao Hai’s side and whispered, “Little Hai, can you really send everyone back to Dark Demon Planet? There’s more than 1000 people here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, rest assured. Since I said that I can do it, then I can do it. Instead, let’s use the next couple of days to make the people from Zhang Family suffer. This way, they would know that we aren’t easily bullied.”

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to use the Space to send everyone back to Dark Demon Planet; since this would reveal one of his cards. However, with Margaret here, he couldn’t help but use it.

Moreover, he wanted to attend the Six Realm Beginner Competition. He was interested in the abilities of the other realms. And this competition was a great opportunity to understand the World of Cultivation.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was confident, Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Alright, we might as well. Since the Zhang Family to sent a lot of people into this meteorite field, let’s clean them up. We’ll let them know how terrifying we really are.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. Then after seeing that Charles and Leo were talking with each other, he whispered to Tie Sheng, “Brother, pay attention to that Charles. He seems to be up to no good.”

Tie Sheng smiled and said, “You think so as well? Rest assured, he can’t do anything. He wouldn’t dare act unreasonably in this place.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright. Then I’ll be taking a rest. Everyone should take a rest as well. We still need to settle accounts with the Zhang Family.”

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Go. Always be careful. You cannot suffer an accident. Otherwise, the Camp Lord will never let me off.” Zhao Hai smiled. Then he waved his hand, opening himself a cave using magic.

The long period spent in the meteorite field as well as the matter with the traitors made everyone very tired. But after they heard that Zhao Hai could send them back to Dark Demon Planet, they suddenly forgot that they were exhausted. After celebrating for a while, everyone returned to their caves in order to rest.

After resting for several hours, everyone began to get up. They still have dry rations on them. Therefore, after waking up, they ate a bit before going out into the main cave to discuss what to do next.

Zhao Hai also walked out from his cave at this time. When he came out, everyone gave him their greetings. After returning the gesture, Zhao Hai went to look for Tie Sheng. At this time, Tie Sheng was already with the commanders, discussing their future actions.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Tie Sheng gave his greetings before asking Zhao Hai to sit down. Then he said, “Little Hai, what do you think we should do next?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Zhang Family is still looking for us in the meteorite field. We’ll find them first and give them a fierce counter-attack.”

Charles frowned and said, “Since the Zhang Family wanted to deal with us, then it is certain that they sent out a lot of people. If we rashly attacked them, then we’ll end up suffering.’

Leo agreed, he added, “Although the meteorite field doesn’t allow their huge numbers to function well, this also applies to us. Not to say about finding them, aren’t we at a disadvantage in a fight?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Numbers doesn’t mean strength. As long as we make proper plans, we can clean them up in one go. It would be best if we send people to scout the surrounding areas. This way, we would be more confident in dealing with the Zhang Family.”

Chapter 1144: Smooth Scouting

Seeing Zhao Hai intending to fight with the Zhang Family, Charles and Leo’s expressions dropped. They don’t want to provoke the Zhang Family at this time. Such an action would only cause more casualties on their side.

Most importantly, Charles was afraid that Zhao Hai was doing this in order to weaken the other camps. To be honest, they didn’t expect this outcome when they started this mission. In their view, Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t that significant. Because of this, they weren’t afraid of Zhao Hai.

Tie Sheng looked at the eyes of the two. With Charles being from the Ghost Symbol Camp, Tie Sheng knew what he was thinking about, “You two, Zhao Hai didn’t want to fight just because he wants to. He currently has a newly refined weapon, so he wants to get accustomed to using it. Moreover, this is required so that we can all return to Dark Demon Planet. Since it is a new weapon, Little Hai is still not comfortable in using it. The more battles he goes into, the quicker he can adapt. Because of this, he needs to fight.”

Upon hearing Tie Sheng, Charles and Leo stopped themselves from talking. Whether this was true or not, they couldn’t disagree on Zhao Hai’s plan at this point. Otherwise, they would be seen as hindering everyone’s return to Dark Demon Planet. This would only make them everyone’s enemies. Naturally, this wasn’t something the two wanted to happen.

Seeing that nobody was talking, Zhao Hai turned to Tie Sheng and said, “Brother Tie Sheng, I’ll go scout ahead to locate the Zhang Family’s people. Meanwhile, you arrange the team to look at the surrounding terrain. It would be better for us if we are acquainted with the surrounding area before we fight the Zhang Family.”

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Alright. Go, leave matters here to me.”

When Zhao Hai left, Charles turned to Tie Sheng and said, “Tie Sheng, is the Bone Symbol Camp alright with being used by Zhao Hai? Why do you agree to anything he says?”

Tie Sheng looked at Charles and coldly snorted before he replied, “If you have someone like Zhao Hai in your Ghost Symbol Camp, then you would also be willing to be used by him. Also, Little Hai had never fought with the others for resources. Ever since he joined the camp until now, he had never consumed potions from the camp. Although he was given a reward, all of that was gained through his own effort. It can be said that the camp was the one treating him unfairly.” Naturally, Charles wasn’t thinking about the Bone Symbol Camp’s well-being when he asked this question. He was just planning to put a wedge in between Tie Sheng and Zhao Hai. However, he wasn’t informed about Zhao Hai’s matters in the Bone Symbol Camp. Because of this, his plan was put to waste.

When Leo saw that Tie Sheng wasn’t joking nor deliberately smudging facts, he couldn’t help but be curious, “What other things did Zhao Hai do for the Bone Symbol Camp?”

Tie Sheng smiled and said, “I can’t tell you that. However, I can say that not only did he give something to the camp, he also offered a gift to the family. Otherwise, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have been able to meet the Patriarch that easily. Moreover, didn’t you notice that the Patriarch didn’t do anything about Zhao Hai and Miss Margaret’s relationship?”

Charles and Leo stared. Then their expressions changed. They had been thinking about competing with Zhao Hai but they actually forgot about Margaret’s status. Naturally, people in their level knew more than others regarding Margaret.

At the time when they heard about Zhao Hai and Margaret, they couldn’t help but sigh about Zhao Hai’s good luck. He actually managed to snatch the family’s princess. However, they actually forgot about the underlying matters.

Upon thinking about the future, Charles and the others couldn’t help but feel envious. If Zhao Hai continued to have a relationship with Margaret, then he would soon leave the Bone Symbol Camp and become a core member of the family. Although it wasn’t the same as directly looking after the Bone Symbol Camp, his future position would still allow Desbarres to stop worrying about the camp.

At this moment, Zhao Hai already left the meteorite base. Since nobody was with him, he could use all of his abilities. Zhao Hai’s figure flashed as he returned to the Space.

Laura and the others were currently in front of the monitor looking at the situation outside. To be honest, the meteorite field was beautiful. Although it was filled with danger, the colorful scenery was still something to look at.

Seeing Zhao Hai come back, they immediately went to welcome him. It has been more than ten days since Zhao Hai entered the Space. Since he was with other people during the ambush, he didn’t have the chance to leave.

Zhao Hai hugged Laura and the others. Although ten days wasn’t a long time, he still missed them.

After everyone had settled down, Meg immediately offered Zhao Hai a cup of tea. Zhao Hai let out a long breath and then said, “The Space is really good. Nothing outside can compare to it.”

Laura and the others smiled. Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “Laura, how are the Zhang Family’s people doing?” While Zhao Hai was absent in the past few days, Laura and the others were busy. They took on the task of mapping the meteorite field.

This wasn’t a difficult matter to accomplish. They divided Liquid Silver into smaller versions and then explored the meteorite field. They even treated it as a game.

At this point, almost all of the Rainbow Meteorite Field had been mapped by the Space. Zhao Hai didn’t need to personally investigate the area. He could just relax inside the Space and look at the monitor.

Laura quickly opened the map of the meteorite field. It can be said that the field was really big. There were also small dots on the map. These dots surrounded a small passage. There were also rows of red dots on both ends of the passage.

Laura pointed at the red dots and said, “Brother Hai, look. The Zhang Family sent 50 medium-sized battleships altogether. They’re currently patrolling the passage. The ones currently pursuing you are only comprised of Mages and Warriors. Most of the Mechs retreated when your group entered the meteorite field. All in all, there are 20 thousand pursuers. They divided themselves into four to five groups and scoured the passage. They’re doing a comprehensive search on the immediate surroundings of the abandoned ship.”

After she said that, Laura gestured towards an area on the map. The region she pointed out were filled with red dots. These red dots indicated the Zhang Family’s search parties.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and nodded, then he said, “It seems like the Zhang Family are working really hard. This is good. It’s time to clean them up. Lizzy, which of the teams do you think are the easiest to deal with?”

Lizzy pointed towards the team that was the farthest from Zhao Hai’s base. Then she said, “It should be this one. They have mechs among them. Although mechs have strong combat power, they’re far less flexible than Mages and Warriors in this meteorite field. Additionally, they can’t deal with long-term battle.”

Zhao Hao nodded. Although the meteorites in this field weren’t too close together, they weren’t far apart either. And don’t forget, besides meteorites, there were also other things in the meteorite field. At the same time, mechs aren’t good for one-man combats. In a one-on-one battle against a Mage or a Warrior, it was likely for the Mage and Warrior to win.

The reason why people thought that mechs were more powerful than Mages and Warriors was because their average strength was better. Mages might win against one mech. However, in a battle that involved thousands, Mages and Warriors would certainly lose against them.

If one were to make an analogy using ancient chinese terms, Mages and Warriors were martial artists while Mechs were soldiers in the army. In a one-on-one battle, martial artists could certainly kill a soldier. However, when it came to large-scale battles, martial artists could never contend against an army.

And in this meteorite field, Mechs couldn’t fight a large-scale battle. Because of this, Mages and Warriors were in an advantageous position. Thus, Lizzy chose the team with the most Mechs.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Lizzy and said, “Let me see the details of that team.”

Lizzy nodded. Then the picture on the screen changed. A region was zoomed in, showing a team. There were 2000 Mages and Warriors as well as another 2000 Mechs. This number wasn’t small.

But it was obvious that these people weren’t stupid. The reason why they had mechs among them was because there weren’t a lot of meteorites in this area. Moreover, the distance between each meteorite was much greater compared to other areas.

Nevertheless, this wasn’t an issue for Zhao Hai. Even if the meteorites were far apart, as long as the battle begins, these meteorites would shatter, causing smaller rocks to splinter out. Mages and Warriors might be able to dodge these fragments, but Mechs would certainly have problems with it.

The information that Laura and the others collected didn’t stop at this. Since the Space’s network was connected to the outside world, they managed to get more than the locations of these teams. For example, they were able to know that these people were from the Zhang Family’s External Hall. Moreover, their identities were public, one could even see their information on the net!

Chapter 1145: Ambush

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t return to the temporary base so soon. It has been some time since he returned to the Space, so he decided to stay here for a while. He would go out from time to time to carry out a personal surveillance of the meteorite field.

Although he can look at the area while sitting inside the Space, Zhao Hai still wanted to see the place for himself. It was only when he was personally there could he become familiar with it.

The area wasn’t small, but the enemy only had 4000 people. This number wasn’t anything compared to the scale of the area.

However, Zhao Hai was still very careful. He knew that he couldn’t underestimate the Zhang Family. Most of these people were Mages. And even if their spiritual force was being suppressed, nobody can guarantee if anomalies would happen. If Zhao Hai was found out, then he would be in trouble. Even if he can escape, the situation still wouldn’t be good.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was paying close attention to their movements through the monitor. Then he would visit the area section by section. Although he was in the vicinity, Zhao Hai believed that the Zhang Family couldn’t find him. This was because he believed that nobody in the Zhang Family had the same level of spiritual force as him.

Zhao Hai returned to the Space after touring the meteorite field for a while. To be honest, there really wasn’t anything to see here. However, it was a very good place to stage an ambush.

There were magnetic storms happening everywhere. And no matter what scale it was, it would still affect Mechs and even people. And there was also the meteorites. If they were large enough, then spiritual force would find it hard to penetrate through. If it weren’t for the Space, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t have been able to properly scout.

Upon returning to the Space, Zhao Hai looked at the situation back at the temporary base. Tie Sheng and the others managed everything well. There were already teams of people scouting the area surrounding the base.

After staying inside the Space for a couple of hours, Zhao Hai proceeded to exit the Space. The place he reappeared at wasn’t that far from the temporary base.

Zhao Hai returned stating that he has something to report. Tie Sheng and the others immediately met with him. Those present were Tie Sheng and the other commanders, their assistants, and also Margaret.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was back, Tie Sheng immediately said, “Little Hai, how is it?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The entire passage has fallen under the Zhang Family’s control. There are 50 ships all in all blocking both exits of the passage. And it seems like they’ve sent more than 20 thousand people for this operation. I don’t know the specific numbers, but they have separated into four to five teams. With the destroyed ship as the center, they branched out to search for us. There are about 3000 or 4000 people on each team.” Tie Sheng and the others didn’t expect this much people to be going after them. Their expressions weren’t attractive to look at. Tie Sheng looked at Zhao Hai asked, “Little Hai, do you have a plan?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course. I discovered a good place to attack. We can certainly wipe out one team.”

Tie Sheng stared, then he said, “Wipe out one team? How many people are there?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s about 4000 people in that group. 2000 Mages and Warriors as well as about 2000 Mechs.”

Upon hearing this, Tie Sheng’s expression changed, then he shook his head and said, “That’s no good. There’s too many of them, it’s too dangerous. They have more people than us. Moreover, half of them are Mechs.” Charles and the others nodded.

But Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “It’s because of the Mechs that I suggested to attack that team. If it was outside, then we might have trouble fighting them. However, we’re currently inside the meteorite field. Those Mechs won’t be able to deal with us. As long as we prepare an ambush ahead of time, we can definitely wipe them out.”

Tie Sheng didn’t know where Zhao Hai’s confidence came from. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Tell us your plan.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he took out a map of the meteorite field and placed it on the stone table.

As Tie Sheng and the others listened to Zhao Hai’s plan, their eyes turned brighter and brighter. To be honest, the Zhang Family’s pursuit made them feel suffocated. But they were also clear that if they vent their anger, then the Zhang Family would catch them all. The outcome couldn’t justify the action. Because of this, they decided to endure.

However, this didn’t mean that they didn’t want revenge. There seems to be no flaws in the plan Zhao Hai proposed. It has a high probability to succeed. As long as they execute everything perfectly, then they could certainly kill 4000 Zhang Family members. This would allow them to breathe out some foul air.

Before long, Zhao Hai finished explaining his plan. Without even waiting for Tie Sheng to talk, Leo slapped his hand on the table and said, “Let’s do it. This plan… it’s most likely to succeed. I’ve been itching to kill some of those Zhang Family bastards.”

Charles smiled and said, “Since the Zhang Family doesn’t want us to leave this place, then we might as well clean them up. Let’s make them understand how terrifying we are.”

Seeing the two agree, Tie Sheng knew that the plan was going to get executed. Sure enough, the other commanders also agreed to Zhao Hai’s plan.

When everyone agreed to the plan, Zhao Hai looked at those present and said, “It’s not too late to start now. I reckon the other party would soon go back to their ship in order to take a rest. We can head there and stage an ambush. Perhaps we can even rest before the attack starts.”

Tie Sheng nodded. Then he turned to look at the other commanders and said, “Call everyone over. Let’s take an hour to rest and eat. After that, we make our move.” Nobody opposed to this, in fact, all of them were quick to move.

Before long, all those who were scouting outside were recalled. Then Zhao Hai took out food for everyone to eat. When the commanders told their people about Zhao Hai’s plan, all of them couldn’t help but be excited.

People from External Halls were like mercenaries. And because of this, they developed an unruly nature. Now that they had been pressured by the Zhang Family, they couldn’t help but feel a fire burning inside them. Hearing that they have an opportunity to take revenge, it was natural for them to burn with excitement.

After eating and taking a short rest, everyone was up and ready to move. This time, everyone including Margaret would move. After all, Margaret alone couldn’t defend the base. And if Margaret was left behind, then she would need people to accompany her. However, the group was currently short on manpower. If they leave some people behind, then their manpower would be further reduced. Therefore, Tie Sheng decided to take Margaret with them.

Under Zhao Hai’s lead, everyone went around specific areas in the field. After travelling for several hours, the group finally arrived at the area Zhao Hai decided on. And it seems like fortune was looking favorably at the Ashley Family, the Zhang Family’s people had already retreated to take a rest. This allowed Zhao Hai and the others to safely prepare an ambush.

Since there weren’t a lot of meteorites in this area, everyone couldn’t hide inside one. Instead, they separated into groups and hid inside separate meteorites, waiting for the time to attack.

The reason Zhao Hai was confident was because he already knew the Zhang Family’s movements. Laura and the others analyzed the Zhang Family’s patterns and found out that in order to perform a carpet search on an area, they would separate into smaller teams and search each meteorite one by one.

In this case, they would be able to find their target much more easily. And now, the place where Zhao Hai and the others were in had a high probability to be searched next. According to the computer analysis that Laura and the others did, the probability that this place would be searched was over 90%. This was the reason why Zhao Hai brought everyone here.

Zhao Hai, Margaret, as well as 100 people from the Bone Symbol Camp were currently inside a small meteorite. Since the meteorite wasn’t huge, they could immediately push it the moment the enemy approached them.

After everything has been taken care of, Zhao Hai made everyone take a rest so that they could maintain their optimum condition. While Zhao Hai was sitting cross-legged on the ground, he was talking with Laura and the others to see when the enemy would resume their search.

Laura and the others already grasped the patterns of the other party. When Zhao Hai and the others left their temporary base, the Zhang Family were still doing their search. They only stopped their search thirty minutes before Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the area. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s group still had plenty of time to rest, allowing them to restore any energy they managed to expend during travel.

After some calculations, Laura and the others estimated that the Zhang Family would take 3 to 4 hours before they resumed their search. Also, from the passage to this place, the Zhang Family would take another 2 to 3 hours. In other words, Zhao Hai’s group would have at least 5 to 6 hours to relax.

Whether it be Mages or Warriors, six hours of rest wasn’t a short time. Even if they underwent a long fight, 5 to 6 hours of rest would be enough for them to recuperate.

With this result in mind, Zhao Hai immediately left and delivered food to the various groups. But even if Zhao Hai had a lot of good food inside the Space, he didn’t take them out. He made sure that the ones he handed over were food that he had taken out of the Zhang Family’s merchant ship.

Chapter 1146: Ambush

Kelly was currently leading a group of people as they slowly flew forward. To be honest, he didn’t agree to the family’s decision. In order to deal with a few Warriors and Mages from the Ashley Family’s External Hall, they actually dispatched a lot of people as well as battleships. They were making a huge fuss over something trivial.

Moreover, the family even commanded a strict search of the surrounding region. To Kelly, this wasn’t necessary. The people from the Ashley Family had already been scared silly. They have already run far far away. It was impossible for them to stay in the vicinity. Perhaps they might even be deeper in the meteorite field looking for another way to leave.

If Kelly was a member of the Ashley Family, then he would do the same. He would try to leave the meteorite field through another place. This was a much better decision than staying in the meteorite field.

However, Kelly cannot defy the family’s orders. Although it has been more than ten years since he ascended, he still wouldn’t dare say anything about the family’s decision. Additionally, this action wasn’t done by only a single camp. They were even followed by a group of Mechs. Therefore, when they started their reconnaissance on a region named sector 5, they immediately divided it into smaller lots. Then they would carry out a comprehensive search on each area.

And they didn’t only search each lot, they also installed strong alarms inside lots they already searched. As long as people enter these areas, the alarm would immediately send out a notification.

Naturally, it was impossible for them to install these alarms everywhere. What they do is put alarms only on places that would have a huge potential of being entered. And as the Zhang Family pushed on, they would reposition these alarms whenever applicable.

Kelly’s group continued to move forward. Before long, they arrived at the area they were about to search. Those who entered the lot first were the Mechs. In the Machine Realm, Mechs held a much higher reputation compared to Mages and Warriors. Moreover, Mech pilots were mostly comprised of Machine Field natives. The reason for this was that the natives don’t look highly upon ascenders. Although Kelly was leading the team, he wasn’t the commander. Conversely, Kelly was the one who needed to listen to the commander of the Mech unit.

Kelly watched the surroundings while they advanced. Even if they haven’t gone to this area before, it wasn’t any different compared to other lots they searched. There were only meteorites everywhere, nothing else.

Kelly had met people from the other teams before they set out. Therefore, he knew that the others were doing their search on areas much more complex than his. This caused Kelly to be glad. In his mind, the less complex the terrain, the least danger they would be in.

As he was going forward, Kelly suddenly felt a movement of energy. He couldn’t help but stare. Then he stopped and sensed the surrounding area. He discovered that the surrounding meteorites were actually flying straight towards them. Kelly was shaken, then he immediately shouted, “It’s an ambush, prepare to fight!”

However, Kelly’s warning came too late. The target of the meteorites weren’t them, it was the Mechs. Although the Mechs were powerful, their mobility was still inferior compared to Mages and Warriors.

The meteorites were like huge stone balls that were fired towards the Mechs. Although the Mechs were doing their best to dodge, only a few managed to remain unscathed.

Moreover, there were quite a lot of meteorites, dozens of them. Although they weren’t large, they were at least a few notches bigger than the mechs. And each one of them were fast, it didn’t take long before the scouting team suffered a huge loss.

But this wasn’t the end. The meteorites weren’t just shot randomly, instead all of them met in the middle. Once they collided, they fragmented, attacking the Mechs once more. Among the 2000 Mechs present, more than 1000 were rendered useless. As for the remaining Mechs, they were also damaged, reducing their functionality by a few layers.

While Kelly and the others were flustered, several hundred sword qi were suddenly fired from all directions. The protective armor of the Mechs were already burst by the meteorites. So upon being hit by sword qi, the entire Mech troop was annihilated.

Following the sword qi were spells targeted towards Kelly and the others. These spells were at least 10 layers with most of them being 50-layer spells. Naturally, all of these spells had long since been prepared.

Although Kelly and the others had set up their own protective shields, it was still useless against the magical attacks. Before long, a large number of casualties emerged from the Zhang Family’s troop.

Another thing Kelly noticed was that these spells weren’t casually targeted. It seems like most of the spells were going towards the Warriors. The first wave of attacks took the lives of 300 Warriors.

After these two attacks were released, two attacks soon followed. It was already too late for Kelly’s side to retaliate. The group had already broken up with people running in all four directions. However, this was good for them. This way, the attacks coming from the Ashley Family wouldn’t deal with them at the same time. There were several people who came out unscathed.

From the beginning of the ambush up to now, Kelly’s group had eaten four rounds of attacks. Now, the Mechs were annihilated, the Warriors were severely cut down, and the numbers of the Mages were also slashed. At this point, Kelly’s group only had a bit more than 1000 people that were able to fight..

At this time, Zhao Hai’s side already began rushing towards the Zhang Family’s people. One side was full of morale while the other was in a panicked state. There was no need to ponder about the winner of this battle.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was eyeing Kelly. This was because he was the leader of the Mages and was the first to respond to the ambush. This meant that Kelly should have stronger spiritual force than the other Mages. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to experience Kelly’s strength. As soon as Kelly felt Zhao Hai’s focus on him, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment before sneering. Kelly knew that escaping was pointless at this point. The only thing he could do was fight.

Kelly was identified as a level 5 Mage. However, nobody knew that he had three staffs in his hand. One staff had a 10-layer formation, another had 50-layers, and then the last one had 100-layers. What he normally used was the staff with 50-layers. The other staffs were his secret weapons. Moreover, he had large quantities of restoration potions in his hand. Kelly believed that he has no need to be afraid of a level 6 Mage.

Kelly was quite an ambitious person. Almost all of the money he raised since he ascended were spent on buying armaments. He didn’t buy a villa nor did he indulge in leisure; all of his money was spent on strengthening himself.

Because of this, Kelly’s armaments could be said to be the best in the Zhang Family’s External Hall. Kelly didn’t only have the three staffs, he also has a protective item. At the same time, his mage robe was a high-level item, providing another point of protection. He also had a piece of metal with a restorative magic formation set inside. It can be said that with these items, Kelly had enough confidence to face level 6 experts. So when he saw Zhao Hai approaching him, he didn’t panic. On the contrary, Kelly took it as an opportunity.

He was preparing to capture Zhao Hai and use him as a hostage. This would give him a token to ask for freedom. Because of this, Kelly just stood in place and sent a spell towards Zhao Hai.

The spell was sent out by the 10-layer formation staff. At the same time, Kelly also activated his defensive formation.

Upon seeing the other party’s magic, Zhao Hai knew that they were using items. However, he didn’t care much about it and just waved his hand. Then a 10-layer formation appeared in front of him, blocking the incoming spell.

But shortly after that, Kelly took his 50-layer formation staff out and sent another spell towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s body changed direction as he moved back. At the same time, he erected another 10-layer formation in front of him. However, this formation didn’t block Kelly’s offensive magic.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai’s retreat was very fast. He arranged another 10-layer formation in front of him. Then immediately after the shield appeared, yet another one was cast. In turn, Kelly’s magic was blocked by three succeeding defensive formations.

Actually, it was completely unnecessary for Zhao Hai to do this. He just wanted to see how strong other people’s 50-layer magic formation were. But to be honest, Zhao Hai was disappointed by what he saw.

Kelly didn’t expect Zhao Hai to block his attack, after all,  it was a 50-layer magic formation. Kelly couldn’t help but give Zhao Hai even more importance. Then he traded his magic staff for the one with a 100-layer formation inside.

In the current Machine Field, 100-layer formations were rarely seen. This was because 100-layers were very hard to make. And engraving this kind of formation into a staff was much more difficult. The material requirements for this kind of endeavor was very high. Generally, staffs with 100-layer formations inside were made out of metal. Mithril as well as other additives were needed for the engraving to succeed.

Because of this, the staff’s weight would increase, as well as its cost. Mages who carry a 100 kilogram staff into a fight would certainly suffer. And because of the formations needed to be engraved, different types of materials were needed, further increasing the staff’s price.

Kelly hoisted his magic staff and inserted his own spiritual force on it. Since it was for a 100-layer formation, the amount of spiritual force needed was quite a lot. However, this sacrifice was worth it for the result. The 100-layer formation was Kelly’s strongest metal-element formation.

This magic formation was known as metal storm. When the magic formation materialized, it began to absorb the metal element energy in the surroundings. The spell grew bigger and bigger before it exploded into shards. Then the shards turned into a huge tornadoes. These tornadoes collided once more as it flew like a storm towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, then he said, “100 layers? Good. This is what I like to see.” Then he locked his fingers together, releasing a 100-layer formation in front of him. However, his formation was somewhat different. Half of the formation was red while the other half was azure.

When the formation had materialized, Zhao Hai loudly said, “Wind and Fire is eternal. Wind aids fire, fire eats wind! Explode!” Along with Zhao Hai’s voice, the formation in front fiercely exploded. A column of inferno began to shoot itself towards the metal storm.

Kelly sneered, he was very confident of his own 100-layer formation. This formation was made out of the most offensively powerful element. He doesn’t believe that Zhao Hai’s formation would block it.

But Kelly would soon realize that he was wrong. When the two formations hit each other, Kelly’s metal storm melted under Zhao Hai’s spell. The metals liquefied and before long they vaporized.

Kelly was left standing there, dazed. He didn’t expect this outcome. The magic staff he expensively bought was actually rendered useless.

Shortly after that, Zhao Hai said, “Fiery feathers, metal arrows. Rain of ten thousand arrows. Shoot!” As his voice fell, a rain of metallic arrows began to fall onto Kelly.

These arrows were very fast. But fortunately, Kelly’s defensive formation activated. When the arrows hit the shield, the shield shook fiercely, as though it would break at any time.

Kelly gawked. He immediately funneled his spiritual force towards the defensive formation. At the same time, he took out his 50-layer formation staff. He wouldn’t dare use his 100-layer formation staff for a long time. This wasn’t only because the staff was heavy, the spiritual force needed to sustain the formation was too huge. Kelly didn’t have the ability to make use of it for a long time.

Just as Kelly was about to launch his magic, he suddenly heard Zhao Hai, “Silent Demon Killing Arrows,. Fire!” After Zhao Hai said this, a 50-layer formation appeared in front of him. The formation was pitch black. Then a pointed tip appeared on the formation shortly followed by a black shaft and a blue tail. This arrows flew quickly, but they were eerily quiet. Their target was Kelly.

Kelly was caught while drinking. Because of his usage of magic, Kelly needed to replenish using a magic potion. Although potions recovered one’s magic quickly, the effect wasn’t immediate.

And while Kelly was restoring his magic, Zhao Hai’s arrow suddenly appeared in front of him!

Chapter 1147: Time To Head Back

Kelly was an old fighter who had a lot of experience in battles. Even if he was drinking a restoration potion, he was still channeling his spiritual qi towards his defensive formation. He knew clearly that his opponent wasn’t easy to deal with. Just the fact that Zhao Hai was able to break a 100-layer formation was enough evidence for his power. Since he knew about this, Kelly drank a potion ahead of time. He was prepared for a long-term fight.

But at this time, Zhao Hai’s dark arrow was already flying over. This arrow was specifically made for killing. It was a dark element formation with three metal element formations mixed into it. And judging by the fact that it was a 50-layer formation, one should be able to imagine how powerful it was.

While Kelly was drinking from his potion bottle, he suddenly felt his defensive formation vibrate. Just as he was about to notice what happened, the shield broke. It didn’t take long before Kelly felt pain from his body. When he put his bottle down, he quickly noticed pitch black holes on his body. The holes kept spurting corrupted blood, it was clear that he was poisoned.

“I should drink a detoxifying potion”was the final thought that came through Kelly’s mind before he died.

The Silent Demon Killing arrows were more lethal compared to other layered formations of its level. This was because the entire power of the 50-layer formation was concentrated on five arrows. Moreover, these arrows weren’t shot at the same time, instead they were successively released in a straight line. Because of this, all five were aimed towards a single point of Kelly’s shield. It took two arrows to destroy Kelly’s shield while the other three hit him. The arrows were also rotating, causing greater damage to Kelly’s body. The arrows were poisonous too. With these effects stacked together, there was no way for Kelly to survive.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t respect Kelly’s corpse, he immediately sent it to the Space and turned him into an Undead. After that, he switched his target to another person. They needed to finish this fight as soon as possible. This way, they could retreat sooner. Otherwise, they would be surrounded by the Zhang Family.

Actually, the fight was already nearing its end. Those who can escape had already escaped. Those who were left behind were already trapped and were nearly eliminated. From the initial 4000 people, 500 escaped while the rest were wiped out.

With Zhao Hai making his move, it didn’t take long before everything has been cleaned up. Immediately after that, Zhao Hai’s group left the area. As they were leaving, Zhao Hai took all of the destroyed Mechs as well as the corpses. If there weren’t smaller Mech fragments as well as crushed meteorites in the area, then nobody would know that a fight happened here.

Naturally, Zhao Hai had Cai’er clean these up after they left. He didn’t want other people to know about this ambush as much as possible.

By this point, the Undead Zhao Hai  created were much stronger compared to his other Undead. Before, Zhao Hai’s undead were at most rank 9 Apprentices. On the other hand, these new Undead were actually level 3 and above. For Zhao Hai, this wasn’t a weak fighting force.

After Zhao Hai and the others made several turns and circles, they managed to return to their temporary base. Everyone was very excited, their action this time allowed them to expel the foul air they’ve been keeping in all this time. Wiping out more than 3000 people from the Zhang Family was truly satisfying.

However, they didn’t celebrate until their brains shut down. Tie Sheng and the others quickly assigned people to act as sentries around the base. Then they commanded the others to take a rest so that they could maintain their optimum condition.

Nbody opposed to this. All of them knew that they were still in danger. Only when they return back to Dark Demon Planet would they attain true relaxation.

In the following days, Zhao Hai didn’t propose going out to attack the Zhang Family. Of course, the Zhang Family responded to the attack they just suffered. In their mind, the Ashley Family’s camp should be near the  battlefield. Because of this, they carried on a strict investigation on the surrounding area. Naturally, they weren’t able to find anything.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t stay in the same temporary base all these days. They moved further into the meteorite field. At this time, their location had become very dangerous.

Tie Sheng and the others knew that the most dangerous element in the meteorite field wasn’t the Zhang Family. It wasn’t easy for the Zhang Family to find Zhao Hai’s group. The meteorite field was just too big. With the number of the Ashley Family’s team compared to the size of the meteorite field as well as the Zhang Family’s numbers, it was almost impossible for Zhang Family to find them.

The most dangerous aspect of the meteorite field were the meteorites, magnetic storms, and other natural disasters that might happen in the field. These things don’t discriminate when it came to their victims. Meteorites would collide with each other and cause chain reactions on the surroundings. And these things happen randomly, making the meteorite field dangerous. Because of this, Tie Sheng and the others chose their temporary bases very carefully. They preferred bigger meteorites since they were more robust compared to the smaller ones.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t leave the new base, he continually placed great attention to the movements of the Zhang Family. Zhao Hai discovered that the Zhang Family had changed their approach. They no longer separated into teams to perform a search. Instead, all of their attention were focused on the passage. They also built temporary bases along the passage. Meanwhile, their ships patrolled the path between the passage and the direction to Dark Demon Planet. Naturally, they were planning to block the Ashley Family with this method.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai understood that the Zhang Family didn’t want to sour their relationship with Ashley Family yet. Otherwise, they would’ve used the occupied ship as a reason to wage war. At this time, Dark Demon Planet was still very peaceful, there were no signs of an approaching war.

The Zhang Family’s goal this time seems to be obtaining a ransom from the Ashley Family or even preventing Zhao Hai from attending the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

The latter point wasn’t just plucked by Zhao Hai from thin air. He speculated these from talks he heard from the Mages and Warriors of the Zhang Family. It seems like the Zhang Family really had a high-ranking spy placed in the Ashley Family. It was because of this that they managed to understand the internal matters of the Ashley Family.

It was also through this spy that they understood Zhao Hai’s strength. Therefore, they wanted to stop Zhao Hai from gaining benefits in the beginner competition.

In the past, Zhao Hai wasn’t clear about the Six Realm Beginner Competition’s importance for the family. But after this event, Zhao Hai knew that for a medium-grade influence like the Ashley Family, it was absolutely important.

Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on bringing trouble to the Zhang Family, he knew that it was impossible. The Zhang Family were now clumped up in and around the passage. They also built several bases on huge meteorites. Once Zhao Hai’s group attacked them, they would immediately be surrounded by walls of iron. Moreover, the Zhang Family set themselves up so that support would quickly arrive once a certain area was attacked. So instead, Zhao Hai spent his time idly inside the base before the time he decided to return to Dark Demon Planet.

Tie Sheng and the others didn’t pester Zhao Hai to deal with the Zhang Family. In fact, even they didn’t want to attack the Zhang Family. They were aware that attacking the Zhang Family was very risky. There was a huge possibility for them to suffer heavy casualties if they do attack.

Those who joined the mission were among the elites of the Ashley Family’s External Hall. It wouldn’t be good if they suffered heavy losses. And since Zhao Hai didn’t raise any plans of attack, the commanders also spent their time with ease. In any case, Zhao Hai had enough food to feed all of them. The only thing they did now was to relax inside the base.

Days quickly passed by. All this time, Zhao Hai was seen to be closing up to practice. However, nobody inside the base were discontented. What they knew was that Zhao Hai was anxiously practicing so that everyone can go home sooner.

Margaret was beginning to look unhealthy as the days went by. Seeing Zhao Hai working hard while everyone was living comfortably hurt Margaret’s heart.

Those who didn’t suffer couldn’t reach Zhao Hai’s level. With Zhao Hai’s strength, it was clear that he had suffered hardships before. Imagining what might have happened to Zhao Hai made Margaret’s heart ache.

During the last incursion, Margaret was able to see Zhao Hai’s merciless side. At the same time, Margaret could see Zhao Hai acting patiently, watching the enemy first before making a decisive move. As she thought of this, Margaret began to see Zhao Hai as a bottomless pit. She wanted to know more about him.

Everyone already knew that Margaret and Zhao Hai were quite close. Most of them knew who Margaret was and were clear that Zhao Hai would become a core member of the family in the future. But even if they were envious of Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but be convinced upon seeing his strength.

Time passed and soon there were only ten days left before the realm qualifiers starts. Zhao Hai had been closing up all this time, making Tie Sheng and the others more and more anxious. Every day, Tie Sheng and the others would send people to Zhao Hai’s cave to see if he came out. They were truly afraid that Zhao Hai might not be able to join the realm qualifiers.

Actually, what they didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was just doing normal training all this time. He did nothing else other than delaying. He didn’t want people to think that it was easy for him to send everyone back to Dark Demon Planet.

Seeing that there were only ten days left before the realm qualifiers, Zhao Hai finally decided to head out. He thought that it was time for him to return to Dark Demon Planet!

Chapter 1148: Coming Back!

Desbarres recently lost a lot of weight. And those who had insider information knew exactly why. He thought that his plan was seamless: but it actually turned out to be a trap! Most importantly, they were the ones who fell for it.

It can be said that the one who suffered the most loss was the Bone Symbol Camp. This was because the mission not only included Tie Sheng, it also had the camp’s most promising member, Zhao Hai. Additionally, with Zhao Hai’s close relationship with Margaret, the camp would be losing heavily if they couldn’t return.

Although it was said that Margaret went on her own decision, if something really happened to her, then it would be put on Desbarres’s head. And the Patriarch wasn’t a very reasonable person.

The only good news was the fact that the Zhang Family didn’t send any word that they had captured a lot of Experts from the Ashley Family’s External Hall. In the past, the Zhang Family would return the captured people and then send a warning to the family.

But if the Zhang Family manages to capture a large quantity of External Hall members, then they could use this as leverage to publicly break off their relationship with the Ashley Family.

Although the Zhang Family had yet to send word, this matter still placed a huge rock in everyone’s hearts. This was especially true for Desbarres. These days, it seems like he had halved his usual size.

Even if the family had yet to cause trouble for the Bone Symbol Camp’s Camp Lord, Desbarres himself felt very depressed in the past few days. Zhao Hai was the Bone Symbol Camp’s hope for revival. And now that he didn’t know when Zhao Hai would come back, Desbarres couldn’t help but have a massive headache.

Moreover, it can be said that Zhao Hai was the family’s primary representative in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. If Zhao Hai doesn’t come back, then the loss to the family would be too huge. This would cause Thunder to make Desbarres pay for his mistake.

With this situation weighing on his shoulders, no wonder Desbarres became so thin. And as the realm qualifiers got closer and closer, Desbarres’s face got more and more unsightly. The other Camp Lord couldn’t help but feel grief at the sight of him.

The Camp Lords had fairly similar states as Desbarres. Although some of them had their own authorities, the power they held wasn’t that huge. Among them, Desbarres clearly held the greater position. He was the Patriarch’s childhood friend and was a trusted aide of the family. This was evidently clear by Desbarres’s position as the External Hall’s manager.

But even if each Camp Lord had a competitive relationship, they were also allies in a way. Since the External Hall was a weak entity, they needed to band together so that they had the right to speak out.

Seeing Desbarres suffer bad luck, the other Camp Lords were also feeling bad. Even Dia who liked to take a jab at Desbarres didn’t say a single word about this event.

Actually, it wasn’t only Desbarres. The entire Bone Symbol Camp was feeling depressed. Zhao Hai just came to the limelight by defeating the other camps and emerging as the family’s champion. All of them were thinking that the revival of the Bone Symbol Camp was near. They didn’t expect a matter such as this to happen. This caused the Bone Symbol Camp to feel an unprecedented disappointment.

People were like this. If they don’t hope, then they won’t be disappointed. However, once they were given hope and that hope was shattered, their disappointment would be magnified by several folds.

The Bone Symbol Camp’s mood was as low as a deep valley. Although Tao Wang saw this, he couldn’t do anything. He was also feeling down in the past few days. And his physique was much worse than Desbarres. He wasn’t fat to begin with, so after all these days, Tao Wang was as skinny as a skeleton.

Seeing that there were only ten days left before the realm qualifiers, Desbarres and Tao Wang began to feel despair. Even if Zhao Hai managed to escape now, he still wouldn’t be able to make it to the qualifiers.

Silence conquered Desbarres’s office, he had lost any motivation and energy to speak at this point. Then suddenly, running was heard from outside. Then a person with a happy expression opened the door. He looked at Desbarres and said ,”Camp Lord, come out, quick. Something just came up!”

Desbarres looked at the person and said, “Something happened? What is it?”

The person excitedly said, “Commander Tie Sheng. Commander Tie Sheng is back!”

Upon hearing this, Desbarres and Tao Wang stared. They looked at each other for some time before they simultaneously stood up. Their faces seemed to light up. Then Desbarres asked, “Tie Sheng? Are you sure it’s him?”

The person immediately answered, “It’s him. Camp Lord, you should take a look yourself!” Desbarres and Tao Wang didn’t wait for the person to lead them out as they quickly ran.

When they arrived at the Bone Symbol Camp’s field, they saw people coming out of an enormous spatial rift.

These people were completely covered in dust. They might look haggard but none of them were injured and all of them had bright expressions on their faces. One of these people stood right by the rift as he led the others out; this man was Tie Sheng.

Desbarres took a deep breath. Then he quickly flew towards Tie Sheng’s side, his face evidently brighter than before as he asked, “Tie Sheng, what is this?”

When Tie Sheng saw Desbarres, he immediately gave a salute, then he replied, “Camp Lord, we’ve come back safely. It’s Little Hai. He used his spatial ability to send us here.”

Desbarres looked at the people coming out of the rift. He scrutinized each person but couldn’t see Zhao Hai. When Tie Sheng saw Desbarres’s action, he couldn’t help but smile as he said, “Camp Lord, there’s no need to worry. Little Hai is behind the rift. He’s doing fine.” Desbarres nodded, then his mood returned to normal. Nobody from the Bone Symbol Camp were among those who were currently pouring out of the rift. Desbarres quickly understood that the evacuation was done according to camps.

It didn’t take long before the people from the Bone Symbol Camp were sent over. When these people saw their friends, they immediately went over to talk. Before long, laughter filled the camp.

Seeing this situation, Desbarres removed the worry in his heart. Moreover, he could see that the losses suffered by the External Hall wasn’t that heavy.

It didn’t take an hour for everyone to go through the spatial rift. The last people to go through were Zhao Hai and Margaret. Zhao Hai’s expression was calm while Margaret had a faint smile on her face. As she followed beside Zhao Hai, she looked like a wife following her husband.

When Zhao Hai came out, the rift quickly closed. Desbarres immediately moved forward to meet him. Seeing Desbarres arrive, Zhao Hai quickly gave a salute and said, “Camp Lord, I’m back.”

Desbarres grabbed Zhao Hai’s shoulders and laughed, “Good, it’s good that you’re doing well. I’m sure it has been hard on you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s okay. There’s no need for the Camp Lord to worry.”

Desbarres gave a nod before he looked at the people from the other camps. Then he laughed and said, “Today’s a happy day. Don’t leave yet, share a meal with my Bone Symbol Camp. Tao Wang, send word to the Camp Lords explaining the situation. Tie Sheng, have everyone wash up while I go and report to the Patriarch.”

Tao Wang also went over to Zhao Hai and gave him a tight hug. Only then did he go to arrange matters. Meanwhile, Tie Sheng nodded and led everyone to the Bone Symbol Camp’s building to take a rest. Desbarres didn’t delay and immediately flew towards Lofty Demon Island.

………………..

Margaret was currently inside a villa prepared for her by the Bone Symbol Camp. Also, this place wasn’t far from Zhao Hai. When she came back to her room, Margaret washed her face and combed her hair. Because of the state of the meteorite field, taking a bath was not an option. Although there were people who can use water element magic to produce water, the amount they were able to take out wasn’t enough for people to take a bath in. This was the reason why everyone appeared haggard.

Originally, Charles and the others readied themselves to return to their camp. However, Desbarres already made preparations for them and even reported the matter to the Camp Lords. Because of this, people from the other camps had no choice but to accept the Bone Symbol Camp’s hospitality.

At this moment, Desbarres arrived at Lofty Demon Island. Due to his excitement, he didn’t ride a car and just flew the entire trip. After arriving at the island, Desbarres went directly to Thunder’s study. This was also the place where the Patriarch did his work.

In the Ashley Family, there were only a few people who can directly find the Patriarch in his study, and Desbarres was one of these people. This was also a demonstration of Desbarres’s status.

Cadjo wasn’t in the study. He was the Ashley Family’s manager. Because of this, he couldn’t just follow Thunder like a secretary. Moreover, Thunder already had his own female secretary.

When Desbarres saw the secretary outside Thunder’s office, he quickly said, “Notify the Patriarch quickly. I have something important to report.”

Naturally, the attractive female secretary knew about the relationship between Desbarres and Thunder. So she didn’t dare to delay as she quickly pressed a key and sent a notification, “Patriarch, Manager Desbarres is here asking for an audience. He said that he has something important to say.”

Thunder’s reply was quickly heard, “Let him in.” The secretary nodded. Just as she was about to ask Desbarres to go in, the fatty already pushed the door and impatiently entered the study.

Thunder was currently sitting in his chair while reading a document. Although computers were prevalent in the Machine Field, documents were still in paper form.

Desbarres bowed and said, “I’ve seen the Young Master.” Thunder looked up at Desbarres and nodded, “Sit. Fatty Des, you’ve become thinner.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Young Master, you can rest assured, I’ll be back to being fat in no time. Right, those who went out for the mission have come back. This includes Zhao Hai and Miss Margaret.”

Upon hearing Desbarres, Thunder couldn’t help but gawk. He placed the document on his hand down as he said, “They’re back? How?”

Desbarres quickly answered, “Tie Sheng told me that it’s because of Little Hai’s space magic. They’re now resting in the Bone Symbol Camp. I’ve invited everyone to a meal after. I’m sure they also suffered a lot.”

Chapter 1149: Breaking The Engagement!

When he heard this, Thunder couldn’t help but raise his eyebrow as he responded, “So it is Space Magic. That is quite a rare ability. But if Zhao Hai can send them back using Space Magic, then why did they only return now?”

Desbarres stared, he didn’t expect Thunder to ask a question at this time. He paused for a moment before he answered, “I don’t know. Young Master, I’ll go ask him when I go back. Then I’ll report back to you.”

Thunder waved his hand and said, “There’s no need. I reckon the timing of their return is related to that thing. Don’t worry about it. Right, have Zhao Hai take a rest. If he needs anything like potions, make sure to give it to him. We need him to be in his optimum condition. The Ashley Family cannot lose in the qualifiers.”

Desbarres nodded, “Young Master, you can rest assured.”

Thunder nodded and said, “Tell the Zhang Family that the Ashley Family denies their allegations. The members of our External Hall have already returned from their mission. If the Zhang Family still dares to be impolite, then we’ll publicly break our relationship with them. Also, tell them that their conduct this time has made me very discontented. Therefore, I’m breaking Margaret and the Zhang Mingyue’s engagement.”

Desbarres stared, then he immediately knew why Thunder did so. The Zhang Family had been publicly saying that since a large part of the External Hall elites were missing, and that an Ashley Family ship was found in the meteorite field, then the Ashley Family were the ones who attacked them.

Actually, the two families knew that this was nothing more than the Zhang Family catching the Ashley Family’s plan. Therefore, the Zhang Family was just using it as a means to pressure the Ashley Family.

But now that Zhao Hai and the others had returned, the Ashley Family could say that there was no such thing. This caused the Ashley Family to sigh in relief.

And at this point, Margaret’s feelings for Zhao Hai were very clear. However, Margaret still had an engagement with the Zhang Family. This might affect Zhao Hai and Margaret’s relationship. Because of this, Thunder decided to use this opportunity to break the marriage agreement.

Desbarres immediately nodded, but he warned, “Young Master, the Zhang Family is becoming more and more brazen recently. It seems like it is a matter of time before they begin moving against us. We need to guard against them.”

Thunder clicked his mouth before he sighed and said, “The Zhang Family has been preparing to deal with us. And we’re a step later than them. However, the Zhang Family is not done with their preparation. They wouldn’t dare fight large scale battles at this time. Because of this, they were still sending cheap shots at us. Hmph. If the Zhang Family really wants to fight the Ashley Family, then I’ll make sure to beat them so hard that they would return with no teeth left.” After he spoke this, the atmosphere around Thunder began to turn cold.

Desbarres was intently listening. Actually, Desbarres and the others were already aware of the Zhang Family’s plan and had repeatedly reminded Thunder about it. However, Thunder didn’t care about it before. He was still thinking that the Zhang Family were the Ashley Family’s strongest ally.

Thunder finally accepted the warning against the Zhang Family when Margaret was attacked. Moreover, upon further investigation, it was proven that it was the Zhang Family who did it. It was also because of this that Thunder agreed to the assault mission. He wanted to strike the Zhang Family in order to test their response.

If the Zhang Family was innocent, then they wouldn’t know about this matter and wouldn’t retaliate too heavily. However, the Zhang Family’s response was fierce, they even set up a trap to take a bite out of the Ashley Family. This opened Thunder’s eyes to the fact that the Zhang Family wanted to deal with the Ashley Family.

The Zhang Family’s plan was good. They wanted to catch Zhao Hai and the others. And even if they can’t, they could still block Zhao Hai from entering the realm qualifiers. This way, the Ashley Family’s benefits would suffer a huge hit. And also, it would be easier for them to deal with the Ashley Family in the future.

However, the Zhang Family didn’t expect how significant Zhao Hai’s impact would be. Now that Zhao Hai was able to bring everyone back to Dark Demon Planet, the Zhang Family’s plan was destroyed. Moreover, their actions had made Thunder vigilant. The Zhang Family tried to steal a chicken only to lose the rice used to bait it.

However, the Ashley Family wouldn’t use this event to strike the Zhang Family. They didn’t have the strength to do it yet. In fact, if it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then the Ashley Family would take even greater losses. Asking a small price in order to deal with this grievance was enough.

Desbarres looked at Thunder and said, “Young Master, with this altercation with the Zhang Family, the importance of the Six Realm Beginner Competition has become more apparent. As long as we make good progress in the competition, we’ll be able to gain more benefits and would no longer worry about not having an ally. The Zhang Family made a significant move against us, they even want to prevent Little Hai from entering the beginner competition. It seems like they’re afraid that we would get a good position. It’s now certain that the Zhang Family has a high-level spy in our family. The most pressing matter for now is to find this spy.”

Thunder Ashley wasn’t a fool. Although he rarely accepted comments, he still knew what to do at certain times. Therefore, he understood what Desbarres wanted to say as he nodded and said, “Rest assured, I will make sure to look this up. There weren’t a lot of people who knew about the mission. I believe we’ll be able to see results soon. Meanwhile, Fatty Des, you make sure that Little Hai gets what he wants. You need to take good care of him.” Desbarres nodded before he turned around and left.

When Desbarres returned to the Bone Symbol Camp, the other Camp Lords were already there. At this time, they were talking to the commanders about what happened.

Desbarres didn’t go to see them but instead he called Tie Sheng over to his office. Desbarres looked at Tie Sheng and said, “Tie Sheng, tell me exactly what happened.” Tie Sheng nodded and then explained everything from the start up to their return. Desbarres listened intently and then nodded and said, “It looks like Little Hai has become better in using Liquid Silver. Moreover, Little Hai’s strength is probably getting closer to ours. It seems like his claims of becoming top ten in the Six Realm Beginner Competition wasn’t just a boast.”

Tie Sheng nodded and said, “Little Hai has become very strong. He will surely blossom in the beginner competition. I’m just afraid that the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to retain him.” Desbarres smiled bitterly and said, “With the Ashley Family’s strength, it’s impossible for us to keep him. Little Hai will certainly become a famous powerful expert. However, even if the Ashley Family family couldn’t keep him, as long as everyone knew that he came from us, then that is already enough to make people think differently about the family. It doesn’t matter if he stays or not.”

Tie Sheng nodded. Then Desbarres said, “Alright, let’s go to the dining hall. The other Camp Lords should already be aware of the situation. They owe us a huge favor this time.” Tie Sheng smiled faintly before he followed Desbarres back to the dining hall.

The dining hall has been filled up. Besides those from the other camps, everyone currently in the Bone Symbol Camp came to the hall. The entire room looked very lively, their faces were full of excitement.

It can be said that this mission concerned the entirety of the External Hall. This was because elites of the External Hall participated in this mission. These people had fairly high status in the Ashley Family’s External Hall, they were the backbone of the force. Whenever a camp loses people like them, the camp would surely suffer a serious blow.

It has been some time before these people had ascended to the Machine Field. Because of this, they were able to make friends with people from other camps; and some even became tied by familial ties. It can be said that these people were more or less involved with each other. In this case, the fact that everyone returned was a very joyous matter.

As for the Zhang Family spies that Zhao Hai captured, they had already been handed over to the family to deal with. Zhao Hai and Tie Sheng had guaranteed their safety as well as return to Dark Demon Planet. As for what happens to them after arriving at the family, that was something that Zhao Hai cannot control.

After Zhao Hai returned to his room, he immediately cleaned himself inside the Space before going back out and heading towards the dining hall.

Zhao Hai wore a black robe. Although it wasn’t ugly, it wasn’t eye-catching either. And with Zhao Hai’s ordinary looks, it would be hard for people to see him in a crowd.

The reason for his lack of presence was Zhao Hai’s decision to not display anything. This made sure that he looked as ordinary as he can be.

After he came out, Zhao Hai immediately saw Tao Wang approaching him. When Tao Wang saw Zhao Hai, he immediately said, “Let’s go quick. Our Brothers want to see their hero.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “How come I became a hero? Right, did Margaret head out already?”

Tao Wang smiled and said ,”Not yet, but you should know that women would take a long time to dress up. I have already told her robot to relay the message.”

Zhao Hao nodded, then he followed Tao Wang to the dining hall. Zhao Hai and Tao Wang arrived at the dining hall at almost the same time as Desbarres and Tie Sheng. As soon Desbarres saw Zhao Hai, he immediately waved at him. Tao Wang and Zhao Hai quickly went over and took a seat. Desbarres smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you’ve done very well. Those guys now owe us big time. Let’s see how they’ll pay us back.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Camp Lord, don’t you think seizing this opportunity for benefit is a bit out of place?”

Desbarres smiled and said, “There’s no need for you to worry about this matter. In any case, this will be good for you. Right, you returned just at the right time for the realm qualifiers. The Patriarch is placing great importance to the competition. He wanted to make sure that I relay this information to you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Camp Lord, rest assured. I know what I need to do.”

Desbarres gave nod, then he asked, “Are you injured? Or perhaps feeling uncomfortable anywhere? The Patriarch said that we should fully support you. He wants you to stay at your best state as much as possible.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and smiled, “Camp Lord, I absolutely fine.”

Desbarres nodded, then he said, “That’s good. Those fellows are here, I need to deal with them. We’ll talk later.” Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t stop Desbarres. Desbarres stood up and then walked towards Dia and the others.

The arrival of the seven Camp Lords made the dining hall’s atmosphere a bit weird for those from the Bone Symbol Camp. Under normal conditions, these Camp Lords would not step foot in the Bone Symbol Camp. This was because of the camp’s constant decline over the years. These Camp Lords even look down on the camp. But this time, they actually went to the camp themselves. Moreover, they came to express their gratitude, which made those from the Bone Symbol Camp proud and elated.

Desbarres didn’t go too far this time. He just chatted with the other Camp Lords for a moment before asking them to sit down. Naturally, Zhao Hai was also present on the table. Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just gave the Camp Lords a salute. Dia and the others returned the courtesy while expressing their gratitude to Zhao Hai. But at the same time, their eyes couldn’t help but show a sense of deep envy.

After everyone had sat down, Desbarres went to the dining hall’s stage. He waved his hand to silence the hall before saying, “The mission had been a huge trial for our External Hall. But it was fortunate that everyone managed to return safely. I need to commend everyone here for their bravery. You certainly didn’t make the Ashley Family lose face. You’re the pride of our External Hall!” After he said this, everyone in the hall issued a cheer.

Desbarres waved his hand once more. After seeing everyone calm down, he continued, “Everyone has certainly suffered in the past few days. I have already discussed it with your Camp Lords, your contribution points for this mission will be increased. Additionally, each camp will add a bonus on top of your initial reward. Brothers, you’re now rich!”

Desbarres’s words brought laughter and whistling to the hall. People from the External Hall liked to hear about rewards. Desbarres’s words were completely aimed at their hearts. There weren’t even any official statements, which made everyone feel great.

After Desbarres calmed everyone down, he said, “Everyone, I know that you haven’t had a good meal and a good rest in the past days. So I won’t be saying anything more. Brothers, eat, drink. Welcome home!” Everyone cheered. Then robots began giving everyone food and drinks. The feast had officially begun.

Throughout his speech, Desbarres didn’t mention a word about Zhao Hai’s merit. This was a brilliant move. Zhao Hai’s action of saving everyone had already been engraved in their hearts. If Desbarres mentioned it, then it would seem too petty.

When Desbarres returned to his table, Dia and the others looked at him strangely. They never talked like this to the people in their camp. It was at this point where they saw their gap with Desbarres.

Chapter 1150: Finding Out

The dining hall’s mood was very warm. But what surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that Margaret wasn’t in sight. But even if he was confused, he didn’t think too deeply about it.

After everyone became drunk, Zhao Hai returned to his villa. He wasn’t able to eat a lot at the feast since he was drinking with Desbarres and the others. However, he used spatial water to dissolve the alcohol. So even if he drank a lot, he wasn’t drunk at all.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he came close to his villa. He just felt someone’s presence inside. However, Zhao Hai didn’t feel any danger because he saw that it was Margaret when he swept his villa using his spiritual force.

Although Zhao Hai was somewhat puzzled, he still entered his villa. Margaret was currently sitting in the living room. When Zhao Hai saw Margaret, he couldn’t help but gawk. This was because the present Margaret was different than before.

In the past, Margaret looked like a humble Mage. Although she still took care of herself, she had a simple image. She also wouldn’t put makeup on her face, she was old-fashioned.

But today’s Margaret was different. She wore a new mage robe. Although the robe was still black, it seemed more attractive than what she wore before. Her hair had also been attractively set-up. Most importantly, Margaret was wearing makeup. Although it was only a faint application, it actually complemented Margaret’s calm temperament.

Margaret had a different temperament compared to Zhao Hai’s wives. Laura sent off an aura of a capable woman, her presence could be felt in a room. There was no need to say about Lizzy and Megan. The two of them were practically brought up to be princesses, so their presence exudes majesty. Meg didn’t have much aura to talk about. However, she had a quiet temperament that told people that her life revolved around Zhao Hai. Ruyen’s aura was a bit less compared to Lizzy’s. After all, she was only a princess of a small Duchy. Moreover, with her past reputation, she always felt that she was inferior to Lizzy and the others. Berry had a different aura compared to the others. She was from a Succubus Clan and also a Demon. Her talent was in assassination so her temperament was kind of cold.

On the other hand, Margaret grew up researching magic formations. After she grew up, she spent her life as an instructor. Because of this, she exudes an aura of a scholar. She had a gentle and solemn temperament.

When Margaret saw that Zhao Hai was staring at her, her face couldn’t help but turn red. Then she slowly stood up and smiled before saying, “Am I attractive?”

Zhao Hai recovered, he looked at Margaret and said, “Of course you are, you’re beautiful.”

Margaret walked towards ZHao Hai, here eyes fixed on his, then she said, “Zhao Hai, ever since you saved me from Tyro Planet, I began to see you differently. Although you have killed a lot of people, I still couldn’t help but like you. And after the mission, I came to see that I liked you more. I want to marry you. It doesn’t matter if you have other wives or if they don’t like me, I still want to marry you. Do you want to marry me?”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Margaret to be so forward. Margaret looked like a silent person whenever they met, he didn’t even feel a bit of intimacy from her. Her words truly made him surprised.

But what Zhao Hai didn’t know was that Margaret had changed after experiencing near death experience twice. The environment back in the meteorite field would make anyone pessimistic, and naturally Margaret was not an exception. She basically grew up in a greenhouse and hadn’t faced hardship before. At that time, Margaret thought that she might really be trapped in the meteorite field or be captured by the Zhang Family.

Also, during that time, Margaret began to discover that life was unpredictable. If they died at the meteorite field, then she wouldn’t have the chance to confess to Zhao Hai.

Although her depressed state disappeared when they returned to Dark Demon Planet, the thought of confessing to Zhao Hai never vanished inside Margaret’s mind. Instead, the idea became more and more intense. Margaret thought about another accident approaching where she really wouldn’t have the chance to show her feelings. Therefore, after she returned to her villa, Margaret decided to tell Zhao Hai as soon as possible.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret, then he lightly sighed and said, “Margaret, I can understand what you’re thinking. But you should know that I love my wives. So if you really want to marry me, then you have to share. Are you still willing?”

Margaret didn’t even think about it as she answered, “I’m willing!”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Margaret, you don’t understand. You’re thinking that my wives are in the lower realms, so you only have to share with me spiritually. But this isn’t the case. I brought my wives with me. So if you marry me, then you will also share physically. Do you understand?”

Margaret had a confused expression. She shook her head, showing that she couldn’t understand what Zhao Hai was saying. What did Zhao Hai mean that he brought them with him?

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret, then he sighed and said, “Please stay calm, no matter where you end up, don’t be afraid. And if you decide not to marry me after this, I hope that you keep things you see as a secret.”

Margaret was still confused at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his hand, opening a spatial rift on his side. Then he took Margaret’s hand and said, “Margaret, come in and take a look. This is my biggest secret.”

Despite being confused by what Zhao Hai said, Margaret still entered the spatial rift. She believes that Zhao Hai wouldn’t harm her.

Right after she emerged from the other side of the rift, Margaret was shocked. What met her vision was an infinitely large space. She was currently standing on a meadow with a somewhat ancient looking villa in the distance. The villa was covered with seven-colored vines while also have huge trees on its sides.

Naturally, this wasn’t the most important thing. What was important were the six beautiful women standing in front. All of them were beauties, not any worse than Margaret herself. Some were even more attractive than her.

Right when Margaret appeared, the woman at the front of the group smiled faintly and saidm “Hello Miss Margaret. We’re Zhao Hai’s wives. My name is Laura. Perhaps you might not know us, but we’ve known you for a long time.”

Upon hearing Laura, Margaret quickly recovered. However, her mind was still not cleared, she could only mechanically reply, “Hello, I am Margaret.”

Lizzy and the others also took the chance to introduce themselves, with Margaret blankly replying. She repeated her response multiple times, looking somewhat silly.

Then at this time, ZHao Hai’s voice was heard, “Margaret, this is my biggest secret. You can follow Laura and they will explain this to you. Laura, please explain everything to Margaret. I’m tired and would like to take a rest.” Laura nodded and took Margaret to the villa.

Margaret was pulled by Laura as she dazedly walked towards the villa. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai returned to his room in the Bone Symbol Camp. He was afraid that Desbarres might come looking for him, so he could only wait there for now.

At the same time, Laura pulled Margaret to the villa and invited her to sit. Meg offered some tea to Margaret as they looked at the Space’s monitor. Displayed on the screen was Zhao Hai inside his Bone Symbol Camp villa.

Laura looked at Margaret and smiled as she said, “We can see everything using this monitor. It can be said that when you first met Brother Hai, we also saw you. And every time you see Brother Hai, we know.”

Upon hearing Laura, Margaret’s face couldn’t help but pale. She suddenly thought that she was like someone who was having an affair with another woman’s husband. And she was now being exposed.

Laura saw Margaret’s expression and immediately understood what she was thinking. So Laura smiled and assured her, “There’s no need to be nervous. In fact, we urged Brother Hai to get closer to you. If you don’t have our support, then I’m afraid your relationship with Brother Hai wouldn’t have developed this quickly.”

Margaret turned her head to Laura, her face couldn’t hide her confusion. Laura smiled and said, “Let us tell you everything about Brother Hai. I believe you’ll understand how good he is after.” Then Laura and the other proceeded to tell Margaret everything about Zhao Hai.

Margaret listened to the legendary life that Zhao Hai had. She heard all sorts of stories about his accomplishments in the lower realms.

Zhao Hai’s matters couldn’t be expressed in just a few words. Moreover, Laura couldn’t tell everything herself. So when she was tired, someone would take her place and continued the story.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was inside his villa. Desbarres and the others didn’t visit him this time. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried since he also needed time to think about the future.

When he attends the Six Realm Beginner Competition, he doesn’t know whether he would meet Lu Wei or the Yin Wind Spirit Emperor. In the past, if he really met the two of them and they take revenge, he wouldn’t know if he can be their match.

But now that he obtained Liquid SIlver, Zhao Hai’s state of mind had changed. Instead of harboring deep dread in meeting these two enemies, Zhao Hai was even thinking of challenging them. This was because these two people were his biggest personal enemies. He needed to defeat them, it was his duty to do so. This way, his status wouldn’t be revealed!

Chapter 1151: On the Nuptial Chamber

The biggest reason why Zhao Hai doesn’t want his identity revealed was because he had another enemy stronger and more terrifying than Lu Wei and the Yin Wind Spirit Emperor. And this enemy was the Myriad Treasures Pavillion!

Zhao Hai knew some details about Lu Wei. He was an elder of the Five Gates Sect, but Zhao Hai knew that his position didn’t have a huge authority in a sect. This was because Zhao Hai was able to find out about known elders from first rate sects. And it seems like Lu Wei was just an ordinary elder of his sect.

As for why Lu Wei, who didn’t have much influence, was able to collect Faith Power from the lower realms, there was a good explanation for it. Those who were able to collect Faith Power did so in secrecy. Even those they were closest to were not told about it.

Moreover, collecting Faith Power from the lower realms required specialized artifacts. These artifacts needed to have a certain relation to the lower realms and could only be obtained through chance.

Zhao Hai looked up some Experts from great sects in the Cultivation Realm, however, he wasn’t able to see Lu Wei’s name. This made Zhao Hai understand that Lu Wei was just an ordinary elder of the Five Gates Sect. He didn’t have real strength to speak of.

There was nothing to say about the Yin Wind Spirit Emperor. The Emperor’s true threat was the fact that he was a free person who didn’t have any foundations that tied him up in place. It might also be possible that his connection with the Underworld was due to luck. So although he was quite strong, there was no need for Zhao Hai to be afraid of him. After all, the ability of a single person was limited.

Moreover, the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor had offended formidable people and was chased down to the point of forcing him into hiding. In his current state, he had no time to chase Zhao Hai down.

But the Myriad Treasures Pavillion was different. The pavillion was a huge trading company in the Cultivation Realm. It can be said that they were a huge power. And because of their scale, they were very rich. This also made them able to have massive amounts of experts working for them. It can be said that offending such an existence wasn’t wise.

And through the internet, Zhao Hai was able to look into how the pavillion was able to grow so quickly. The reason for their growth was the unique yin-attribute items that they were able to sell.

Upon seeing this report, Zhao Hai knew that he was in big trouble. Breaking a merchant’s source of income was the same as breaking their legs. This hatred would forever remain unforgotten. And Zhao Hai just severed the Myriad Treasures Pavillion’s main source of income.

Breaking the pavillion’s source of income meant that Zhao Hai was now the pavillion’s biggest enemy. Additionally, the Myriad Treasures Pavilion was different than Lu Wei or the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. Unlike the latter two, Zhao Hai didn’t just offend one person, but the entirety of the pavilion itself. If the pavilion were to know about Zhao Hai’s identity, then a huge trouble would come for him.

Although Zhao Hai had cut off the pavilion’s benefits, the pavilion was still unaware as to who he was. Their connection to the Underworld was just a low-level transmission formation. And it was impossible to see Zhao Hai through that formation.

But things were different when it came to Lu Wei and the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor. The two sent avatars to the lower realms, so they were able to see Zhao Hai’s appearance. If the two knew about Zhao Hai’s enmity with the Myriad Treasures Pavillion, then it was possible for them to work together with the pavilion to deal with Zhao Hai. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen, therefore, he needed to hunt down Lu Wei and the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor as soon as possible.

While Zhao Hai was pondering about these matters, Laura and the others had already told Margaret about Zhao Hai’s accomplishments in the lower realms. They didn’t only tell Margaret about these matters, they also showed her pictures and recordings taken by the Space.

In addition to Zhao Hai’s accomplishments, Laura and the others also told Margaret about the Space, which without a doubt surprised her.

After the talk, Laura looked at Margaret and said, “Margaret, we can see that you’re interested in Brother Hai. We always encouraged him to pursue you because he needs you. Your identity will allow him to integrate better into the Ashley Family. However, Brother Hai doesn’t want to pursue you for this exact reason. If you didn’t confess to him today, then he would never reveal this place to you. This is because this place is Brother Hai’s roots. He can move unhindered in this world because of this. Do you understand?”

Margaret gave a nod. Then Lizzy added, “It’s also because of the Space’s abilities that Brother Hai wouldn’t easily tell other people about it. Him letting you enter the Space today means that he has already accepted you. But if you really don’t want to share Brother Hai with us, then we hope that you’ll forget everything you heard about this place. Otherwise, Brother Hai wouldn’t be able to have a place in this realm.”

Margaret looked at Laura and the others, then she smiled and said, “I’ve already decided on Zhao Hai, naturally I won’t regret my decision. Zhao Hai not pursuing me because he is thinking about you only told me that he is a person who won’t betray me. With a man like that, I wouldn’t have anything to worry about.”

Upon hearing Margaret, Laura and the others couldn’t help but smile. Then Laura pulled Margaret and giggled as she said, “Then you need to be at your best. Megan, help Margaret with her makeup. We’ll have her share a room with Brother Hai today.”

When Margaret heard Laura, her face couldn’t help but turn red. However, she was faintly smiling as she was taken away by Megan. Meanwhile, Laura called Zhao Hai over, “Brother Hai, come here quick.”

Zhao Hai immediately broke out of his thoughts. Then his body flashed as he entered the Space. Seeing Laura grinning from ear to ear, he couldn’t help but ask, “What happened?”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, then she said, “Brother Hai, Margaret has agreed to marry you. Go get ready quick. Everything’s been taken care of. It’s time for you to go to the nuptial chamber.” Upon hearing Laura, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly as he said, “Margaret just learned about the Space, why is the nuptial chamber already involved?”

Laura pouted and said, “Brother Hai, you’re really stupid. Margaret has already confessed to you, so there’s nothing to worry about. Go get ready.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Why do you need to make a big fuss over this. Alright, I’ll go prepare.” Laura didn’t delay and immediately made Zhao Hai wear formal clothing. Then he had Zhao Hai sit down so that she could handle his hair. It was necessary for Zhao Hai to be in his best attire when he enters the nuptial chambers with Margaret.

Zhao Hai was a man, so he was clueless about how important a wedding was to a woman. This was especially true for men that they loved, they would make sure that it was special. If Zhao Hai was too casual about this, then Margaret would regret it all her life.

Before long, Margaret was sent over by Laura and the others. Zhao Hai was also in his best attire. Then Laura and the others performed a simple chinese wedding for Zhao Hai and Margaret before they pushed the two towards the nuptial chamber.

Seeing Zhao Hai and Margaret entering the nuptial chamber, Laura and the others let out a long breath. After cleaning up, Laura said, “Alright, Margaret’s matter has finally been solved. I believe Brother Hai’s status in the Ashley Family would become more solid. And with Margaret’s help, our identity will slowly be solved.” Lizzy and the others also nodded. To be honest, they weren’t really jealous of Margaret.

Since Zhao Hai already had multiple wives, adding one more wasn’t a problem. After cleaning the place up, everyone proceeded to take a rest.

There was no need to say about Zhao Hai and Margaret’s matter inside the nuptial chamber. The next day, the two of them shared breakfast with Laura and the others before saying goodbye and then leaving the Space.

After coming out of the Space, Margaret turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, although we’ve officially become a couple, I think we should keep it from others in the meantime. Otherwise, we don’t know what kind of things would come up.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Margaret, you’re underestimating the family too much. You came over here but you didn’t return for the night. The Patriarch has surely gotten word of it. Forget it, just stay here.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but get startled, then she quickly said, “What do we do? What if he doesn’t agree?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, there’s no problem. Take a seat while we wait for the Camp Lord and the others to arrive. It seems like they’ve been looking for us the entire night.” Margaret nodded, then she sat down albeit her face was red. Zhao Hai waved his hand, then a pot of tea appeared on the table. This tea wasn’t from the Machine Field, instead it was from the Space. The tea from the Space tastes much better than tea from the Machine Field.

Not long after the two began drinking tea, Desbarres’s group of three arrived. The three didn’t think much after seeing Margaret. She was seen more and more often with Zhao Hai, so they were already used to seeing her.

After the three were asked to sit down, Zhao Hai quickly offered them tea. But this time, the tea wasn’t from the Space, it was already replaced when the three arrived.

Drinking a sip of his tea, Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you need to prepare. We’re leaving for the realm qualifiers.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I don’t have much to prepare. We can go whenever you want.”

Desbarres nodded, then his face turned serious as he said, “Little Hai, this realm qualifiers is very important for the Ashley Family. You need to get good results or else the family would face huge problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I understand. You can rest assured. Camp Lord, the Zhang Family also wanted to block me from entering the realm qualifiers, right?”

Chapter 1152: Ten Great Experts

When Desbarres heard Zhao Hai, he nodded and said, “Correct, the Zhang Family is indeed planning to do that. Since they have spies in the family, they were aware about your abilities. They don’t want you to join the realm qualifiers and then gain benefits for the family. This is because once you show your ability in the competition, the family would no longer worry about having allies. When that time comes, the Zhang Family would have no way of dealing with us. This is also the reason why you should win and gain the best position you can. The better your position, the safer the family would be.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, Camp Lord, I understand.”

Desbarres nodded, then he turned to Margaret and said, “Miss Margaret, will you be coming with us?”

Margaret nodded and said, “Of course I’ll go. We can go anytime, I also don’t have much to pack.”

Desbarres smiled bitterly and said, “Alright, then we’ll be heading to Lofty Demon Island first. The Patriarch wouldn’t be going with us. Instead, Cadjo will be leading our fleet.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go. The Family’s matters are important, we can’t afford to waste time.”

Desbarres nodded, then he brought Margaret and Zhao Hai out of the villa. But as they went out, Desbarres looked at Margaret and noticed something different about her.

Desbarres was an experienced person, therefore, he knew that something happened between Zhao Hai and Margaret between now and last night. With this thought in mind, Desbarres couldn’t help but worry.

Although Thunder had agreed to Zhao Hai and Margaret’s relationship, the two were doing things prematurely. Desbarres wasn’t sure if Thunder would be provoked by this or not.

The group went out of the building and immediately rode a car to Lofty Demon Island. While sitting inside the car, Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “After you came back, the Patriarch immediately warned the Zhang Family. Moreover, the Patriarch dissolved Miss Margaret’s marriage agreement with them. This is literally a slap to the Zhang Family’s face. The Patriarch is afraid that we might meet danger along the way, so he told us to leave as soon as possible.”

When Margaret heard Desbarres, she couldn’t help but stare. Then her face lit up as she asked, “Fat Uncle, did the Patriarch really dissolve my marriage agreement?”

Desbarres nodded with a smile and said, “Of course. I wanted to tell you this yesterday. But because I drank too much, I wasn’t able to. Who knew that you two would reach this point.”

Hearing Desbarres, Margaret knew that he had already found out about Zhao Hai and her. Her face couldn’t help but turn red as she lowered her head in silence. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord, will the Patriarch blame me for this matter?”

Desbarres sighed and said, “At present, there’s no way for the Patriarch to blame you. After all, the family still needs you. Moreover, the Patriarch has already agreed to wed Miss Margaret to you.”

Zhao Hai didn’t worry about this matter. He believed that Thunder should already know about Margaret not returning to her villa last night. Judging by the fact that Thunder didn’t send anyone over last night, it’s highly probable that he wouldn’t send someone today.

The car arrived at Lofty Demon Island while everyone was talking. The island was very huge and also quite lively. But the car didn’t stop and just immediately sped towards the port. Cars and small-sized ships were already waiting there as well as Cadjo and the people from the other Camps. Only the Bone Symbol Camp was missing.

When the car stopped, Desbarres immediately went out of the car. When he saw everyone, he laughed and said, “I apologize for being late. I drank too much yesterday.”

Cadjo stared at Desbarres before turning his head to look at Zhao Hai. Then he smiled and said, “Forget it, I’ll let you be proud this time. Get in quick, the Patriarch said that he wouldn’t see us out. But when everyone heads back victorious, the Patriarch will personally fetch us.”

Everyone nodded and entered the ship with Cadjo. Desbarres went to the other Camp Lords and said, “Everyone, there’s no need to worry about the fellows from the External Hall. I’ll take care of them.”

Dia and the others nodded. They didn’t say anything. They just owed Desbarres and Zhao Hai a huge favor this time, they could no longer act like before.

Desbarres didn’t say anything else as he boarded the ship. Since this ship was just used for transport to the outer space base, the ride wouldn’t take too long. Therefore, Cadjo didn’t assign any rooms to everyone. They were all just standing inside the command hall.

The ship smoothly took off and soon it was passing through the planet’s atmosphere. Cadjo looked at the view outside the ship and said, “The family will send five medium-sized ships this time. Additionally, we’re going to take 10 thousand mechs. This should be enough to ensure our safety. Our goal is the planet at the core of the Machine Field, our realm’s capital. The qualifiers will be held there.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded, then Cadjo continued, “It will take us eight days of full-speed travel to get there from Dark Demon Planet. The time we have left should be sufficient enough. As for any accidents on the road, you won’t need to worry, the family has already taken care of it.”

The ship arrived at the outer space base during Cadjo’s speech. They didn’t stop here as the small ship immediately went towards the family’s medium-sized ships. Not long after everyone had transferred, they took off once more.

The medium-sized ships that they were in were larger than the one used in the previous mission. Not only can this ship store thousands of mechs, it also had smaller emergency ships inside. Moreover, this ship had much stronger firepower.

After assigning everyone their respective rooms, Cadjo called them over to the conference room. Although it was smaller than large-sized ships, this medium-sized ship actually had complete facilities along with several conference rooms.

Everyone was called over to a small conference room. Present inside were Cadjo, Desbarres, Zhao Hai, Margaret, and then the other participants from the other camps.

After everyone had sat down, Cadjo said, “I called you over to tell you about the opponents that you might meet in the qualifiers. These are very powerful people, you need to be careful if you encounter them. Besides Zhao Hai, everyone should have already received information about the participants from the other families.” Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You can use these days to read up on them. It’s fine as long as you get a general idea of their strength.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Then Cadjo continued, “I’m here to tell you about experts that you need to pay special attention to. These people are said to be the strongest participants in the realm qualifiers.”

After he said this, Cadjo moved to the side as the wall behind him turned into a display monitor. On the monitor was the image of a person, a Mage. Displayed on his side were pale blue formations. His hair was also pale blue. He was quite handsome with his faintly smiling face. One would feel intimate while looking at him

On the person’s side was an introduction. Zhao Hai read the description: Name: Streep. Nickname: Saint of Ice. Background: Water Temple. Ascendance: Four Years. Strength: Level 4 Mage. Conclusion: Extremely dangerous. Some reports state that he fought with a small battleship and ended up destroying it.

Then there were even more detailed introductions. Zhao Hai looked at it and understood that Streep was truly strong. He managed to reach level 4 just four years after ascending. And from the time he ascended up to the present, he had already experienced hundreds of battles and suffered no defeat.

After the introduction, Streep’s fighting scenes were seen. These video clips were very short, some were even fuzzy. One of these fuzzy scenes seems to show an arena, most likely from the local qualifiers. From the video, one could see Streep cast ten-layer formations with no problem. And he could also cast 50-layer formations in a short time. One could see that his spiritual force was strong from this point.

With Zhao Hai as an exception, all other participants had unattractive expressions as they looked at the video. When they saw that 10-layer formations were easily being sent out, they thought that it was because of a magic staff. However, the person on the video didn’t actually use one. This ability was too formidable.

They knew that only Zhao Hai could face Streep. It was impossible for them to fight these kinds of people.

Although the equipment that the family provided them were the best there was, the other participants would be the same as them. Since everyone deemed the competition as a very important matter, people like Streep would also have top-graded equipment.

At this time, the image on the monitor changed. When he saw the person depicted on the monitor, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It was because this person looked so strong, it also seems like he wasn’t a human being, more like a giant. However, his height was somewhat shorter than most giants.

The man was about two and a half meters tall. He was bald and had skin akin to molten copper. And with his well-developed muscles, the man looked like an ancient giant that came out of the earth.

He was currently wearing armor that covered his whole body, boosting his formidable image even more. However, the most noticeable aspect of this person were the two sledgehammers on his side. They were quite large, looking almost impossible to wield.

One must know that spatial equipment weren’t uncommon in the Machine Field. It was a general practice for experts, even some normal people, to have spatial equipment on them. And whether one was a Mage or a Warrior, those of notable ability would be bestowed at least a spatial item by their families. Because of this, it was impossible for this burly person to not have any spatial equipment on him. Nevertheless, he was still carrying his impossibly huge sledgehammers on his side.

Zhao Hai looked at the person’s information and found out that he was named Xiong Li, nicknamed Violent Bear. He was a warrior from the Wu Family that had ascended three years ago. He was already a level 4 Warrior and was known for the powerful sword qi that he could send from his hammers. He was also physically and defensively strong judging by his copper-like skin. After making his debut, he was already undefeated in a thousand battles.

Zhao Hai knew that the Wu Family was a famous Warrior Clan and was a huge influence in the Warrior Association. Moreover, people from the Wu Family were famed for their strength. Xiong Li ascending in the Wu Family was his absolute luck.

The third expert was an assassin named Lone Wolf Yan Zhenshan. He wore black clothes to cover his dark and thin body. His facial features were ordinary, but his eyes had a sharp and cold look. He was also at level 4. His hand techniques were very formidable. Without using any swords, he was able to one-shot his enemies. He was merciless. In the four years since he ascended, he already assassinated 1000 people, and all of them died, nobody survived.

The Tian Family where Yan Zhenshan came from was quite a special existence. Unlike the Ashley Family or the Wu Family that were famous for being Mages or Warriors respectively, the Tian Family dabbled in both practices. However, their Mages were always Dark Mages while their Warriors were always Assassins.

But even with their special practice, the Tian Family was a member of the Dark Church. This was because the people from the Warrior Association didn’t like them, they always thought that they weren’t a Warrior Family. Because of this, the Tian Family joined the Church Alliance becoming one of the forces that the Alliance had against the Warrior Association.

The fourth expert was named Swift Wind and Rain Lei Xiaotian. He’s a Wind and Water element Mage from the Wind God  Palace’s Lei Family. He wasn’t surnamed Lei initially, but after he ascended and demonstrated his innate skills, the Lei Family decided to take him in and bestow him the surname Lei. This man was a level 4 Mage. And because he was a double-element Mage, his strength was quite formidable. In his three and a half years since ascending, he was able to fight more than 100 battles undefeated.

The fifth Expert was Divine Fire Dragon Sword Dongfang Yu. This man ascended three years ago and joined a family from the Flame Dojo of the Warrior Association. He’s a level 4 Warrior with a fire element sword technique named Fire Dragon Sword. He became a force to be reckoned with in the Dongfang Family. All of his 300 missions in the family were all completed in a perfect manner. He was a person who was serious in his duties.

The sixth expert was Strong Wind Li Kuangren. He wasn’t very tall but his muscles were quite developed. He wields a two-handed ax and practices the Strong Wind Technique. He’s a level 4 Warrior from the Song Family.

The seventh expert was named Meteor Zhu Chen. This man was from the Earth Temple and had ascended three years ago. His handle on earth magic was superb. He could use 10-layer formations as comfortably as drinking water. Moreover, he claimed that he was the strongest level 4 Mage in the realm.

The eighth expert was Army Breaker Lu Dingtian. He’s a level 4 Warrior from the Warrior Association’s Dong Family. With his one-handed axe, it was said that he managed to hold off against a 1000-man army.

The ninth expert was Fire Saint Sun Fei. Unexpectedly, this person was from the Fire Temple’s Zhang Family who had an enmity with Zhao Hai. He ascended four years ago and was also a level 4 Mage of the fire element. He was known to use 10-layer formations easily.

The last expert was Golden Egg Zhang Qinghe. This person had just ascended three years ago. There were no metal element ability users back in his lower realm. However, after he ascended and taken in by the Divine Palace of Metal’s Rhea Family, his talent in metal-element formations blossomed. It took him three years to reach level 4. And with his talent in metal-element formations, both his attack and defense were beyond formidable. He’s someone whose strength couldn’t be underestimated!

Chapter 1153: Quicksand Starfield

TN: Looked into LNMTL and Piaotian5 to see where the first half of the chapter went. However, both were replaced by a section from another random novel. However, the context should still be found in the next chapters. These things happen occassionally but this is the first time where a part of the chapter actually went missing. Usually, the chapter would just be pushed down.

Zhao Hai also heard about Quicksand Starfield, however, he didn’t worry about it. He looked at Cadjo and said, “General Manager, do we know what kind of ship they are using?”

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai in confusion, he doesn’t know why Zhao Hai was asking this. But he still answered, “About 20 medium-sized warships. Although their level is lower than the ones we have, 20 is still enough to cause us serious damage.”

Zhao Hai replied, “If we wipe them out in the Quicksand Starfield, what consequences would we face?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Cadjo couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “And how could we do that? Although our five battleships are more advanced compared to theirs, they have the numbers. Perhaps we might be able to survive, but wiping them all out is impossible.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Naturally, it would be impossible if we only depend on the family’s five ships. But if you add me, then it’s possible.”

Everyone in the room stared. Mages couldn’t fight against a fleet, this was a well-known fact in the Machine Field. But now, Zhao Hai actually wanted to fight against the enemy’s battleship fleet? This was completely out of everyone’s expectations.

After Desbarres recovered from his shock, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Are you confident?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am. If they come, then they would not be able to return. Perhaps we might even seize a couple of ships for ourselves.”

Desbarres looked at Cadjo. Naturally, Cadjo also thought about Liquid Silver. He doesn’t oppose this idea, but he still hesitated before he asked, “Do you need any help from the ships?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Actually, our fleet doesn’t need to face the enemy fleet. Our ships can form an encirclement around their ships. After that, we will disrupt their communication systems. This way, even if they can still talk to each other, they wouldn’t be able to send a message back to their family. Can the General Manager do this?”

Cadjo blankly looked at Zhao Hai, then he said, “It wouldn’t be difficult, however, it seems like you want to face all of their ships alone? Little Hai, don’t joke. The other side has 20 medium-sized battleships.”

Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, “Even if they have a lot of ships, I’m only a single person. If they cannot hit me, then what use do their numbers have?”

Cadjo couldn’t help but bod. In fact, one person destroying a battleship fleet wasn’t unheard of in the World of Cultivation. However, there wasn’t a case where someone from the Machine Field was able to do so.

Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and Desbarres and said, “General Manager, Camp Lord, I’d like to talk to you two alone. What I’m about to say is quite important.”

When Cadjo and Desbarres heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but pause. Then they nodded before commanding everyone to leave. Only the three of them and Margaret were left in the small conference room.

Once the others had retreated, Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what do you need to say?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s good news this time. General Manager, Camp Lord, you should already be clear about my relationship with Margaret. Although Margaret and the Patriarch’s relationship isn’t good, they are still father and daughter in the end. Moreover, Margaret is already closely tied to the Ashley Family. Although I wouldn’t dare to insert myself in the Ashley Family’s matter, now that Margaret has become someone from my side, I need to do something.”

Cadjo and Desbarres were intently listening to Zhao Hai, they were waiting for what he has to say next. Zhao Hai continued, “In the past few days, Margaret and I have been analyzing the refinement method used on Liquid Silver. And after we had a glimpse of the method, we were able to discover something. Although we can’t make something as strong as Liquid Silver, we can still make inferior replicas of it. If we can successfully achieve it, then this would be an absolutely good news to the family.”

Cadjo and Desbarres were immediately shaken. They never expected a windfall such as this to appear. It has been a dream for many generations in the Machine Field to refine Liquid Silver. However, even with how many materials and methods were used, none were able to succeed. And even if the Machine Field was becoming much more advanced compared to the past, this matter was still left unaccomplished. The many failures caused people to be disinterested in this matter. It was precisely because of this that Liquid Silver has been seen as a waste in the Machine Field. People only regarded it as an antique with a significant history behind it. They never did look at it as a weapon.

Chapter 1154: A Good Plan

After some time, Cadjo and Desbarres sobered up. Then their eyes lit up. Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you telling the truth? You really can make replicas of Liquid Silver?”

One couldn’t blame Cadjo for his excitement. Zhao Hai wasn’t from the World of Cultivation so he might not know that replicas were almost always easier to use than the original copies.

It was widely known that the Cultivation Realm was the most powerful realm in the World of Cultivation. Almost all huge sects and factions in the Cultivation realm had incomparably powerful magical artifacts; each one capable of turning mountains to seas. However, such artifacts couldn’t be easily taken out.

But in addition to these powerful artifacts, these huge powers also had replicas of said artifacts. These replicas were made by these powers themselves. But even if they were just replicas, one shouldn’t underestimate their might. The power held by these influences wasn’t unrelated to the quality of their artifact replicas. Because of this, there was a huge market for artifact replicas in the Cultivation Realm.

Thinking that the Machine Field would have these replicas thanks to Liquid Silver, it was no wonder that Cadjo became excited.

Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and nodded as he said, “Yes, we can certainly produce replicas. Little Silver has already chosen me as its owner. It has my spiritual imprint, allowing me to study it better. If I hand Liquid Silver over to the family, then it would only be useless. As long as I have the time, I reckon I’ll be able to find out the materials used to make it. As for the refining method, it would take a while. But when the time comes, I’ll have to ask the family to provide me the materials for refinement.”

Cadjo happily replied, “There’s no problem with that. As long as you can make replicas of Liquid Silver, then the family will give you anything you want.”

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why didn’t you reveal this before?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he replied, “Camp Lord, the time just wasn’t right. If Margaret couldn’t become mine, then what benefit would I have if I reveal it? If I did, then I’m afraid I wouldn’t be able to guarantee my freedom.”

When Desbarres heard Zhao Hai and thought about Thunder’s temperament, he couldn’t help but sigh and stayed silent. Zhao Hai looked at Desbarres and said, “Camp Lord, I’m aware of how well you treated me, and it has been engraved deep inside my heart. However, Liquid Silver already belongs to me. And no price can make me hand it over. If the Patriarch wants to take liquid silver away because of its value, then I would have no other choice than to leave the Ashley Family. Of course, I wouldn’t preemptively do this. After all, I already have a deep relationship with the camp. Nevertheless,  I wouldn’t just recklessly reveal the matter of the replica. But now that Margaret has become my woman, I’m already a member of the Ashley Family. Because of this, I have already placed the family’s benefits inside my mind. Therefore, I decided to reveal this matter. I’ll have to ask the General Manager and the Camp Lord for forgiveness.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “This matter has already passed. Little Hai, you don’t need to worry too much about the family. Also, when the time comes, don’t forget to call me uncle.”

Cadjo was indeed worthy of being a General Manager. He knew when to let things go. Naturally, people in the family who had the power to forgive numbered only a few.

When Margaret heard Cadjo, she couldn’t help but feel embarrassed. She adorably pouted and said, “Uncle, you’re teasing me.”

Cadjo laughed and said, “This little girl. You actually knew about these matters but decided to hide it from me. Hai, it seems like there are no good women left in this world.”

Margaret turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai didn’t tell me that it was Liquid Silver. He just told me that it was a special metal and he needed my help to study it.”

Zhao Hai and Margaret reached a tacit agreement about what to say about this matter. But since Laura already told Margaret about the Space, she naturally knew about Liquid Silver. And because Laura and the others didn’t hide anything from her, Margaret knew that Zhao Hai was deliberately lying. But in order to not expose the identity of the Space, Margaret decided to help Zhao Hai with his lie.

Cadjo teased Margaret several times more. Then after some time, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Are you confident in dealing with the enemy fleet?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I was able to return from the Rainbow Meteorite Field with more than 1000 people. Taking care of a fleet wouldn’t be any harder. Since we don’t want the Zhang Family to know that their fleet has been destroyed, I’ll have to ask the General Manager to disrupt their communications. We cannot let the Zhang Family know about this information. If a war were to happen before the end of the Six Realm Beginner competition, then the Ashley Family would suffer.”

Cadjo has been a General Manager for the Ashley Family for decades. He has seen a lot of things. Therefore, he understood what Zhao Hai meant. He immediately nodded and said, “Little Hai, you can rest assured that information about this wouldn’t be sent over. All of us here are core members of the family, so there’s no need to worry about loyalty. You just need to put your mind into fighting. Hurting the Zhang Family would make us expel some bad air.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “General Manager, you should send a message back to the family. Have them go to Quicksand Starfield in order to take the captured battleships.”

Cadjo laughed and said, “Alright, I’ll go send a message. You go rest.”

However, Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I can’t rest now. I still need to look at the general situation. General Manager, Camp Lord, I’ll be heading out first.” Then after he said that, Zhao Hai vanished from the ship.

When Cadjo saw Zhao Hai disappearing in a flash, he couldn’t help but turn to Margaret.

Margaret just smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai has left. Uncle, you forgot that Brother Hai can use the space element. If he wanted to leave the ship, then he wouldn’t need to open any doors.”

Cadjo stared, then he understood that Zhao Hai was showing him his capabilities. Moreover, Cadjo knew that although Zhao Hai said that he got help from Margaret to study Liquid Silver, Liquid Silver was complex enough that Margaret wouldn’t be able to give much help. And as for Margaret being his woman, that was just a reason that Zhao Hai thought up.

Cadjo was convinced that Zhao Hai not telling the family about Liquid Silver’s replicas was in order to leave a backdoor for himself. Everyone knew that Desbarres has been good to Zhao Hai. And it seems like Zhao Hai took the matters of heart very seriously. Therefore, Zhao Hai shouldn’t have any reason to betray the family.

Moreover, if the Ashley Family did decide to deal with Zhao Hai, it wouldn’t be very easy to do so. Zhao Hai had his spatial abilities. With the help of Liquid Silver, he was even able to send more than 1000 people to Dark Demon Planet from the Rainbow Meteorite Field. Such capability couldn’t be looked down upon. If Zhao Hai really wanted to leave, then nobody would be able to stop him.

Zhao Hai using his spatial ability in front of Cadjo might be him showing that nobody can stop him if he really decided to leave. And if the family decided to take action against him, then they wouldn’t just gain nothing, they would also have a formidable enemy. Such a plan wasn’t worth it, so the family might as well treat Zhao Hai well.

Cadjo sighed at Zhao Hai ‘s thorough plan. Although he was still weak compared to the Ashley Family’s overall strength, Zhao Hai still had cards he could play, allowing him to stand at an equal position with the family. At this point, it wouldn’t be wise for the Ashley Family to make a move on him.

Cadjo turned to Margaret and said, “Little Margaret, go take a rest. I’ll send the message back to the family. I reckon it wouldn’t be long before we need them to take the captured ships away.”

Margaret nodded before turning around and leaving. Her face had no signs of worry. After experiencing the marvels of the Space, Margaret was already confident in Zhao Hai’s survival.

Once Margaret had left the room, Cadjo sighed as he turned to Desbarres and said, “Fatty Des, this Zhao Hai is quite the character. I only hope that he can be tied down by Miss Margaret. This way, the family will gain a lot.”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “I believe that as long as the family doesn’t make a move against him, then Zhao Hai will not betray the family. Even if he gets separated from the family in the future, he will still look after the family because of his relationship with Margaret. Once he becomes an expert of the realm, then the family can sleep without worries.”

Cadjo looked at Desbarres and smiled, “You fatty, you really think so? You’re that confident in Zhao Hai?”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Do you think someone who completed Liquid Silver is a normal person? Maybe the whole Machine Field wouldn’t be enough to contain Zhao Hai.” Cadjo didn’t say anything more about the topic. This was because he was beginning to believe Desbarres’s words.

When Margaret entered her room, a spatial rift suddenly appeared in front of her. Margaret stared for a moment before she entered the rift. Once she was on the other side, she saw Zhao Hai along with Laura and the others.

Margaret stared, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, didn’t you go scout? Why are you here?”

Laura looked at Margaret’s expression and smiled, “Silly girl. We have the Space, so why does Brother Hai need to scout himself? Unless it is a special area, Brother Hai doesn’t need to head out. Alright, let’s go to the living room to have some fun.”

Before long, Margaret entered the living room. Upon entering, Margaret noticed that the monitor already had some images displayed on it. There wasn’t much to look at it since it was a view of outer space. But it wasn’t just stationary space, the image seemed to be moving fast. Margaret knew that this wasn’t the space moving, but something was moving quickly through it.

Then Margaret was attracted to an area close to the monitor. Laura and the others were playing with Liquid Silver replicas to control flying needles outside.

Although Zhao Hai hadn’t gone to the Quicksand Starfield before, there was already a star map saved inside the Space. This star map was something that was publicly distributed in the Machine Field. Although the star map had yet to be incorporated into the Space, Zhao Hai and the others can still use it as an ordinary map.

Chapter 1155: Fig Leaf

Three days later, Zhao Hai returned to the ship. But what made Cadjo and Desbarres wonder was Margaret being always absent at the same time Zhao Hai was gone. She would make people deliver food to her room and would just stay inside.

When Zhao Hai returned to the command hall, Margaret was also with him. Seeing that Zhao Hai had come back, Cadjo and Desbarres quickly welcomed him. Zhao Hai went to the command hall’s main computer and opened the Quicksand Starfield’s map and said, “The Zhang Family hid in these spots. They made sure that they were hidden well. Moreover, their ships don’t emit any electromagnetic signals, making it hard to detect them. If we weren’t prepared, then we might get too relaxed and fall for their sneak attack.”

Cadjo didn’t become an expert by doing nothing. He clearly knew that the Zhang Family’s positioning was the optimal setup that they could do. It seems like the Zhang Family really wanted to destroy them.

Cadjo nodded and said, “So what do you need us to do next?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We’ll deviate from our original route. Although we may still encounter the Zhang Family, I will deal with them, there’s no need to worry. The General Manager just needs to encircle these ships and interfere with their communication systems.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “That’s not a problem. So when do we make our move?”

Zhao Hai replied, “We’ll just go along our usual time frame. After we arrive at the destination, then you do what you need to do. The battle will start immediately. Alright, then I’ll start getting busy.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure vanished from the ship.

Cadjo looked at Desbarres and smiled bitterly as he said, “This kid, he’s already giving us commands. Alright, let’s start getting busy as well.” Then he turned to Margaret and said, “Little Margaret, what have you been doing these days? Why did you decide to head out of your room now?”

Margaret yawned and said, “I came out because I’m starting to get bored. I don’t have much to do unlike you old men. I just enjoyed playing games inside my room. Alright then, Uncles, I’m taking my leave.” Then she turned around and left Cadjo and Desbarres puzzled.

Desbarres quickly stopped Margaret and said, “Little Margaret, aren’t you worried about Zhao Hai? He’s going to face a fleet.”

Margaret turned towards Desbarres and just smiled as she said, “I’m not worried. There’s nobody in this world that can kill Brother Hai.” Then she waved her hand and returned to her room.

Cadjo and Desbarres looked at Margaret, speechless. They didn’t expect Margaret to be this confident in Zhao Hai. What they didn’t know was that Margaret spent the last days inside the Space with Zhao Hai. The two had been together all this time.

Zhao Hai went back to the Space with Margaret following behind soon. When he entered the Space, he immediately looked at the huge monitor. This time, everyone wasn’t planning on playing any games, they were planning the attack on the Zhang Family’s fleet.

The Zhang Family’s fleet was now fully being monitored. Zhao Hai even stationed some of the silver needles around the ships. In this case, there’s no way for the fleet to escape.

The only thing left for them to do was to begin to take action. Lizzy looked at the map and said, “The Zhang Family’s fleet has 20 ships and about 40 thousand Mechs. This isn’t a small number. Dealing with them wouldn’t be easy. I think we should use the Undead to assault them. Brother Hai, you’ll use Liquid Silver to break their shields so that we can lead the Undead to attack them in close proximity. We’ll destroy them in one go.”

Zhao Hai agreed to the plan. The Zhang Family didn’t bring any Mages or Warriors with their fleet. As long as Zhao Hai breaks their shields, the Undead could overwhelm them. When the time comes, the ships would just be sitting ducks waiting for slaughter.

Zhao Hai also recently discovered that the Liquid Silver’s needles couldn’t touch the other ships if their shields were up. Because of this, he wasn’t able to see the situation inside each ship. It was only once the shields were down that the needles could get in close and invade.

Because they were staging an ambush, the Zhang Family’s ships had been passive in the past few days. They would only erect their shields if meteorites came close. This situation provided Zhao Hai opportunities to make some experiments.

Zhao Hai knew that he would encounter more battleships in the future. Therefore, he needed some time to understand them more. This way, he would know their strengths and weaknesses. And his recent results came out very good.

Actually, when Zhao Hai discovered that he could send Undead into the battleships, he didn’t immediately think about handing the ships over to the Ashley Family.

But soon, Zhao Hai realized that the more valuable aspects of warships were its operators. It wasn’t easy to train people that can run a battleship. Once he defeated the Zhang Family’s fleet, not only could he get their battleships, he would also gain Undead operators that could help him run the ship.

In the end, Zhao Hai decided to give the ships to the Ashley Family. However, the soldiers and operators inside would have to be taken away.

Megan looked at the ships and said, “We need to keep everyone in the ships inside. It would be a problem if the Mechs headed out.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “If those Mechs manage to escape, I’ll personally go deal with them. The Space doesn’t have enough materials to make a lot of Liquid Silver replicas, we’re quite lacking in that aspect. The Space’s army is still not enough to contend against a Mech army. I have to deal with the Mechs myself. But as long as we take control of the battleships and turn the operators into Undead, we’ll be able to deal with those Mechs. There’s no need to worry much about it.”

Megan and the others nodded. Then they discussed other aspects of the attack. Actually, what was left to discuss was very simple. They were only waiting for the right time to make an attack.

After the discussion, Laura turned to Margaret and said, “Margaret, do you want to lead a team?”

When Margaret heard Laura, she couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then she felt cold. She just heard them talk about murder as though it was a game. She wasn’t used to it.

When Laura saw Margaret’s expression, she immediately knew what she was thinking. Laura smiled and said, “It’s fine. I can’t even count the number of people Brother Hai killed since his debut. However, all of these people are his enemies. Enemies needed to be destroyed or else they will come after us in the future.”

Margaret nodded. She practically grew up in the greenhouse, so she was quite pure. However, she was already prepared for these events when she decided to follow Zhao Hai. This was the real Zhao Hai, and she must adapt in order to follow him.

It can be said that Margaret was a complete idealist in the past. She always lived inside a very safe environment. The most cruel and ruthless situation that she experienced were internal family issues.

But after following Zhao Hai in the past few days, Margaret began to see the true face of the Machine Field. Although the Machine Field was dominated by the three major forces, the smaller influences were bearing grudges against each other and were constantly fighting. One could only kill their enemy if they wanted to improve themselves.

Because of this thought, Margaret agreed to commanding a team of Undead. Since she already accepted Zhao Hai, then she would need to help.

Once they were done with their discussions, Laura changed the monitor’s display to the Quicksand Starfield. There were a few green dots seen on the map.

Besides these green dots, there were also red dots seen. These red dots were the Zhang Family’s fleet. Zhao Hai saw this situation and said, “Calculate when the General Manager will arrive at the area.”

Laura nodded and said, “There’s no need to worry about that. It would take a day for the General Manager and the others to enter the area, and another four hours before arriving at the predetermined place. Then it would take another two hours before they could suppress the electronic communications. When the time comes, we can make our move. Brother Hai, you should take a rest. After all, when the time comes you will need to personally act.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “You take a rest as well. We can leave this area to Cai’er. We don’t want you to be exhausted when the battle begins.” Laura smiled and said, “Rest assured, we will do well.” Zhao Hai nodded before turning around and entering his room.

Cadjo and Desbarres didn’t share the same relaxed mindset. They stayed inside the command hall all the time. They didn’t even think about asking for reinforcements from the family in order to help Zhao Hai. They believed that once the family makes a move, the Zhang Family would notice it. And when that time comes, the Zhang Family would also send their own troops, triggering an open war between the two; which was very bad for the Ashley Family.

The Zhang Family were doing everything they can in order to prevent Zhao Hai from participating in the competition. With the realm qualifiers happening in a few days, Cadjo’s fleet couldn’t afford to be delayed.

Since Zhao Hai was confident enough to eliminate the enemy fleet, what they needed to do now was to send a message back to the family asking for personnel to man the soon to be captured ships. This would allow them to rush to the Machine Field’s capital as soon as possible.

At this point, the Zhang Family and the Ashley Family’s contradictions were beginning to reveal itself. Only a piece of fig leaf was keeping everything from blowing up. However, none of the two sides wanted to remove this fig leaf. Once this barrier was punctured, things wouldn’t bode well for both groups.

And with this fig leaf, it was impossible for the two sides to fight on a large scale. Since they couldn’t fight with huge numbers, they could only resort to small-scale conflicts like this fight between a 20-ship fleet and a 5-ship fleet. The number of ships involved wasn’t large and none of them sent large-sized ships.

Most importantly, both sides were still official allies. Even if they knew that the other party was responsible for a small conflict, they would still deliberately ignore it. They would take it as a pirate vs army situation. Since battles between those two sides were common, nobody would be able to say anything.

Actually, from what Zhao Hai can see, the current farce was disadvantageous to both families. They need to wait until after the Beginner Competition ends, then they could have a final showdown.

The ten great experts gave the people from the Machine Field hope. Therefore, high-level figures of the Machine Field regarded this competition as crucial. If the two families dared to disturb this event, then the three major powers would certainly take action.

Even if the Ashley Family and the Zhang Family held great power and influence, they would still suffer if they offended the three major powers. After all, the rulers of the Machine Field were still the big three.

With this thought in mind, Cadjo and Desbarres only sent for personnel to operate the captured ships. They didn’t ask for military reinforcements since they already decided to believe in Zhao Hai.

They believed that Zhao Hai’s Liquid Silver was something that the gods had bestowed to the Machine Field. Therefore, they were very confident in Liquid Silver.

The two stared at the computer screen for a while. Then Cadjo turned to Desbarres and said, “Fatty Des, what do we do if Little Hai isn’t able to take control of those ships? When the time comes, we would have to meet head-on.”

Desbarres coldly snorted and said, “If we need to fight, then we would do it. We’re not afraid of fighting head on. Also, if Little Hai didn’t propose this action, wouldn’t we still need to fight them? We don’t have much choice. We need to believe in Little Hai.”

Cadjo sighed and said, “It seems like we can only proceed like this. Let’s hope that Little Hai succeeds. If he does, then his ability is already enough to reach the top ten in the 6 Realm Beginner Competition.”

Desbarres looked at Cadjo and said, “Don’t underestimate Little Hai’s strength. Do you think  beginners from the other realms are able to defeat 20 medium-sized battleships on their own? If Little Hai succeeds, then he might as well snatch the top position.”

Cadjo looked at Desbarres and said, “Fatty Des, don’t boast too much. We’re talking about the Six Realm Beginner Competition.”

Desbarres rolled his eyes and said, “I know what I said. Or do you want to bet on it?”

Cadjo looked at Desbarres’s expression, then he waved his hand and said, “I wouldn’t dare bet against you. I’m not dumb enough to jump into a pit you dug.” When he heard this, Desbarres couldn’t help but laugh.

Chapter 1156: Done

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the Ashley Family’s fleet through the monitor. They had already arrived at the designated area. However, they were an hour later than what Zhao Hai expected.

Zhao Hai knew that this was because Cadjo and the others were still reluctant about his capabilities. Nevertheless, he didn’t say anything nor go see Cadjo. What he needs to do now was to maintain his mysterious capabilities, making Cadjo and the others feel that he was an unreadable character.

Maintaining one’s mystery can save you a lot of trouble sometimes. Others would hesitate to take action against you if they had yet to grasp your capabilities.

Zhao Hai was doing this exact thing. He would help the Ashley Family with their matters but he wouldn’t reveal everything to them. Besides his family, he wouldn’t easily trust anybody else.

Upon seeing Cadjo and the others entering the predetermined area, Zhao Hai shifted his attention towards the Zhang Family’s fleet. Because the Zhang Family’s fleet had their communications withdrawn, they weren’t able to detect the Ashley Family’s fleet. They could only rely on the sentries they sent outside for information. However, these sentries had already been dealt with by Zhao Hai. Because of this, the Zhang Family fleet wasn’t in any state to fight, which gave Zhao Hai the best opportunity to attack.

Zhao Hai saw that Cadjo was almost prepared to start. However, he wouldn’t immediately take action. He would wait until Cadjo and the others began to suppress the enemy’s electronic communications.

You ask why Zhao Hai knew that Cadjo’s fleet was prepared to take action? Zhao Hai had been inside Cadjo’s ship for a long time. At this point, he knew how many cockroaches were inside the ship and where they were.

When Cadjo and the others began suppressing the enemy’s communication system, Zhao Hai immediately began to move. In a flash, large quantities of Undead appeared inside the Zhang Family’s ships. However, these Undead weren’t controlled by Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai came out of the Space and arrived in front of the Zhang Family fleet.

Just like what Zhao Hai expected, the ship operators couldn’t resist the onslaught of the Undead. On the other hand, the mech soldiers were still on standby when the Undead attacked. A lot of them engaged in melee combat with the Undead. Some of these soldiers died while some were able to ride their Mechs and exit the ship.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at these Mechs. Mechs pilots were all elite soldiers. If these people didn’t have Mechs, then their strengths would be worse than Mages and Warriors. But as long as they were inside their machines, they would then be able to fight groups of Mages and Warriors. These people started their training earlier than Mages and Warriors. Among the major influences, their status was higher compared to Mages and Warriors of their level.

Being able to exit the ships in a short period of time was a testament to these Mech pilot’s capabilities.

Now that the battleships were being overrun by Undead, the tall Mechs would be inconvenienced to fight inside. Moreover, it seems like they have guessed that the other battleships were also under attack. Because of this, they ran out of their ships to either escape further into the starfield or regroup with the Mechs from the other ships. It can be said that they made the correct choice.

They were truly elite soldiers. However, it was a pity that they were against Zhao Hai. And there was no chance for Zhao Hai to be polite to them.

The Mechs were still flustered from the surprise attack. And with Zhao Hai killing them one by one, the panic among the pilots was increasing.

But just before the Mechs were about to find their footing, they suddenly saw their ships starting to open fire. This collapsed the Mech army. They were now aware that there was no way for them to survive this ordeal.

Even if they were able to realize this, the thought came too late. The battle was over very quickly. And just like Zhao Hai expected, the Zhang Family fleet tried to report the situation to the family. But with Cadjo’s suppression, their last hope was destroyed.

Twenty battleships were defeated just like that. The battle was extraordinarily simple. In less than five hours, all ships were captured and the Mechs were destroyed. Besides the ships and Mech fragments, not much else was left.

Bloodstains were the only things left inside the ships. Not a single living person nor dead corpse was seen. Meanwhile, the ships and the unmanned Mechs were left in fairly perfect condition.

After Zhao Hai swept the battlefield, he glanced at the battleships before returning to the Space. At this time, Laura and the others had already finished their work.

Seeing Zhao Hai return, Laura immediately said, “Brother Hai, are we done?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Margaret and said, “Margaret, we should head back.” Margaret’s expression wasn’t good. She just commanded a team of Undead to slaughter the people inside a ship. Although she was looking at the situation through a monitor, her face was still quite pale.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret, then he softly comforted, “It’s fine, Margaret. Don’t forget that they are enemies.” Margaret nodded.

Zhao Hai couldn’t bear to see her pale expression, so he immediately changed to another topic, “Right, Margaret, how powerful is the jammer that you made? Is it strong enough to stop the flight recorders inside the battleships?”

Flight recorders were machines used to record what was happening in the ship during an emergency. This machine was connected to the main computer of the ship but was set up independently. It was contained inside a high-strength alloy which cannot be easily destroyed. Sometimes, even if a battleship was destroyed, these flight recorders would still work with no problems.

Although flight recorders and the main computer were connected, flight recorders were independent from the main computer. As long as unauthorized people entered the ship, the flight recorder would immediately start recording everything that happened on the ship.

Zhao Hai knew about these things before he began his attack. This was also where he had some problems. Whether it be the Ashley Family or the Zhang Family, both of them would be able to use these flight recorders to look into what happened, which was very bad for Zhao Hai.

However, this issue was actually solved by Margaret. Besides being a Mage, she was also interested in magic formations inside electronics.

In fact, in the Machine Field, Mages and electronic products have an inseparable relationship. The technology here was different than on Earth. Earth electronics were generally made with a combination of mechanical and electrical engineering. But in the Machine Field, electronics had magic formations mixed in them. Each electronic product in the Machine Field had some sort of magic formation inside. And there was no need to say about the compositions of battleships and Mechs.

The magic formations inside these Mechs and electronic products weren’t just ordinary formations. They were specifically designed for electronics. The main function of these formations were to assist, not to fight. Because of this, Mages wouldn’t normally dabble to deep into these formations. In the Machine Field, there were only a few Mages in each family who researched these formations. The lack of any offensive and defensive capabilities of these formations made most Mages ignore it.

Even Zhao Hai ignored these formations when he started learning Magic Theory. Only when he took note about flight recorders did these formations enter his eyes. If this matter wasn’t solved, then there was a risk that his secrets would be revealed.

But at the right moment, Margaret actually offered some help. She made a type of jammer for Zhao Hai to use. The range of this jammer wasn’t huge, but its power was quite large. As long as a jammer was inside a ship, then the flight recorder would be as functional as space junk.

It was through this matter that Zhao Hai began to look into the significance of supporting formations. And after looking into it, he found out that these supporting formations were able to increase the offensive and defensive strength of formation sets.

Zhao Hai asked the question in order to distract Margaret. And he succeeded. Margaret quickly replied, “Brother Hai can rest assured. There won’t be any problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Margaret and said, “That’s good. Now, my strength wouldn’t be exposed. Let’s head out. After you return to the Space, you can study these formations. They might provide great use for us.”

Margaret’s thoughts immediately shifted to these formations. Her face turned for the better as she nodded repeatedly. Seeing her recover, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. Margaret was shaping up to become like Karen and the others.

After sending Margaret back to her room, Zhao Hai also teleported inside Cadjo’s ship. Desbarres and Cadjo were eagerly looking at the direction of the Zhang Family’s fleet. They want to see when Zhao Hai’s fight would begin. However, nothing happened in the distant space. There weren’t any lights nor sounds being captured by the ship. This caused them to be puzzled.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly appeared in front of them. Seeing Zhao Hai come back Cadjo quickly asked, “Little Hai, how is it? Do we need to ask for help from the family? If so, then I’ll immediately send a message. However, we cannot stay here for long. We need to rush towards the capital.” Cadjo thought that Zhao Hai had yet to engage the Zhang Family. Therefore, he said these words.

Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and smiled faintly as he said, “General Manager, we can leave. I’ve already dealt with the Zhang Family’s fleet. The family can come and collect the ships.”

Cadjo and Desbarres stared. They looked at each other and saw the doubt in each other’s eyes. Twenty battleships were dealt with just like that? How is that possible?

Chapter 1157: Everpresent Ancient Sand

Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and Desbarres’s expressions, then he smiled and said, “General Manager, Camp Lord, you can rest assured. I’ve already taken care of it. If you want, we can go and see the situation. In any case, confirming it wouldn’t take too long.”

Naturally, Cadjo and Desbarres agreed to visit the site. They directed their fleet to where the Zhang Family’s ships were. And as soon as they arrived, everyone was dumbfounded. Besides a few Mech fragments in Space, everything else in the fleet was completely preserved. It looked like they didn’t receive even a point of damage.

If not for the absence of shields as well as incoming attacks, they might have thought that the Zhang Family were still manning the ships.

Cadjo and Desbarres turned to Zhao Hai with completely confused expressions. Zhao Hai just smiled at them and said, “Camp Lord, General Manager, do we head inside a ship to take a look?”

The two couldn’t help but look at each other. At this time, Margaret, who had already entered the room, smiled and said, “Alright. Let’s go and take a look. I want to see how different the Zhang Family’s ships are compared to ours.”

Since they didn’t have anything to say about the matter, Cadjo and Desbarres just nodded when they heard Margaret. Before long, their ship suspended a bridge to connect towards a Zhang Family battleship.

Entering another ship through a connection bridge required the approval of the ship being boarded. If nobody were inside the other ship, then the connection bridge would be useless. Cadjo and Desbarres turned to Zhao Hai and wondered how it worked. If it weren’t for Margaret, the two wouldn’t have been confident in boarding the ship.

Once they entered the decompression chamber of the other ship, Cadjo and Desbarres couldn’t help but stare. This was because those in the decompression chamber weren’t human, they were Undead!

There were no living beings in sight, but the two Undead present were wearing the Zhang Family’s uniform. When the Undead saw the group arrive, they immediately gave a salute before going to the side.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this as he led the others towards the ship. Once they were inside, Cadjo and Desbarres finally began to believe Zhao Hai. This was because they were able to see bloodstains inside the ship. However, besides the bloodstains, not a single person nor corpse was there.

Zhao Hai looked at the scene, then he smiled and said, “General Manager, Camp Lord, I have turned all of the people in the Zhang Family fleet into Undead. The ships have been completely preserved. As long as the family arrives, they can have the operators take over the ship and be more familiar with it. With enough practice, they would be able to use these to fight.”

Cadjo stared at the battleship, then he laughed all of a sudden. He repeatedly pat Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Good, Little Hai, well done. I’ll immediately explain the situation to the family. Also, I’ll leave a ship behind to guard this area. I’ll also leave some operators behind. At the very least, we could erect the ship’s shields and weapons. It’s highly probable for these ships to be hit by meteorites at any time. If we don’t guard them, they might be destroyed.”

Desbarres and the others were also laughing with happiness. After they returned to their ship, operators were left behind to staff the captured ships. Then shortly after that, they continued on with their journey.

Cadjo detailed everything Zhao Hai said in his report to the family. When Thunder read it, he couldn’t help but be surprised. He never thought Zhao Hai to move this flawlessly.

But what made him confused was how Zhao Hai was able to enter these ships silently. Nevertheless, Thunder proved that he was equipped to be a Patriarch. He didn’t ask much about the process and instead just sent people to retrieve the ships.

Naturally, the people who were with Zhao Hai on the fleet knew about his accomplishments. Their admiration towards him was now going through the roof. At the same time, those from the other camps completely removed the dissatisfaction in their hearts. When someone who defeated you only had a bit more strength, then you might feel that the result was unsatisfactory. However, when that person shows overwhelming strength, you couldn’t help but just accept it.”

Two days after Cadjo’s fleet left the Quicksand Starfield, the Ashley Family’s operators arrived. They quickly took over the 20 ships. The Ashley Family basically gained a fortune by doing nothing.

At this moment, Zhao Hai was inside the Space, observing the Quicksand Starfield. Naturally, the scene he was observing wasn’t the meteorite field outside the Quicksand Starfield, but instead the wide expanse of desert in the center.

Laura and the others were also looking at the vast desert. After some time, Megan said, “Big Brother Hai, don’t you want to take a look at the desert?”

After following beside Zhao Hai for a long time, Megan and the others were already aware of his thoughts. Seeing how Zhao Hai looked at the vast desert, they immediately knew that he wanted to personally see it for himself.

But there was one of them who was still clueless. When Margaret heard Megan, her expression changed as she asked, “Brother Hai, you really want to go there? You shouldn’t. It’s too dangerous.”

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret, then he smiled and said, “It’s fine. Nothing’s going to happen to me. I just want to take some sand and send it to the Space to see if it’s something useful.”

Margaret was still unwilling to let Zhao Hai go. But at this time, Laura said, “Margaret, it’s fine. There’s no need to worry about Brother Hai. And Brother Hai, you can go, but don’t go deep into the sand sea. Just take some sand for the Space and then exit the area.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then his body vanished. The next moment, he appeared on the screen. Margaret was looking at him with worry in her eyes.

When Laura and the others saw Margaret’s expression, then couldn’t help but smile. They weren’t worried about Zhao Hai at all. This was because they knew that nothing will happen to him.

Zhao Hai stood on a meteorite just on the outskirts of the sea of sand. Looking at the boundless desert, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh inside. This desert was too big. Under the radiance of the nearby stars, it shimmered with seven-colored lights. Such scenery wasn’t present inside the Space.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on taking a step towards the vast desert since he didn’t want to make Laura and the others worry. Instead, Zhao Hai waved his hand as a spatial rift appeared ten thousand meters in front of him. Before long, the spatial rift began sucking up the nearby sand. But what Zhao Hai didn’t expect was the corrosion brought up by these sand particles. As they came in contact with the rift, they actually made it even bigger.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, then he immediately closed the spatial rift. Then at this moment, the Space issued a prompt: “Everpresent Ancient Sand detected. Earth element attribute detected as well as the property to last for a very long time. It can be used to augment a weapon. It has effect stronger than black iron. It also has the ability to corrode materials as well as eliminate spiritual force.”

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he paused for a moment. He didn’t expect the sand to be this formidable. It could actually corrode all things. Moreover, it can eliminate spiritual force. These properties were terrifying.

The ability to corrode might be alright. However, the property to eliminate spiritual force was another thing altogether. Take the Cultivation Realm, for example. Weapons that underwent spirit attachment could be branded using one’s spiritual force. Once one was able to brand their spiritual force into a weapon, then that weapon would forever belong to them.

Fortunately, the spiritual force in most weapons could be eliminated once their masters were killed. However, if one killed a descendant of a powerful being, then they would need a substantial amount of spiritual force to remove the branding. Even if a trace of that powerful being’s spiritual force was left, it would still be very hard for it to be eliminated. Moreover, the powerful being could use that branding to locate the weapon and kill the thief.

In the Cultivation Realm, murders because of weapons were common. However, not a lot of people dared to kill those with powerful backgrounds. If they did, then they would be tracked down and killed. However, with the everlasting ancient sand, eliminating spiritual force on a weapon would be easier. Even those powerful experts would have no way of tracking their weapons.

Besides weapons, there was also another thing. In the Machine Field, most spatial equipment had no spiritual branding. So if it was lost, it would be very hard to find it. But in the Cultivation Realm, spatial items were like magical artifacts and were branded with spiritual force. If you cannot eliminate the owner’s spiritual branding on a spatial equipment, then it would be impossible for you to access its contents.

And if you decide to be forceful in breaking through the spatial equipment, then it might create a spatial disturbance inside and destroy everything. What you need to do was to erase the spiritual branding bit by bit. And this process would take quite a long time.

However, if one uses the everpresent ancient sand, this issue would be easily solved. It can be said that this material would be very useful for robbing the people from the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai entered the Space and immediately examined the sand. The sand was extremely small, much finer than ordinary sand. However, it was very heavy. Zhao Hai felt that the handful of sand he held weighed about ten thousand jin(5 thousand kg). Such weight to volume ratio was too astonishing.

The sand was golden yellow, bordering the color of gold dust. Because of this beauty, Laura and the others couldn’t help but look curiously at it.

After seeing nothing else, Zhao Hai stored the sand as everyone returned to the living room. The image currently displayed on the screen was the situation inside the ship.

Seeing that nothing was out of the norm, Zhao Hai turned to Margaret and said, “Margaret, how far are we from Machine Field Planet?”

Margaret smiled and said, “We’re not that far. We should be able to begin seeing ships from other families in two days.”

Chapter 1158: Uses of Supporting Magic Formations

And just like Margaret said, after two days of travel, the Ashley Family’s fleet began seeing the fleets of other families. These fleets weren’t huge. At most, there were ten ships in a fleet.

Zhao Hai was somewhat puzzled by this situation. After asking Margaret, he came to know that each family wouldn’t send too many ships during the realm qualifiers because Machine Field Planet couldn’t handle a lot of ships.

In the Machine Field, there were no less than 10 thousand small and large powers. Imagine if all these groups send large numbers of ships over. Then how many would fit in the space around the capital? Therefore, every realm qualifier, it was agreed that each power wouldn’t send too many ships.

Zhao Hai also saw Cadjo and Desbarres beginning to get busy greeting the other fleets. They even made direct communications from others. As for the rest, flashing their signal lights was enough.

Zhao Hai stayed in the Space for over two days before returning to the ship. He didn’t stop his cultivation during this time. His body tempering technique was beginning to get more and more refined. And as his body got stronger and stronger, his spiritual force was also increasing. Although these effects were only appearing slowly, Zhao Hai still kept pushing on.

Moreover, Zhao Hai began condensing formations once more. But this time, the formations he used were supporting magic formations. Zhao Hai also discovered that the number of supporting formations weren’t less than offensive and defensive formations, it was even possible that there were more.

It wasn’t easy making new combat formations. This was because there are latent dangers during each testing. However, this danger didn’t exist when it came to supporting magic formations. Some of these formations were used to increase the strength of metals. Some were designed to increase a metal’s radioactivity, some for increasing its property of transmitting signals, and many more.

Most importantly, there were no dangers in testing these formations. Even if the test failed, two or three things might be destroyed, nothing else. Because of this, there were more supporting formations than offensive and defensive formations.

Zhao Hai didn’t know whether he could find any uses for these formations. In any case, he still decided to condense them. Even if they were useless, nothing remarkable would be lost.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the result he would get. After these supporting formations were condensed and analyzed, it actually elevated the quality of Zhao Hai’s formation sets. Now Zhao Hai can use his spiritual force to support 3000-layer formations sets. These formations sets had a lot of supportive formations inside. After these supportive formations were added, not only was the strength of these formations preserved, the spiritual force needed to operate them also reduced by a lot. This was a very good news for Zhao Hai.

There was no need to mention his 5-layer and 10-layer formations. Their power increased by several folds while also reducing the time needed to cast them.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect these supporting formations to have this effect. But more surprised than Zhao Hai was Margaret. In the Machine Field, people always believed that supporting and combat magic formations were different. The two cannot be combined, otherwise the power of formation sets would drop.

But after seeing Zhao Hai’s formation sets, Margaret’s thoughts were changed. This event made Margaret more curious, she wanted to understand what was happening.

Margaret knew that if supporting formations and combat formations could really be united and have this effect, then it would be a huge boost for the Machine Field’s Mages. This will cause Magic Theory to obtain a huge qualitative leap forward.

This didn’t mean that nobody in the Machine Field tried to combine supporting and combat formations together. However, nobody had succeeded before. After seeing what just happened, Margaret knew that the issue was with how the two were combined.

There were simply too many supporting and combat formations in the Machine Field. Combining combat formations together was already hard, so there was no need to say what would happen if supporting formations were added to the mix. The more factors there were in a combination, the more complex the results would become. Finding a suitable combination for a formation set was easier said than done.

The Machine Field failed to combine combat and supporting formations because they had yet to find success. After carrying out experiments, they weren’t able to find an appropriate combination to make into a useful set. Because of this, the might of the resulting formation set was reduced, causing the current misconception.

But with the Space’s scanner, things like finding a suitable combination was made much easier. Because of this, the effect of supporting formations was seen.

At this point, in Margaret’s eyes, Liquid Silver was no longer the most valuable item in Zhao Hai’s hands. Instead, it should be the Universal Scanner. If people came to know about this godly device, then they would certainly find means to snatch it. The uses of the scanner far surpasses Liquid Silver.

Liquid Silver was a formidable weapon, enough to shake the current state of the realm. But in the end, Liquid Silver was just that, a weapon. Moreover, the spiritual force needed by Liquid Silver was enormous. Not anyone could use it.

On the other hand, the Universal Scanner would calculate differently according to different people. It was the most formidable device for making magic formation sets.

Imagine if a family had their hands on a universal scanner. All of their formations would be combined to form more powerful formations.

Powerful Experts were certainly important to families. However, a comprehensive increase is strength was something that they needed more.

While Zhao Hai was being busy, they finally arrived at Machine Field Planet. When they reached the planet, Zhao Hai and Margaret quickly went to the command hall. They wanted to take a look at the Machine Field’s capital.

Machine Field Planet was the realm’s center, its capital. This was where the three major powers stationed themselves. They even have their fleet stationed in its outer space bases.

From outer space, Machine Field Planet had three colors – green, blue, and silver! The green part was the forest, the blue part was the oceans, while the silver part were the buildings built on the surface.

Almost all of the buildings in the Machine Field Planet were made of metal. This place was the most developed area in the entire realm. All of the talented natives were also here, at Machine Field University.

The Machine Field University was an institution studying all sorts of fields. There were departments for Magic, Martial Arts, Magic Formations, Magic Formation Sets, Mechs, Battleships, Military Command, and other fields. All of the realm’s best teachers were also hired by the university, making it the best learning and research environment in the realm. Majority of the Machine Field’s Patriarchs were graduates from this institution.

Besides the university, Machine Field Planet also had the most special place in the realm, Leng Wuyeng’s Tomb!

Leng Wuyeng held a very special status in the Machine Field. It could even be said that the Machine Field would not exist without him. Therefore, every year on Leng Wuyeng’s day of passing, plenty of people would come here to pay homage. This has become a tradition in the Machine Field.

Looking at the beautiful planet, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel somewhat excited. This place was an amalgamation of the realm’s talents. He would be lying if he said he wasn’t thrilled.

Cadjo looked at the planet, then he looked at Zhao Hai. Seeing Zhao Hai’s calm expression as well as the burst of fighting intent in his eye, he couldn’t help but smile and said, “While we wait for the qualifiers to start, I’ll be taking you to visit people who had made friends with our Ashley Family. We’ll also visit Bishop Gode from the Dark Church. You can explore the place when the competition ends. But before that, we can’t have you aimlessly wander the planet.”

All the family’s representatives nodded. At this time, the ship’s captain received confirmation for their dock. Before long, the ship was anchored on a dock with a platform.

Once the ship has stopped, Cadjo brought Zhao Hai and the others out of the ship. This dock wasn’t an outer space base. Instead it was a place where outsider ships could dock their ships. It was designed roughly the same as outer space bases.

When Cadjo and the others got down from the ship, a person wearing Dark Mage Robes immediately walked over and said, “General Manager, Camp Lord Desbarres, welcome. The vehicles have already been prepared.”

Cadjo smiled faintly and said, “Luke, you’re too courteous. Little Hai, let me introduce you. This is Luke, he’s a family director stationed in Machine Field Planet. Luke, this is Bone Symbol Camp’s Zhao Hai, the champion of the family’s qualifier.”

Luke looked at Zhao Hai, his eyes shone as he nodded said, “Zhao Hai, I’ve heard about you. The family’s new genius. I’ll be eyeing you in the realm qualifiers.”

Zhao Hai was also observing Luke. The man was about 1.8 meters tall. His hair was very neatly combed. His robe was also carefully organized that one couldn’t see a single crease on it. One could see from this point that he was a very old-fashioned man.

Zhao Hai quickly returned the greeting, “I wouldn’t disappoint Director Luke.”

Luke nodded, then he turned to Cadjo and said, “Everything has been arranged. As for the ship’s staff, somebody else is in charge of taking care of them.” Then he led the group to a nearby small ship.

After everyone entered the ship, it immediately took off and flew towards the planet. From what Zhao Hai saw, Machine Field Planet was much more prosperous than Dark Demon Planet. There were a lot of other small ships shuttling back and forth in the planet’s atmosphere. It was a very busy scene.

The ship quickly entered the planet’s atmosphere. Before long, the ship stopped in front of a building. This building wasn’t very high, at least thirty floors. With the buildings surrounding it having more than 100 floors, it appeared on the shorter side. On this large building was a huge emblem. Upon looking at it, Zhao Hai identified that the insignia belonged to the Ashley Family.

After the ship stopped, Luke quickly led everyone down. Along the way, Luke was seen whispering things into Cadjo’s ear. Luke was quite casual with Cadjo. Neither one of them exuded authority over the other. One could see from this point that Cadjo trusted Luke very much.

Luke led everyone into the building. Then after everyone were assigned their own room, Luke invited Cadjo and Desbarres to his room.

Not long after the three met, a robot arrived outside Zhao Hai’s room and knocked on the door. When Zhao Hai opened the door, the robot immediately said, “Mister Zhao Hai, Director Luke is asking for your presence. Please come with me.” Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. He just closed the door and then followed the robot to Luke’s room.

When Zhao Hai entered Luke’s room, he couldn’t help but stare. He expected everyone to be here. Instead, the only other people inside were Cadjo and Desbarres. Nobody else was here, not even Margaret.

Although Zhao Hai paused for a moment, he immediately recovered. He didn’t say anything and just gave the three a salute and then sat down.

After Zhao Hai sat down, Cadjo said, “Little Hai, we invited you over to let Luke introduce you to Machine Field Planet’s situation. This is to prepare you for the future. At the same time, we also want to tell you about an order from the family.”

Zhao Hai stared, but he still nodded and asked, “What order did the family give?”

Cadjo’s eyes flashed a cold light, then he said, “The Patriarch wants you to cripple Sun Fei!”

Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised, he nodded and said, “Alright, the moment I face Sun Fei, I will immediately cripple his cultivation. The General Manager doesn’t need to worry about this. Even if the family didn’t give me this order, I will still cripple him to lessen the Zhang Family’s benefits.”

Luke was somewhat surprised at Zhao Hai’s response. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to accept the order this easily. One must know that Fire Saint Sun Fei wasn’t someone that could easily be dealt with. He was known as a rare talent in the Zhang Family. Moreover, his title wasn’t just nonsense. His fire element magic was indeed more powerful than most. Average people wouldn’t even think of winning against him. So why was Zhao Hai talking about this matter as though it was as simple as brewing tea?

But what surprised Luke more were Cadjo and Desbarres’s responses. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai was saying something strange, they wore normal expressions when they heard Zhao Hai.

Cadjo nodded and said, “Try to not head out in the next few days. Now that only a few people know about your true strength, people will want to understand you better. If someone provokes you outside, make sure to endure.”

Zhao Hai just nodded and didn’t say anything.

Chapter 1159: Visit

Desbarres sneered and said, “If they really want to test Little Hai’s strength, then he might as well show them. Let Little Hai go out and challenge those bastards. I can still remember what they did in the past.”

Cadjo smiled and said, “All these years, we’re always at the receiving end of their bullying. It’s good to expel some bad air.”

When Luke saw how confident Cadjo and Desbarres were, he couldn’t help but get curious. He looked at the two and asked, “Is Little Hai really that strong?” Cadjo smiled and said, “If you face Little Hai, then even you might not survive. Alright, Little Hai, you can head back first and study the materials we gave you.” Zhao Hai nodded before he turned around and left.

Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Luke looked at Cadjo and Desbarres and said, “You really are that confident in Zhao Hai huh? Anyway, you two really showed off this time. You defeated 20 ships of the Zhang Family. You even managed to leave them intact. The Young Master is very happy. I’m sure he will reward you when you return.”

Cadjo and Desbarres looked at each other and smiled, then Cadjo said, “You say we defeated 20 Zhang Family battleships? What if we tell you that they were defeated by Little Hai alone? Will you believe me?”

When Luke heard Cadjo, he couldn’t help but stare, then he exclaimed, “He did that? Are you telling the truth? Don’t you lie to me.”

Cadjo rolled his eyes and said, “Bah. Luke I’m telling you this because Zhao Hai’s relationship with Miss Margaret is doing well. It wouldn’t be long before he becomes a powerhouse of our Ashley Family. Do you really think that we will falsely give him merit?”

Luke muttered, “So the kid is really a hero huh. It seems like its time for us to hold our heads up high.” One must say that Luke had been feeling suffocated all these years. It wasn’t only the Ashley Family who had a building in the Machine Field Planet. The other families also opened branches here.

If the relationship between two families were good, then they would lend each other a hand. However, if two families were at odds with each other, then it’s normal for them to compete.

In the Machine Field Planet, people wouldn’t act unreasonably. After all, this planet was where the three major powers did their work. Moreover, this was where Leng Wuyeng was buried. If they dared to disturb the peace, then the three major powers definitely wouldn’t let them off.

However, things like discouraging talks couldn’t be avoided. In the past few years, the Ashley Family has been getting bad results in the realm qualifiers. Naturally, this gave the Ashley Family’s enemies an opportunity to take shots at them. The amount of negative words that Luke had received all this time was enough to kill a human being.

Because of this, Luke had always been hoping for the family to produce a powerful expert. This way, the Ashley Family could turn the tables and allow Luke to breathe out some foul air. And now that Zhao Hai was here, Luke couldn’t help but be happy.

While the three were talking to each other, a knock was suddenly heard, then a voice came in, “Director, Zhang Family’s Young Master Mingyue is here. He wants to see Miss Margaret.”

When he heard this, Luke immediately opened the door. He looked at his assistant and said, “What?” The assistant replied, “Director, the Zhang Family’s Young Master brought people over to pay Miss Margaret a visit. They’re currently in the guest room.”

Luke knitted his brows. Then he waved his hand and said, “Alright, I’ll go down soon.” The man responded before turning around and leaving.

Luke looked at Cadjo and Desabaress and asked, “What do you think?” Luke knew about the dirty matters regarding the Zhang Family. Therefore, he asked the two for their opinion.

Cadjo sneered and said, “Let’s inform Miss Margaret about this first. I want to see what she has to say.” Luke nodded, “Alright, you wait here while I go see her.” However, Cadjo and Desbarres stood up and said, “Let’s go together.” Then the three walked over to Margaret’s room.

Just after Cadjo knocked on the door, Margaret’s voice was heard, “Yes?” Cadjo said, “Little Margaret, it’s me.”

Margaret opened the door and was shocked. She didn’t expect Cadjo and the others would look for her. She looked at the three and asked, “Uncle, what’s the problem?”

Cadjo replied, “Young Miss, Mingyue is here. He wants to see you. What do you think?”

Margaret’s expression sank, then she coldly said, “Mingyue wanted to see me? And why should I meet him? Our engagement has already been broken.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “Alright, I understand.” Then he turned around and went towards the elevator. He will go meet the Zhang Family’s Young Master.

When Margaret saw the three of them leave, she didn’t immediately go back to her room. Instead, she went to Zhao Hai’s room. She thought that it would be best to tell Zhao Hai about this. After all, she was once engaged to the Zhang Family. She didn’t want Zhao Hai to misunderstand. Although she hasn’t seen Zhang Mingyue for a long time, she didn’t have any feelings towards him.

Margaret knocked on Zhao Hai’s door. Before long, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Come in.”

Margaret pushed the door open and saw Zhao Hai sitting beside the table reading the materials Cadjo gave him. These materials were information regarding the various participants in the realm qualifiers. Naturally, it was impossible to list all of the participants. Cadjo made sure to sort them out and leave only those with substantial strength. However, the list still had several thousand people.

Zhao Hai looked at Margaret and said, “Margaret, why are you here? Come take a seat.”

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, Mingyue came. He said he wants to see me. But since I don’t want to meet the Zhang Family, I had Uncle Cadjo see him.”

Zhao Hai said, “Zhang Mingyue? Who’s that? Ah, its that Third Young Master from the Zhang Family, the one you were engaged to. Why is he here? Doesn’t he know about the current state between the Zhang Family and Ashley Family?”

Margaret replied, “I don’t know. Even I don’t understand. I haven’t even met him that many times. His visit here is somewhat strange.”

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows. Then he suddenly smiled and said, “Interesting, very interesting. I think this Mingyue didn’t come to see you, he wants to challenge me. Hehe. It seems like the Zhang Family is unwilling to give up.”

When Margaret heard this, she couldn’t help but feel relieved, then she looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, what do we do now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This MIngyue didn’t bring Sun Fei. Instead, he wants his family’s experts to cripple me, reducing the risk to Sun Fei. Let’s head inside the Space.” Margaret nodded and the two went to the Space.

Upon entering the Space, the two saw Laura and the others in front of the monitor. On the screen was the confrontation between Cadjo and another party.

The other party only had ten people in it. Leading them was a young man. This young man was wearing a fire red mage robe. He had a delicate and pretty appearance, as well as a masterful bearing. However, arrogance could be clearly seen on his face. His two eyes were cold making everyone he looked at feel uncomfortable.

Behind him were five Warriors and four Mages. The five Warriors looked much older than the young man, with the youngest looking at least 30-years old. All of them carried a sword and seems to share the preference for two-handed swords. Their swords were longer than what seems comfortable and was also wider than normal swords. The sword cross also looked very imposing, which made them look magnificent.

As for the four Mages, they were also wearing fire red mage robes. Just like the Warriors, they were older than the young man. They also held red magic staffs on their hands. Although one couldn’t see what the staffs were made of, it was clear that they were advanced-level goods.

Zhang Mingyue stood up when he saw Cadjo and said, “Cadjo, don’t give me that smiling face of yours. I want to see my fiance. This isn’t something you can budge into.”

Cadjo was smiling, however his eyes began to narrow down. Those familiar with him would know that he was close to losing his temper. But Cadjo still chuckled and said, “Young Master, you must be joking. Your fiance isn’t here. My family has already renounced our arrangement with the Zhang Family’s Patriarch. Is the Young Master unaware of this?”

Zhang Mingyue coldly snorted and said, “So you’re saying that my engagement has been broken? Who gave you such power? Did this Young Master agree to it?”

Cadjo just smiled when he replied, “Young Master Mingyue misunderstands. I didn’t renounce your engagement, the Ashley Family’s Patriarch and the Zhang Family’s Patriarch agreed to it. Does the Young Master not know this? Or you just don’t agree with your family head’s decision?”

Zhang Mingyue expression changed. He knew that he would need to think about his next words. Otherwise, his father wouldn’t let him off. Although they were father and son, in the face of the family’s matters, paternal love was useless.

Zhang Mingyue sneered and said, “Of course I know about the decision. However, we’ve been in a good relationship all these years. I just want to see Margaret. Am I demanding too much?”

Cadjo smiled and said, “So this is what Young Master meant. However, I’ll have to apologize. Our Young Miss is not here. She just left and I don’t know when she’ll be back. I’ll have to ask the Young Master to return another time.”

Zhang Mingyue’s expression changed. He knew for certain that Cadjo was deceiving him. However, he didn’t have the means to push through. If he decided to force himself in, then Cadjo might make a move. If this matter reaches outside, then the Zhang Family would face consequences. After all, this was Machine Field Planet, not the Zhang Family’s domain.

Zhang Mingyue also had talent for cultivation. After years of cultivation, he managed to reach level 6. However, he still fell short compared to the cunning of Cadjo. With Cadjo here, Mingyue was left not knowing what to do.

At this time, a Mage behind Mingyue stepped forward and said,” I have seen General Manager Cadjo. Since Miss Margaret left, then we’ll have to let this matter go. However, the Young Master is also here to meet the Ashley Family’s new genius, his name is Zhao Hai right? We heard that he’s quite strong. Although he just ascended months ago, he’s already able to win your family qualifiers. When our Patriarch heard about this, he couldn’t help but feel happy. Because of this, he prepared a gift specifically for Zhao Hai. He wants us to personally hand it over. I don’t know if General Manager Cadjo will allow us to see him?”

Chapter 1160: Exhausted

When Cadjo heard the Mage, he immediately knew what they were after. They just wanted Zhao Hai to appear so that they could challenge him. Then they would find an opportunity to kill him in battle.

To be honest, Cadjo wasn’t afraid of Zhao Hai being challenged by these people. He believes that Zhao Hai could easily defeat them. However, it might force Zhao Hai to explode with his true strength, which wouldn’t be good for Zhao Hai.

Cadjo smiled faintly and said, “This is really unfortunate. Zhao Hai has been closing up recently. Not just here, but also on the ship. Because of this, he couldn’t see Young Master Zhang. If Young Master Zhang has something to give Zhao Hai, then I can give it to him on your behalf.”

Shameless!

Mingyue and the others had this same thought inside their hearts. They had seen shameless people before, but they haven’t seen someone so shameless that they would lie straight to their face. There wasn’t even a tinge of red on his face.

However, Mingyue and the others couldn’t do anything about it. This place was the Ashley Family’s office. If they caused any trouble here, then their family would be directly affected.

Zhang Mingyue rolled his eyes, then he suddenly had an inspiration. He looked at Cadjo and laughed, then he said, “I didn’t expect the Ashley Family’s so-called genius to actually be a cowardly turtle. I heard that Margaret has been playing around with him lately? So is he just a pretty boy that she feeds? Hahaha. Only knowing how to hide under a woman’s skirt. So this is the Ashley Family’s genius. Such a person wants to receive my gift? I’m leaving!” Zhang Mingyue made sure to use magic alongside his voice so that the entire building could hear him.

Although Zhang Mingyue said that he was leaving, he didn’t actually have any intention to head out. He just stood there arrogantly and waited.

Awkward silence!

Cadjo and Desbarres looked at the proudly standing Zhang Mingyue. Nobody made any noise. At the same time, Mingyue stayed there, as though waiting for Cadjo to say something.

Five minutes passed by…

Zhang Mingyue’s expression began to turn dark….

Ten minutes passed by, Zhang Mingyue turned pale. In these ten minutes, Cadjo didn’t say a single word. Desbarres and Luke were also similarly silent. And even Zhao Hai who was badmouthed stayed silent. Zhang Mingyue began to feel like he was acting like a fool, jumping on the limelight in order to attract attention. And now that nobody bought his antics, he looked like a stupid monkey.

Cadjo and Desbarres naturally knew about Zhang Mingyue’s thoughts. To be honest, they were afraid of Zhao Hai falling into Zhang Mingyue’s trick.

In the beginning, Cadjo intended to berate Zhang Mingyue with a few words. However, after looking at his proud expression, Cadjo began to want Zhao Hai to come out and deal with Zhang Mingye’s group.

But what Cadjo didn’t expect was Zhao Hai’s absence. Seeing Zhang Mingyue left drying up in the sun for several minutes, Cadjo really wanted to speak. But after seeing Mingyue’s expression turned darker and darker as Zhao Hai continued to be absent, Cadjo decided to stay silent. He just stood there to watch the fun.

He suddenly found out that ignoring someone was also a good way to deal with taunts. Not only that, knowing that they were being ignored, the perpetrator would become angrier as time goes by.

Cadjo observed as Zhang Mingyue’s expression turned blue. He couldn’t help but suppress his laughter. He felt that Mingyue would spit out some blood soon. It was actually amusing to look at.

Desbarres was also happily spectating at the side. On the other hand, Luke’s expression was somewhat distorted. His stomach was contracted too much that it might get shredded. If he wasn’t facing the Zhang Family, then he would have long since laughed out loud.

Seeing that Zhang Mingyue was about to spit out some blood, Cadjo couldn’t help but cough lightly and said, “Young Master Zhang, Zhao Hai is unavailable. If you have anything to give Zhao Hai, then I can send it on your behalf. If you don’t have any other matters here, then I’ll have to ask you to leave.”

At this moment, Zhao Hai’s stomach was already hurting from laughter. Not only him, Laura and the others were also making fun of Zhang Mingyue’s current expression.

Seeing Zhang MIngyue leave, Zhao Hai stopped laughing and turned to Margaret and said, “Margaret, stop laughing. Let’s go out, it’s time to return.”

Margaret nodded as she wiped the tear on her eye. Then she took deep breaths to calm herself down from laughing. After some time, she stopped and the two returned to Zhao Hai’s room.

When Mingyue and the others were out of sight, Cadjo and the others wildly laughed. It took almost all of their strength to stop themselves from laughing. But now that the other party was gone, they laughed loudly.

It took some time before the group calmed down. Then they went back to the elevator and headed towards Margaret’s room. But when they knocked on the door, nobody was in. Then when they thought about it they immediately went to Zhao Hai’s room.

Sure enough, after knocking on Zhao Hai’s door, Margaret was the one to open it. The three entered and saw Zhao Hai sitting beside the table, looking through materials.

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Little Hai, did you hear Zhang Mingyue?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Of course I heard it. That person is interesting, he came here just to shout like an idiot. Hahaha. He actually wanted to trick me. Did he leave?” When Cadjo recalled Zhang MIngyue’s dark expression, he couldn’t help but laugh once more. As they talked about what just happened, even Zhao Hai and Margaret laughed at times.

After talking about this matter, Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Right, Little Hai, you need to hold back even if you get taunted by them. The family isn’t officially at war with the Zhang Family. If you deal with Zhang Mingyue now, then the situation would escalate. This wouldn’t be good for our future plans.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t intend to head down at all. If I know that the other side is tricking me and I still go, then wouldn’t I be the fool? But they better make sure that I don’t meet Sun Fei, or else I’ll immediately kill him.”

Cadjo smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then you go take a rest. Don’t leave the building in the next few days. I’m certain that the Zhang Family has sent people to monitor your actions. Once you get spotted, they will immediately attack you. I can only ask for your forgiveness for the next few days.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “General Manager, it’s fine. You can rest assured, I wouldn’t leave the building.”

Cadjo nodded. Then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder before leaving.

When the three men left, Zhao Hai brought Margaret to the Space. While Zhao Hai was sitting on the side reading some information, Margaret and the others divided Liquid Silver and then used it to explore the entire planet.

It has already become a custom for Laura and the others to release needles to scout whenever they reach a new area. This way, they would become more familiar with the place and also monitor their enemies.

The silver needles were originally tiny. And with Laura and the others commanding it to fly at high altitudes as well as deep underground, it was impossible for other people to discover them. Because of this, the women looked like they were playing around.

Zhao Hai actually wasn’t paying much attention to the things written in the materials he was provided. It was impossible for these people to be a threat to him. Paying attention to them would only be a waste of energy. Therefore, he just swept through most of the material without any care.

The levels of these participants weren’t too high. The strongest among them were level 4 while the lowest was level 1.

The Mages and Warriors sent by the smaller powers had some qualities worth looking at. Some of them were level 3 or level 4. It seems like these smaller powers were trying to use this qualifiers to elevate their positions.

Nevertheless, Zhao Hai still didn’t care. He just read these materials in order to get acquainted with the general state of the realm. After all, no participant could match him in this competition.

In addition to reading about the beginners, Zhao Hai also checked their situation using the internet. But unfortunately, the network of the Machine Realm wasn’t so interconnected. He couldn’t find a lot of useful things.

At this time, while Zhao Hai was browsing through information, Laura suddenly yelled, “Brother Hai, come here, quick. We found something!” Zhao Hai quickly put his computer down and went to the living room. Shown on the monitor was a fight. And among these people was someone who left an impression on him, Strong Wind Li Kuangren!

This Li Kuangren was one of the ten experts that Cadjo introduced. Judging by the information they had on him, this person was quite strong. When Zhao Hai saw the fight, he became curious and immediately sat down to spectate.

Li Kuangren was about 1.8 meters tall. He had withered and uncombed hair with a full beard. His two eyes were cold. He only had ordinary clothes on. And in his hand were his two broad axes. He didn’t look very big but it was evident that he was strong. His face was quite long horizontally. He had a dark skin that seemed to have a special luster to it. When he saw this, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but flash. His defense was quite formidable, otherwise his skin wouldn’t turn into this appearance.

Zhao Hai was curious about his opponent. But as he looked at the other side, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get surprised. This was because he knew these people. They were the five Warriors that Zhang Mingyue had with him, the ones with the heavy cross swords!

Chapter 1161: Strong Wind Li Kuangren

Zhao Hai noticed these Warriors at that time. All of them had heavy cross swords and they also have similar temperaments. From what he can see, it seems like they practiced a coordination technique. Zhao Hai wanted to see it in action.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Laura, can you look into how these people had a  conflict with Li Kuangren? Aren’t they with Zhang Mingyue just earlier?”

Laura turned to look at Cai’er. Cai’er waved her hand and changed the image on the monitor. When Zhang Mingyue left the building, he was very angry that he needed to drink at the hotel. And because of his anger, he heavily scolded a hotel staff. Meanwhile, Li Kuangren was at the same hotel. When he saw Zhang Mingyue, he coldly snorted.

Zhang Mingyue was already incensed about Zhao Hai. Hearing someone snort at him, he immediately stood up and pointed towards Li Kuangren and said, “What are you snorting about? You have something to say?”

Naturally, Li Kuangren wasn’t a peaceful monk, he also stood up and said, “Pretty boy, do you know who you’re pointing to?”

This made the situation even more difficult. Mingyue just called Zhao Hai a pretty boy, and now Zhang Mingyue was called the same thing. This caused Zhang Mingyue to be even more angry, he coldly snorted and said, “I’m talking to you, outsider. You think you can just call everyone out when you’re from the lower realm? Know your place.”

Zhang Mingyue’s words weren’t unusual here in the Machine Field. However, only a few people would dare to publicly say this, unless they want to offend all the lower realm ascenders. One must know that there were a lot of ascenders in the Machine Field. There’s no benefits to offending all of these people.

Zhang Mingyue’s words made the room turn colder. The words he spoke were taboo. It wasn’t only Li Kuangren whose expression changed, even the other Warriors and Mages in the room had ugly expressions.

Li Kuangren looked at Zhang Mingyue, then he laughed and said, “Pretty boy, you’re quite fearless aren’t you. Since you don’t know your manners, let this grandfather teach you a lesson.” Then after he said that, he went straight for Zhang Mingyue.

Although Zhang Mingyue looked delicate, his strength was the real deal. He waved his hand and released a 5-layer defensive formation to protect himself. At the same time, he retreated behind the five Warriors who already pulled their cross swords out and rushed forward.

These five were indeed cultivating a special technique. All of their moves were well coordinated. Their five swords proceeded to assault Li Kuangren, attacking him at all points.

Li Kuangren was also an expert. When he saw the situation, he immediately retreated backwards. Then he flew out of the hotel with his two broad axes. At the same time, he yelled out, “Pretty boy, you still owe 300 rounds with this grandpa.”

But before he could add to his sentence, the five Warriors already jumped out of the hotel and stood opposite him.

And this led to the present situation. The display on the monitor changed once more and returned to Li Kuangren’s confrontation with the five Warriors.

Li Kuangren gripped his axes. He looked at the five Warriors opposite him, then he said, “The Five Element Tigers. You’re quite the celebrities in the Zhang Family’s External Hall. This Li Kuangren has heard so much about you. But I didn’t expect that you’re just lackeys to someone like Zhang Mingyue. Wanting to die for him is such a disgrace.”

Because Zhao Hai had just recently ascended, and had spent most of his time cultivating, he didn’t know much about famous characters in the Machine Field. On the other hand, Li Kuangren had already ascended for four years. And with how many missions he has accomplished, he was well-versed with experts of External Halls. As for these five cross-sword wielding Warriors, Li Kuangren knew that they were the Five-element Tigers of the Zhang Family’s Golden Sword Camp.

The Zhang Family’s External Hall was named differently from the Ashley Family. Their External Hall was divided into eight camps; metal, water, wood, fire, earth, wind, light, and dark. The Gold Sword Camp was the Zhang Family’s camp that belonged to the metal element.

All ascenders of the Zhang Family would join these camps according to their attribute. It didn’t matter if they were a Mage or a Warrior, they were categorized the same.

As for the five-element tigers, they were metal element Warriors from the Gold Sword Camp. The reason they were called five-element tigers was due to the technique that they practiced, a formation known as the five-element golden light. With this formation set, the five were able to make a name in the Machine Field.

One of the five element tigers coldly snorted and said, “Li Kuangren, it seems like you want to withdraw from this competition. You need to know that there are some people that you can’t offend.”

Li Kuangren laughed when he heard this, “Unable to offend? You mean the pretty boy? Hahahaha. He’s just a useless pretty face who had his marriage agreement broken. Hahaha. What ability does he have?”

Zhang Mingyue couldn’t bear the humiliation as he pointed at Li Kuangren and said, “Kill him! Kill him for me!”

The Five Element Tigers quickly moved and threw themselves towards Li Kuangren. The five surrounded their opponent in all directions.

Li Kuangren began to wildly laugh as he said, “Good, good. Let this grandfather see the  mighty five elements golden light.” Then he began to wave his axes, causing strong winds to surround the area.

Zhao Hai now knew why Li Kuangren was given the nickname “Strong Winds” The attack of his axes had some special characteristics. When he attacked, the axes would cause turbulence in the surrounding area. Not only would this increase its power, it also added a rotational orientation to the attack, increasing the potential damage that it could inflict.

Zhao Hai was thinking that Li Kuangren’s axes must be very heavy. And it was certain that he was using a special technique to wield them. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to control his axes as he continued to wave them around.

At this time, the winds surrounding Li Kuangren were getting bigger and bigger before finally turning into a whirlwind. The Five Element Tigers were wrapped up in it, the sound of clashing weapons were endless.

Zhao Hai watched this happen and couldn’t help but secretly nod. He didn’t only agree to Li Kuangren’s method, he also commended the five element golden lights that the five Warriors were using. When this formation set was used by the five Warriors simultaneously, one could see that it was very powerful. If not for Li Kuangren’s exquisite control of his axes, then he would have already been defeated. However, with the current situation, it wouldn’t be long before Li Kuangren would admit defeat.

To be honest, Zhao Hai quite liked Li Kuangren’s character. However, he wouldn’t go so far as to help him at this moment. This was because Zhao Hai knew that fights in this planet wouldn’t last long. This was Machine Field Planet, causing too much commotion here would incur the ire of the three major powers.

Just as Zhao Hai expected, not long after the two sides began fighting, several cars flew over and surrounded them. Then a voice was heard, “Stop fighting immediately. If you don’t, then don’t blame us for being impolite.”

Li Kuangren and the Five Element Tigers slowly stopped their movements. Then they jumped out of their battle area. At this time, another announcement was heard, “Fighting is forbidden in Machine Field Planet. If you want to duel, you need to go to the police station and register. This is a warning, the next time you fight, you will be arrested.” Then after they said that, the cars left the area.

But even when the police had left, the two sides didn’t continue fighting. Although Zhang MIngyue was the Zhang Family’s Young Master, he was a nobody here. If he dared to act unreasonably, then there’s no stopping the police force from being impolite.

Because of the realm qualifiers, the planet was currently filled with a lot of influential figures. Some important members of smaller powers even came here to see the competition. One could say that the current Machine Field Planet was filled with Patriarchs. In such a situation, Young Masters were merely dogs on the street. If Zhang Mingyue really dared to continue fighting, then he would be arrested by the police. By that time, he would become a joke in the Machine Field. And this wasn’t something that Zhang Mingyue would want.

The same was true for Li Kuangren. Although he looked crude, he wasn’t insane. He’s a participant in the realm qualifiers. If he did get arrested by the police, then he might not be able to compete. Once he returns to his family, his status would certainly drop. The situation wasn’t worth it.

Since both sides had no intentions of fighting, nobody made another move. Li Kuangren stored his axes as he looked at Mingyue and said, “Pretty boy, I’ll remember your Zhang Family. You best pray that I don’t run into your participants in the competition. Otherwise, you can’t blame me for being merciless.” Then he coldly snorted and left.

Zhang Mingyue’s face was pale as he looked at Li Kuangren. Then he countered, “Commoner, you better survive this competition. I still have to kill you personally.”

Li Kuangren laughed as he walked out.

Seeing Li Kuangren’s actions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is nice. The Zhang Family just offended someone. Hehe. Let’s just hope that Li Kuangren doesn’t encounter Sun Fei. Or else I won’t get my chance.”

Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, this Li Kuangren is quite interesting. It might be good to be friends with him.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I also think that he’s interesting. If I have the opportunity, then I’ll befriend him. He might look rugged, but at least he still knows when to advance and retreat. He also has a good heart. He’s worth paying attention to.”

At this time, Lizzy turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, look, I saw someone.” Zhao Hai turned to look at Lizzy’s screen and saw a person wearing mage robes. He had pale blue hair and was quite handsome. It’s actually the first of Cadjo’s ten experts, Streep.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Saint of Ice Streep. He actually dared to walk outside. It seems like the Water Temple is confident that nobody would challenge him.”

Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, who do you think is the strongest among the ten experts?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m not completely certain but I’m confident in Zhang Qinghe, Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, and Lei Xiaotian. They look very strong to me.”

Megan stared, then he looked over their information. After she read through them all, she said, “Brother Hai, why do you favor these people?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Zhang Qinghe is a rare metal element Mage. And with Rhea family’s training, his fighting strength has improved by a lot. You should already be aware about the metal element’s offensive strength. As for Xiong Li, he has been favored by god and was given an innate talent in cultivation. Additionally, Xiong Li has very rich actual combat experience. Dongfang Yu has the Fire Dragon Sword. Although it looks superficial, his ability to use this artifact allowed him to reach his current status. You should know that artifacts only choose those who are worthy of them. Being chosen by the Fire Dragon Sword means that he has something special. And lastly, Lei Xiao Tian is a dual-element Mage. As long as he levels up and masters his elements, he will be much stronger than other Mages of his level. Naturally, the others couldn’t be underestimated. Take Li Kuangren for example, I reckon that he’s still holding back in the fight just now. During the competition, the participants would certainly show the aces in their hands.”

Margaret nodded and said, “Those ten experts certainly have some secrets. Talents from the External Halls are carefully trained by their families. Regarding these talents, families wouldn’t be stingy when it comes to resources. They’re not like the Ashley Family that develops everyone equally. Therefore, these people would surely have powerful items. But since the competition has yet to start, they wouldn’t dare take them out.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. Not to say about the others, even our Bone Symbol Camp has a very rich treasury. Taking into account that entire families are involved in this matter, these ten great experts certainly had massive amounts of resources poured over them. It’s impossible for them to not have any aces or two. Therefore, we can’t just look at the surface to see who is stronger. Equipment is also a huge factor to consider.”

Laura and the others nodded. Then Zhao Hai sighed and said, “If the experts from the Machine Field are already like this, then what would the other realms have? People in the Machine Field are at the bottom in terms of strength in the World of Cultivation. Seeing how strong these Machine Field Experts are, one might wonder about the strength of the other realms.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others couldn’t help but feel heavy inside. Seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, I’m just thinking too much. If they aren’t strong, then it would be boring. Hahaha.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s soaring confidence, Laura and the others couldn’t help but stare at him. Zhao Hai normally appeared ordinary. But at this moment, his body was extremely radiant.

Chapter 1162: Survival Elimination Series

Time quickly flew past and the first day of the realm qualifiers had come. In these past few days, Machine Planet was anything but peaceful. There were more than several hundred duel requests that were submitted to the local police station. It was fortunate that the local police had already prepared for this. As long as both sides were willing to fight and the participants pay rent for the arena, they would no longer budge in even if someone was killed. Naturally, these fights would be held in areas approved by the police.

Unlike other people, Zhao Hai didn’t head out to see the scenery outside. Instead, he looked at the planet through the Space’s monitor. But even if this was the case, other people were still able to gain information about him.

One shouldn’t underestimate a person’s ability to find information. These families had existed in the Machine Field for many years, and their relationships had gone completely intertwined. Today, you might find a spy in your house, and then the other day you would plant a bomb on theirs. There was no such thing as secrets to the people in the Machine Field.

Naturally, the core secrets of the families were heavily guarded, otherwise that family would be finished. So even if nobody knew that Zhao Hai completed Liquid Silver, the other families still knew that he was strong. And there were fuzzy videos of his battles being passed on to other people.

Zhao Hai was already considered as the eleventh expert after the ten famous ones. And his information had also been placed on the desks of major families.

To be honest, when these great families saw Zhao Hai’s material, they were shocked. They never expected a monstrous talent like him to appear. He hadn’t even ascended for a year yet he was already a level 4 Mage. Moreover, he was able to win first place in the family qualifiers.

Zhao Hai has already incurred the attention of all forces in the Machine Field. Information even from the time he ascended were dug up. Seeing Zhao Hai’s enchanting growth, it wasn’t a mystery why these people were surprised.

Nowadays, a lot of participants had already tagged Zhao Hai as the most dangerous person in the competition. But even if Zhao Hai knew about this, he didn’t care. After all, his goal wasn’t in the Machine Field, but in the much broader World of Cultivation.

Zhao Hai and Margaret were currently inside the Space while drinking tea. Then suddenly, Cai’er came over and said, “Young Master, you need to go back to your room. Desbarres is looking for you.” Zhao Hai nodded and returned to his room. And before long, a knock was heard on the door.

Zhao Hai opened the door and saw Desbarres, Cadjo, and Luke outside. He immediately invited the three in. After they had sat down and were drinking tea, Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and said, “General Manager, do you need me for anything?”

Cadjo nodded and said, “The competition is tomorrow. How do you feel?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really don’t feel anything. I’m just normal.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “I’m here to tell you about the competition. As it turns out, this competition had a record high number of participants. Because of this, the competition committee decided to change how it went. Unlike the past, the competition wouldn’t be a fight in the arena and instead would be an elimination series.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Elimination series? How different is it?”

Cadjo nodded and said, “There’s a huge difference. This time, the fight won’t happen in an arena. Instead, it’s a survival elimination.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed a cold light, then he asked, “Survival Elimination? We can kill others?”

Cadjo gave a nod, “Right, you can kill. Little Hai, I think you should have heard about Yellowsand Planet, right? The elimination will happen there.”

Zhao Hai has certainly heard about Yellowsand Planet. This planet was quite famous, its existence was very special. It can be said to be one of planets that haven’t been completely conquered in the Machine Field. Majority of the reason for this was because its environment was terrible.

Yellowsand Planet was situated at the edge of the Machine Field. Even if it wasn’t far away from the Cultivation Realm, it was still closer to the Machine Field. But even if this was the case, only a few people from the Machine Field went there. In comparison, there were more Cultivators that frequented the planet.

Yellowsand Planet consists of 70% land and 30% water. Then dividing the land was 70% desert and 30% mountains. Its years lasted for 12 months with ten of them filled with hurricanes and two months where it rained.

The winds that blew on the planet weren’t ordinary winds, they were violent ones. These were the type of winds that would destroy a human body upon contact. Even experts wouldn’t be able to last long once they were buffeted by these winds. And eventually, their bodies would end up drying up before they die.

Generally, such unforgiving environment wouldn’t be able to support life. However, the planet actually had a lot of lifeforms, both fauna and flora.

There was nothing else to say about plants since they could live in the most extreme of environments. And on this planet, even the most common grass had strong medicinal characteristics.

The most famous aspect about Yellowsand Planet was one of the animals living there, the Hurricane Beasts! Nobody knew how these beasts were able to survive such a terrible environment. And even while being hit by merciless winds, they were still able to move freely and unfettered.

And since they were living in a terrible environment, they evolved into strong beings. Even the smallest and weakest one of them were at level 1 strength. It was also rumored that the strongest beast could be considered a powerful expert in the Cultivation Realm.

But what was peculiar about these beasts was the fact that even if they had the strength, they still wouldn’t leave the planet.

With all these things added together, Yellowsand Planet became quite famous not only in the Machine Field, but in the entire World of Cultivation. Every year there would be plenty of people who would go to the planet and take risks to harvest some plants. This was because the planet’s plants fetch a very high price in the market.

When Zhao Hai heard Cadjo say that the elimination round would happen in Yellowsand Planet, he couldn’t help but stare. The planet was infamous for being unforgiving. There were plenty who risked entering the planet for riches, with only a few managing to survive. And more importantly, among these risk takers were famous individuals in the Cultivation Realm. There was no exception to who survived or died in that place.

Zhao Hai frowned and asked, “Are they treating Yellowsand Planet lightly? What results do they want to see? Or do they want all of us to die there?”

Cadjo smiled bitterly and said, “This time, the number of participants in the qualifiers had exceeded 100 thousand. Can you imagine thinning these amount of people and leaving only 150 people behind? Among these 150 people, 100 are the official participants in the Six Realm Beginner Competition while 50 are reserves. Because of the amount of participants, the committee decided to choose Yellowsand Planet for the competition. But you don’t need to worry. The place that the committee chose is a relatively safe place in the planet.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I’m not worried about myself, I’m concerned about the other participants. The participants are mostly comprised of elites from External Halls. If a lot of these people die, then it wouldn’t be good for the Machine Field. This survival elimination round is borderline unfair. We not only have to face our opponents, we would also face the environment and the beasts. Even the top ten participants wouldn’t be able to hold out for long when faced with those beasts. If one of those ten gets killed by a beast, then it would decrease our chances of winning against the other realms. I really don’t know what the idiots of the committee are thinking about, to actually come up with a stupid idea.”

Cadjo couldn’t help but bitterly smile. To be honest, he also didn’t approve of this arrangement. However, it was easy for people to speak than to be heard. He gave his opinion to the committee only to be stopped and said that luck was a part of one’s strength.

Cadjo thought that this reason was simply fart. However, he didn’t have any means to change the decision. He could only accept it or have his participants withdraw.

Desbarres sighed and said, “Forget it, if someone really dies, then that’s their bad luck. Those fellows in the committee had their heads too high that they won’t listen to us. The survival elimination will only last for three days. You only need to survive against the beasts for three days and then you’ll be picked up after. And if you feel that you can no longer last, you can release a signal and someone will fetch you. However, all those who needed rescue would be eliminated.”

Cadjo said, “Although three days isn’t long, it isn’t short either. After all, it is Yellowsand Planet. And after three days, those who didn’t die nor eliminated will enter a formal competition.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. In any case, it won’t affect me. We should inform the others about this so that we can team up. This way, everyone can have more opportunities to survive.”

Cadjo’s expression changed as he said, “Little Hai, you can’t. You’re the family’s biggest hope. If you join up with the others, then they would drag you down. You’re biggest priority is surviving, understood?”

When Zhao Hai heard Cadjo, he knew that he couldn’t say anything to change his mind. However, he still said, “I’m aware of that. But General Manager, I think it’s still better to group up at the very beginning. I’ll try to help them any way I can.”

Cadjo smiled bitterly and said, “Even if I agree, it is still impossible. You aren’t permitted to bring any electronics to the planet and each participant will be randomly assigned to a transport ship. It’s impossible to team up in a short time. Because of this, I didn’t consider forming teams.”

When Zhao Hai heard Cadjo, he couldn’t help but bitterly smile. It seems like the committee really wants the participants to suffocate and die. They even removed any means to better survive the situation.

Chapter 1163: Entering Yellowsand Planet

Zhao Hai was currently calmly sitting inside his room in a ship. This room wasn’t big, only at about 20 square meters. Moreover, he wasn’t the only one in the room. All in all, the room accommodated four people. They lived together in bunk beds stuck on the wall.

Zhao Hai didn’t know anyone in the room with him. Although he scanned the information about the participants, he didn’t pay any attention to them.

But still, Laura and the others reminded Zhao Hai to leave a good impression. Therefore, when Zhao Hai entered the room, he greeted everyone inside in a friendly manner. However, what met him were hostile gazes. Naturally, since they were hostile, Zhao Hai didn’t care about them anymore.

Zhao Hai also knew why they were like this. Although they were roommates today, when the match starts, they would be enemies. There was no need to maintain any friendly attitude towards each other.

This time, Cadjo and Margaret weren’t with him. There were 100 ships that set off from Machine Field Planet to send Zhao Hai and the others to Yellowsand Planet. Then after that, they would be left alone to fend off against the planet’s dangers.

Although there was quite a distance between Yellowsand Planet and Machine Field Planet, the travel between the two planets went peacefully. After all, these 100 ships were sent from the capital. Nobody would dare touch a fleet like this.

It took the fleet ten days altogether to reach Yellowsand Planet. However, Zhao Hai’s silver needles were faster than the ships. They arrived at the planet sooner and began to do a search on the area.

The ships stopped right outside the planet’s atmosphere as Zhao Hai and the others were grouped up in their ship’s decompression chamber. There were 1,000 other participants inside the ship Zhao Hai was in. However, Zhao Hai didn’t know any of them, none of the top ten experts were here.

At this time a Mage walked over and said, “All of you will be staying inside Yellowsand Planet for three days. These are your transmitters. You need to have them on your body at all times, and they cannot be placed inside your spatial equipment. Not only do you need to survive for three days, you also need to protect these devices. If we lose contact with your device for an hour, then we’ll take it that you failed and you will be rescued. There is also a rescue button on the device. If you feel like you need to forfeit, then you can use it so that someone can fetch you. But if you use this function, then it means that you’ve forfeited. Are we clear?”

Seeing Zhao Hai and the others nod, the Mage added, “Then take these transmitters. Remember, you can’t hide them inside your spatial equipment. If you place them inside, and we don’t detect your signal for an hour, then you’ll be eliminated.” Then he proceeded to give everyone their own transmitters.

These transmitters looked like small badges. One couldn’t even see any antenna on it. However, nobody dared to neglect this thing since it was related to their future.

Zhao Hai also received his own transmitter. Before long, the Mage said, “Start the signal.” Then just as his voice fell, everyone’s transmitter flashed for a moment before it returned to its original look.

The Mage looked at everyone and said, “There’s no need to worry about your transmitters being faulty. If your transmitter is proven to be faulty with no external influences, then you will immediately pass the test. Alright, prepare yourself. We’re opening the decompression chamber.” Then after he said that, the Mage left the decompression chamber.

Zhao Hai looked at the others around him and smiled. Then he attached his transmitter on his robe and stood in place. He waited for the decompression chamber to open.

Before long, the decompression chamber was opened and Zhao Hai flew out of the ship. Not too far from where he appeared was Yellowsand Planet. This planet was much bigger than Machine Field Planet and Dark Demon Planet. Moreover, it wasn’t in a scale of two. At the very least, it was bigger than Dark Demon planet by ten times. This caused Zhao Hai to be surprised.

But what surprised ZHao Hai even more was the yellow surface of the planet. There was no other color seen, only yellow. Zhao Hai knew that the color of the planet was caused by the huge sandstorm that buffeted the entire planet. And it happened to be the time where the sandstorm was at its peak.

At the same time, Zhao Hai noted a row of flashing red signals in a circle on the surface of the planet. Zhao Hai and the others were already informed that these signals showed the area where they should be in. If people died outside this area, then the committee wouldn’t be responsible for them.

Zhao Hai also noticed that the other participants were heading out of their own ships. Moreover, everyone was staring at Yellowsand Planet. Zhao Hai didn’t care about the others as he flew towards the planet. The Space had already mapped the planet, so there was no need for Zhao Hai to be cautious.

Seeing Zhao Hai flying towards the planet, those who were still observing couldn’t help but stare. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to move forward this quickly. However, Zhao Hai’s actions caused the others to move forward  as well.

Before long, Zhao Hai entered the planet’s atmosphere. As he plunged into the planet, Zhao Hai casted a 5-layer formation. The formation was a yellow shield that surrounded his body.

Upon entering the planet’s atmosphere, Zhao Hai immediately felt the winds surround him. These winds were very strange. Even if the shield blocked the force of the wind, Zhao Hai could still feel a faint trace of coldness passing through his body.

Zhao Hai knew that this was the special effect of the hurricanes. But even if he doesn’t care, this didn’t mean that nobody else did. At this time, he heard a prompt, “Massive amounts of harmful energy detected entering the host’s body. Extracting energy. Analyzing. Energy contains radioactive elements that are harmful to human blood. Making antidote to neutralize the energy.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect the Space to take action against Yellowsand Planet’s winds. Zhao Hai looked around him and saw that even if the others had followed him in, they were still far from reaching his position. It seems like they were afraid that he would attack them. Zhao Hai didn’t care about it and just continued to descend down the planet.

It also needed to be said that as Zhao Hai was getting closer to the surface, the winds were also becoming stronger. By the time he reached the ground, the winds were big enough to pulverize stone into sand.

The moment Zhao Hai stepped into the surface, he immediately opened a rift. Just as the sandstorm entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Harmful energy storm with polluted yellow sand detected. Energy may be used to attack the enemy. The yellow sand can also be used for refining. Violent wind element detected, combining with the wind bead. Combination successful. Harmful energy storm is now ineffective against the host.”

When he heard this prompt, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pause for a moment. Then he was reminded about the Wind Bead inside the Space. It seems like he was now immune to the storm because of it.

Sure enough, after the Space’s prompt, Zhao Hai could no longer feel any wind around him. Even if it was windy, the least he could feel was a gentle breeze. Moreover, the cold he felt before had completely disappeared.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That was great. It seems like we’ll have to collect more of this sand into the Space.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift, taking in more wind and sand into the Space. After some time, the Space issued another prompt, “Since the host has absorbed a large amount of negative energy and irradiated sand, the host can now designate an area inside the Space for a sandstorm. This sandstorm can generate negative energy storms and irradiated sand on its own. These generated resources will be immediately stored into the inventory.”

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he smiled and closed the spatial rift. There was no need to absorb more.

Zhao Hai looked all around him, then he smiled and said, “I heard that the hurricane beasts here are very strong. I need to collect a few of them for the Space.” Then his body moved as he flew away.

At Yellowsand Planet’s ground level, eyesight could no longer be used as a means of perception. The dizzying hurricanes blowing in all directions made visibility less than 5 meters. In this case, it was impossible to use one’s eyes in order to spot any enemies. One could only depend on their own spiritual force.

However, Zhao Hai discovered that the hurricanes had a property to suppress spiritual force. In the past, Zhao Hai could stretch his spiritual force to 10 thousand kilometers. But now, this range was reduced to 10.

Then all of a sudden, Zhao Hai stopped and then quickly moved upwards. And just as he moved, a huge figure emerged from the ground beneath him. If Zhao Hai didn’t quickly move, then he might have already been swallowed by the thing that came out.

When Zhao Hai moved to the side, he managed to get a glimpse at the creature that attacked him. It was a giant worm looking thing. It was much much larger than any worm he saw before. The tip of its head spread out like a flower, making its mouth bigger than its body. Most importantly, its teeth were stacked into 18 layers. All of the teeth were creepily moving around like a meat grinder. Seeing the glint on their tips, one could see how sharp each tooth was.[1]

Zhao Hai was now 100 meters off the ground. However, the worm was still catching up to him as though it had endless length. Naturally, the worm was more than 100 meters, enough to call it a giant.

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows. He discovered that this worm wasn’t that simple. This was because his spiritual force failed to detect its approach. He only discovered it when it was drilling up from underground. It’s ability to hide itself was too formidable!

* * *

I reckon it’s this = The Sandworm(https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmonsterlegacy.files.wordpress.com%2F2014%2F04%2Fsandwormcropped.jpg&f=1&nofb=1)

Chapter 1164: Formidable Yellowsand Worm

While Zhao Hai was wrapped up in his thoughts, the worm spun and bit towards him. Zhao Hai immediately cast a 5-layer formation and shot a fireball towards the worm’s mouth.

Zhao Hai looked at the worm but couldn’t see its eyes, so he aimed for its mouth. When the fireball was sent out, the worm swallowed it in one bite and then closed its mouth.

When he saw the worm swallow the fireball, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sneer. His fireballs weren’t something that could be swallowed.

After the worm swallowed the fireball, Zhao Hai found out that the worm had no bones and its skin was transparent. He could clearly see the fireball going down the worm’s body and towards its stomach.

The worm looks like it had swallowed a chug of water and was satisfied. When it closed its mouth, it slowly sank back into the sand. At this moment, the fireball suddenly exploded.

Zhao Hai expected the worm to be instantly killed by the blast. However, the worm’s stomach just bulged and then shrank back in. Then it opened its mouth and burped black smoke before going back down underground.

Zhao Hai just stared at the worm as it returned to the sand. This worm was too absurd, it could actually eat everything. His fireball should be able to roast the worm on the spot. Instead, it was eaten. Wasn’t the worm a bit too strong?

At this time, Laura’s voice was heard inside Zhao Hai’s mind, “Brother Hai, that thing is called a yellowsand worm. They’re very famous in Yellowsand Planet. The defensive ability of these beasts is formidable. However, their offensive method is simple. This thing wouldn’t attack people under normal circumstances. They could eat anything. If they don’t find anything else to eat, then they would consume sand. This thing is very difficult to kill. Even if they are bisected, they could still survive.”

Zhao Hai responded,”There’s such a thing? It seems like it would be good if we take this thing to the Space. Cai’er, take that thing to the Space.”

Cai’er said, “Young Master, it’s about 200 meters underground. However, this yellowsand worm is more than 1000 meters long. Do you really want to bring it into the Space?”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai immediately reacted, “It’s more than 1000 meters long? Are you sure? My goodness. Interesting. It’s about ten meters thick but it’s actually more than 1000 meters long? I have to take it to the Space.”

Then his figure moved and burrowed into the yellow sand. Then Zhao Hai discovered that although the sand looked like ordinary sand, it was actually very different. This yellow sand had faint traces of energy that wasn’t good for humans.

Zhao Hai knew that this energy was the negative energy that was mentioned by the Space. It’s a kind of radiation that would adversely affect anyone who came in contact with it for a long time.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai penetrated 200 meters below ground. He saw the worm there, motionless. However, it completely blended into the surrounding sand. Not even Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was able to feel it out.

Naturally, the worm was able to feel Zhao Hai’s existence. It squirmed its body but it didn’t attack Zhao Hai. After circling the worm, Zhao Hai knew how long this thing really was. It was actually 1500 meters long.

After taking a careful look at the worm, Zhao Hai opened a spatial rift. The rift went along the worm’s body from the head to the tail. Before long, the entire worm was sent to the Space.

As soon as the yellowsand worm entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Discovered a sandworm that has mutated because of radiation. Mutation allowed the creature to be extremely tenacious. At the same time, it is able to absorb anything in its body. Host may breed it inside the Space. Mutated sandworm has been placed inside the Space’s shop. Host may purchase creature in the shop.”

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai had Cai’er pick an area inside the Space for the sandstorm. Now he has a constant source for violent winds and yellow sand. He also placed the sandworm to live in that area.

After taking the yellowsand worm, Zhao Hai flew out and swept the surroundings with his spiritual force. Upon finding nothing else nearby, he immediately flew away.

When he had flown for about five kilometers, Zhao Hai suddenly stopped. This was because he could discover something in front of him, and it looked quite familiar. On the yellow sand was a branch-like thing, and on its top was a small flower.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he smiled as he asked Cai’er, “Cai’er, is that a sandworm?”

Cai’er looked at the monitor, then she nodded and said, “Young Master, it’s a sandworm. That small flower on its head is used to attract prey. It’s just that we haven’t noticed it before. Do you want to take it to the Space as well?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No, I want to see how other people would deal with it. Right, what level was that sandworm from earlier?” This time, Laura replied, “Brother Hai, there isn’t much information about yellowsand worms in the internet. It was only rated as a grade 1 beast.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Grade 1 beast? How is that possible?

Laura smiled and said, “It’s possible. It’s really a grade 1 beast. And it’s because of its growth potential. As long as it gets left alone, it could reach 10 thousand meters long. When that time comes, nothing in Yellowsand Planet could threaten it. There’s a record of one appearing in the past. In the end, the Cultivation Realm sent more than a hundred Nascent Soul Experts to kill it.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect the yellowsand worm to be this formidable. More than a hundred Nascent Soul Experts, what kind of fighting power is that? Even the Ashley Family would be exterminated with that much fighting force. And it was used to eliminate one yellowsand worm? Isn’t this worm too overpowered?

One must know that the stages in the Cultivation Realm were divided into Body Tempering, Qi Condensation, Foundation Establishment, Core Formation, Nascent Soul, Transcending Tribulation, Severed Spirit, Immortality, and much more. However, there were clear dividers between these stages. Not to mention Immortals, if a sect had a few Transcending Tribulation experts, it was already considered good. In the Cultivation Realm, Nascent Soul Experts were overlords of a region. They can open their own sects and establish their own school of thought.

Although Zhao Hai was already very strong, he estimates that his level could only contend against Core Formation experts. And most Core Formation experts would find it very hard to contend against Nascent Soul Experts.

So after hearing about the yellowsand worm’s capabilities, Zhao Hai was truly startled. But in the end, he couldn’t help but rejoice. If he grew a few sandworms, then he would have helpers in the future.

At this time, Laura’s voice was heard once more, “It’s also said that the yellowsand worm is only considered dangerous whenever it’s hungry. Otherwise, it would stay docile and will not actively attack anyone.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “This yellowsand worm is interesting. Alright, let’s wait here and watch the fun. In any case, we’ve already mapped the planet. Moreover, the beasts here aren’t something we can just find at will. We’ll stay in this worm’s territory for now. And when we grasp the planet’s strength, we’ll go out and take some of the planet’s beasts.

Laura nodded, “From what I can see, the reason the committee chose this area is because it is the territory of the sandworms. These worms don’t attack people most of the time, therefore, there won’t be too much casualties.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “That might be it. I’ll stay here for three days, but I cannot enter the Space during that time. It’s a pity that you can’t come out here and join me.”

Laura and the others laughed, then Megan said, “Brother Hai, you came here for the competition, not for vacation. If we go out to join you, then you’re just insulting the other participants.”

Zhao Hai laughed, then he took some furniture from the Space and sat down. Then he pulled out a pot of tea and slowly drank it. His easy manner doesn’t match with his surroundings.

If other participants saw Zhao Hai, then they would certainly feel irritated. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care. Yellowsand Planet was filled with danger. Take the yellowsand worm for example, it would take him quite the effort to deal with it. And if he really met a very powerful beast that he couldn’t deal with, he would only hide inside the Space and be eliminated. Therefore, there was no need to run around the entire time.

While Zhao Hai was leisurely spending his time, the other participants were starting to feel the pressure. They didn’t have the Wind Bead nor the Space to overcome any obstacles for them. Therefore, they met the full brunt of the planet’s winds.

The hurricanes in yellowsand planet had sand mixed in with them, making it enough to be called a formidable weapon. Most Mages and Warriors wouldn’t be able to survive inside it for a long time. Even if they were powerful experts, they would still need a shield to support them from time to time. After all, prolonged exposure to the sands would cause damage to one’s body.

Although the Machine Field’s cultivation method was different than the Cultivation Realm’s, they still knew about the Cultivation Realm’s methods. In the Cultivation Realm, the most powerful attacks weren’t the ones with elemental attributes, instead, they were techniques infused with special qi.

These types of methods were the most effective when it came to attack. For example, there were techniques called yin attacks in the Cultivation Realm. There were a lot of sects who had these methods. There were also variation in naming this attack, some sects called it dark attacks. But no matter what they were called, these attacks merged qi into an ordinary attack. Because of this, the effects were formidable.

Something similar to evil qi was astral qi. Both of these things could enhance offensive power. If one merges evil qi into their attacks, then they would be yin attacks. If astral qi was merged in, then that would be astral attacks.[1]

However, merging evil qi or astral qi requires one to find a source for them. Then they would have to condense evil qi and astral qi into their bodies slowly.

Also, condensing these two energies into one’s body was a very dangerous matter. If ten were to try this action, then four would succeed while the other six would die. One could see from this point the risks in using evil qi and astral qi.

As for the Machine Field, they didn’t have a method to merge these energies into their bodies. Because of this, both Mages and Warriors could only rely on protective shields in order to survive. Even then, it wasn’t an easy matter, astral qi attacks kill without shedding blood.

…………………..

Wan Xiang considers himself as an unlucky person. He ascended more than three years ago. Despite his short time of ascension, he was still able to reach level three and would reach level 4 soon. It can be said that he was a genius. However, he wasn’t valued by his family. This was because his family was strong, there were already plenty of people like him. The strongest participant that their family sent for the competition was a level 4 expert.

Wan Xiang’s attendance in this competition was supposed to be his lucky break. If he could obtain good results, then this status in the family would improve. This was a very good thing for Wan Xiang. He even believed that he was blessed by good luck. But upon arriving at Yellowsand Planet, he discovered that he was actually very unlucky.

Not long after he flew into Yellowsand Planet, he was met by an attack from a yellowsand worm. In the end, he was able to run away after spending a huge amount of his battle qi. Although he was drinking recovery potions all this time, supporting his protective shield reduced his strength to 70% of what was before.

Wan Xiang sighed as he carefully advanced. He needs to survive in this place for three days, otherwise he would be eliminated. If he was out of the competition by the first round, then he would certainly gain zero benefits from the family.

Wan Xiang released his spiritual force as he advanced, paying careful attention to his surroundings. Although the spiritual force of Warriors were inferior compared to Mages, for all Ascenders, their spiritual force was already enough to maneuver themselves on the planet.

As he carefully moved along, Wan Xiang suddenly encountered something. When he saw this, his expression couldn’t help but change!

* * *

“Astral” might be a temporary term, I couldn’t find other meanings to the character Gāng(罡) other than being related to planets or constellations or internal gods.

Chapter 1165: Formidable Supporting Magic Formation

There was a very small tree in front, it was yellow. In fact, most of the plants in Yellowsand Planet were almost this color. Therefore, there was nothing strange about it.

And in this small yellow tree was a little yellow flower. This flower shook amidst the wind, it might even look as if it would fall at any time.

However, Wan Xiang clearly knew that it was impossible for this flower to fall. This was because this flower was part of a yellowsand worm’s body.

One shouldn’t underestimate the yellowsand worm’s bait. This little flower would exude a very unusual fragrance. As long as a beast smelt it, they will most likely run over. Naturally, those beasts who did became food for the worm.

In the beginning, people didn’t know about this ability from the yellowsand worm. Back then, when people killed a yellowsand worm, they would use these little flowers as accessories. But they didn’t know that it was actually attracting large numbers of beasts. It didn’t take long before people became aware of the little flower’s use.

Now, whenever people see these little flowers, they know that they should walk around it. The area around the flower would be the domain of a yellowsand worm. Yellowsand worms became beasts that nobody would provoke in Yellowsand Planet.

These worms generally won’t attack people. And since they had no obvious weakness, they were very difficult to kill. Their tough skins also dissuade people from hunting them.

Moreover, it was very difficult for people to find yellowsand worms. Once they hide in the sand, they would immediately become one with their surroundings. It was common for people to lose sight of them, even if they were Mages with formidable spiritual force.

Additionally, the speed of the worms under the sand was quicker than human flight. They had a strange body structure that allowed them to swallow sand and eject it from their behind. The process of ejecting sand would propel the worm further, increasing its speed. They depended on this trait in order to traverse the sand underneath the surface.

Another reason why nobody provoked the yellowsand worms was because there were no indications whether a worm was only a few tens of meters long or 10 thousand meters. Most of its body was buried under the sand, and one couldn’t use their spiritual force to find it.

Because of this, when Wan Xiang saw the little flower, he looked as though he saw a severe flood coming or a violent beast. He immediately turned and circled around the flower.

Just as Wan Xiang stepped forward, he stopped and couldn’t help but shake his head. It was as if he found something unreasonable. He couldn’t believe what he just saw.

However, he immediately found out that he wasn’t seeing things wrong. There was actually a person in front of him, sitting on a chair and sipping tea!

A man just drank tea as though nothing strange was going on around him. He seems to be unaware that he was at Yellowsand Planet and was surrounded by violent winds. If someone did it at this environment, then they would have been eating sand!

However, the person was really drinking tea. Moreover, he had a chair to sit on. This caused Wan Xiang to stare, he didn’t know how to react.

Wan Xiang already knew that this Mage wasn’t someone ordinary. And if this was the case, then he might have already been discovered. So now, Wan Xiang was stuck on how to face this person.

He was currently in Yellowsand Planet, and each person here was a competitor. With this in mind, he was left with two choices, either to run or to fight.

But while Wan Xiang was having doubts on what to do, the Mage kept leisurely sitting there. It was as though he had nothing to be afraid of. Wan Xiang wasn’t sure if he can win if he rushed towards the Mage.

Before Wan Xiang arrived at the planet, he already had an understanding of the powerful contestants. And since he knew about the ten geniuses, then he was naturally aware of the Ashley Family’s Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s name had already spread in the Machine Field. A level 4 Mage that had ascended just a few months ago, this was an unprecedented event. Therefore, Zhao Hai can be said to be the most talented contestant in this competition.

A genius character such as Zhao Hai wasn’t someone that Wan Xiang could contend against. However, Zhao Hai’s quick rise was precisely the reason why some people doubted his strength. How strong would a person be just a few months after ascending? How far could he have progressed in Magic Theory?

Wan Xiang was one of those who didn’t believe that Zhao Hai was strong. In his mind, Zhao Hai might just have a rare treasure on his body.

Seeing Zhao Hai now, Wan Xiang’s ideas were solidified. Yellowsand Planet was covered with violent winds, yet Zhao Hai was leisurely sipping tea as though no wind came to touch him. Wasn’t this very strange?

“He really does have a rare treasure!” Wan Xiang was even more assured of this idea.

With this thought in mind, Wan Xiang’s greed couldn’t help but emerge. He immediately kicked off and flew towards Zhao Hai, his sword already drawn.

Naturally, Zhao Hai had already discovered Wan Xiang. Moreover, upon seeing him, Laura immediately gave him his detailed information. One could say that Wan Xiang wasn’t simple. He was from the Shui Family, the most powerful family in the Water Temple. Even the Ashley Family wasn’t at its level. The Shui Family was able to send 15 people to attend the realm qualifiers. Of the 15, 14 were level 3 while the remaining one was level 4. Although this person wasn’t among the ten great experts, this person’s strength was still very high.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t really care. He didn’t mind attacking the Shui Family. In this elimination round, him not provoking others was already their fortune. If he did go out of his way to attack people, then the participants would suffer extreme bad luck.

Zhao Hai wasn’t initially planning to kill Wan Xiang. In his opinion, this elimination round was very unfair. Even if they had some skills, resisting the winds and the sandstorm wasn’t easy. And with beasts scattered around the land, surviving was already hard. And there was still the last element which was the other participants.

But even if one doesn’t want to hurt the tiger, the tiger would still harm humans. Zhao Hai didn’t want to deal with Wan Xiang, but Wan Xiang wanted to deal with him. When Zhao Hai saw Wan Xiang pulling his sword out, he couldn’t help but sigh deeply inside.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move. He still sat there, with his teacup in hand. The yellow sand mixed with the wind made a very magnificent view of the surroundings.

Wan Xiang waved his sword and sent a sword qi towards Zhao Hai. Seeing the attack, Zhao Hai sighed and waved his hand, releasing a 5-layer formation. The formation immediately became a huge shield, blocking the sword qi in front of him. Only a few sparks appeared on the shield before peace returned. There wasn’t even a scratch on the shield.

Upon seeing this situation, Wan Xiang’s complexion changed. Although he just attacked, he was able to see Zhao Hai’s strength. Zhao Hai wasn’t someone that can be easily dealt with.

Wan Xiang and Li Kui, the most powerful beginner in the Shui Family, had compared notes before. Li Kun was also a Mage. Although he specialized in the water element, his ice shield was something that could compare to metal element shields. During their spar, Wan Xiang was able to shatter Li Kui’s shield. Li Kui even said that Wan Xiang’s offensive strength was very formidable, and that he had a rare talent for offensive attacks.

But now that he was faced against Zhao Hai, the offensive strength that he was so proud of was actually rendered useless. He wasn’t even able to leave a trace on Zhao Hai’s shield.

But what Wan Xiang didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was also very surprised. This was because the shield that he sent out wasn’t an ordinary 5-layer shield. This one was a revised version that included a supporting magic formation. According to Zhao Hai’s estimates, 5-layer formations should be able to contend against level 3 Warriors. However, it was impossible for it to be unscathed, it should have shattered alongside the sword qi.

And now that supporting formations were added, the shield actually blocked Wan Xiang’s sword easily. There wasn’t even a scratch on the shield. Moreover, the amount Zhao Hai used to release the formation was a third of what 5-layer formations usually required. This result was too astonishing!

Arranging formation sets was a great subject of study. Choosing five formations from thousands of formations, putting them together, have them display the most amount of power while also maintaining the proper balance was something that was easier said than done.

The five formations that Zhao used were a metal-element supplying formation, metal-element solidifying formation, a reinforcing supporting formation, a strengthening supporting formation, and a metal-element shield formation.

This wasn’t the case before, instead of two supporting formations, the other two formations used were metal-element strengthening formations. Their effect wasn’t as good and they used up more spiritual force.

It was through this revised formation that Zhao Hai understood how formidable supporting formations were. At the same time, it made Zhao Hai happy. These supporting formations would increase his strength by two-folds. He was now more confident in dealing with his enemies.

Seeing his attack having no effect, Wan Xiang didn’t stay and instead turned around and left. Looking at Wan Xiang escape, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Then he coldly snorted as he sent a sword qi towards Wan Xiang.

This was Zhao Hai’s first time using sword qi in the outside world. This sword was also sent through a formation set. However, the formation used to strengthen his sword qi was different from the conventional formations. He also included supporting formations in his sword, causing its effects to be elevated.

Chapter 1166: Testing the Body Tempering Technique

Wan Xiang knew that it was impossible for him to match Zhao Hai. He was someone who was tactful of his actions. He would do his best to avoid extreme danger. This was the reason why he immediately ran away when his attack was effortlessly blocked.

However, just as he turned around, he suddenly felt the hair on his back go up. Wan Xiang was an experienced Warrior who had developed his own instincts. He knew that an attack was coming for him.

Wan Xiang didn’t immediately turn around but he continually waved his sword and sent sword qi flying behind him. Then he took a quick glance back and saw something he didn’t expect.

This time, Wan Xiang couldn’t help but pause. He was almost certain that a magic spell was coming for him. However, what he saw wasn’t a spell, instead it was sword qi. A completely solid sword qi.

Wan Xiang already noticed that the three sword qi that he sent was already destroyed. Despite his surprise, Wan Xiang was still able to use his sword to block the incoming sword qi.

Clang! A sound of clashing swords rang out. And at the same time, Wan Xiang’s figure accelerated forward. This wasn’t due to Wan Xiang increasing his speed, but instead it was because of the collision that just happened.

Wan Xiang felt his vitality take a huge dive. Even if he felt worse, he still used his own blood essence to propel himself further on.

The only thing inside Wan Xiang’s mind was to escape as soon as possible and as far as possible from Zhao Hai. Then he would find a place to hide and survive for three days. He needs to tell the family that Zhao Hai was both a Mage and a Warrior. Perhaps he might receive a reward for this information.

Any influence attached great importance to information, especially those that involved talented characters. If one can uncover a previously unknown aspect of a great talent, then the family would most likely give a reward.

Zhao Hai was considered to be a highly valued talent. He was a level 4 Mage just after a few months of ascending. It was a talent that nobody would believe the first time they heard about it.

And now, Wan Xiang was actually able to discover that Zhao Hai was not only a Mage, but his skill as a Warrior wasn’t any worse than his skills as a Mage. This information was too important for the Shui family.

It’s just a pity that Zhao Hai would never let him go. Zhao Hai tried to attack Wan Xiang using his sword qi to see how strong it was. And it seems like it was very good.

Zhao Hai had the same thought as Wan Xiang. If he let Wan Xiang escape, then the whole Machine Field would know that he was a Warrior as well. This wasn’t good, as far as he knew, there were only very few people who were both a Mage and a Warrior.

Zhao Hai moved and appeared in front of Wan Xiang, then he attacked. He didn’t use Liquid Silver this time, instead he tried his new fist technique.

The fist technique was a separate aspect of the tempering method. And only when the Stellar Transformation Body Tempering Technique was used that the fist technique would show results. Otherwise, it would just be a common fist technique.

The attacks of the fist technique weren’t the same as battle qi. When the fist techniques were carried out, they follow through the system widely used in the cultivation realm. This method was much more complicated than the ones Warriors used.

The cultivation realm uses the meridians of one’s body to transfer energy from acupoint to acupoint. These acupoints were directly connected to one another but they formed a small cycle. After each cycle of energy, a person’s body would be geared to do their attack.

In the Machine Field, this action was done with the support of weapons, which was an external influence. As for the Stellar Body Tempering Fist, it uses one’s meridians to circulate qi and then send the energy in one go. This belonged to internal strength, which was different.

When Wan Xiang saw Zhao Hai appear in front of him, his eyes shrank. He was a level 3 Warrior, but he wasn’t able to see Zhao Hai move.

At this moment, Wan Xiang saw Zhao Hai wave his fist. He couldn’t help but stare. There were very few Warriors in the Machine Field that attacked using their fists. Even if they did, they would have a gauntlet or something to aid their attack. However, Zhao Hai was actually barehanded. This caused Wan Xiang to be surprised.

Wan Xiang looked at Zhao Hai’s fist as though it was a joke. This was because he couldn’t feel any energy coming from Zhao Hai’s fist.

But just as he was about to open his mouth, Wan Xiang suddenly felt an extremely powerful qi coming towards him. This strength wasn’t sharp like a sword, but it was imposing like a mountain. With such a colossal energy coming towards him, Wan Xiang found himself having trouble breathing.

Wan Xiang didn’t have any time to be surprised, he immediately used his last remaining energy to wave his sword. Then he released a huge amount of qi towards Zhao Hai.

However, the sword qi became like a bubble when it met Zhao Hai’s fist. When the sword qi was destroyed, Zhao Hai didn’t give Wan Xiang any time to make another move as he immediately condensed his energy and charged towards Wan Xiang’s direction.

Wan Xiang discovered that he had made a huge mistake. He shouldn’t have sent an attack. Now, he didn’t have any energy left to defend against Zhao Hai.

Wan Xiang suddenly felt his qi resisting the attack. But just like a fly caught in a spider web, he wasn’t able to struggle away from Zhao Hai’s attack.

A large amount of energy kept pouring inside Wan Xiang’s body. When he wasn’t able to resist anymore, a bang was heard. As Zhao Hai’s qi flooded Wan Xiang’s body, all of Wan Xiang’s bones and blood were shattered. His skeletons and meridians were torn into shreds. After experiencing a spike of intense pain, Wan Xiang’s vision turned black.

Zhao Hai looked at the mess on the ground. Wan Xiang became a huge splat on the sandy soil. This was the first time that he used the body tempering fist against an enemy. He didn’t expect the amount of qi to be this overbearing. It completely destroyed Wan Xiang’s body. It can be said that only Wan Xiang’s skin could be seen, everything else has been turned into a bloody mush.

Zhao Hai sighed and waved his hand, receiving Wan Xiang’s sword and storage ring. Although Wan Xiang was wearing chain armor, that armor has also been destroyed by Zhao Hai’s fist, it was rendered completely useless. As he was burying Wan Xiang using earth element magic, Zhao Hai thought that he needed to tone down the amount of energy used whenever he attacked using his fists. It would be a complete waste if he wasn’t able to turn his enemies into Undead!

After processing Wan Xiang’s corpse, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to the storage ring. Upon careful inspection, the ring caught Zhao Hai’s interest. This was because Wan Xiang’s ring had something that cultivators normally had, a spiritual seal!

Spatial items with spiritual seals were quite rare in the Machine Field, how was Wan Xiang able to get his hands on it? While he was thinking about this, Zhao Hai took out some Everpresent Ancient Sand and then wiped it on the ring. The ring emitted black smoke as the spiritual imprint was removed.

Then Zhao Hai used his spiritual force to scan the contents of the ring. Wan Xiang’s ring was full of potions. Some of these potions restored energy, some were antidotes, and some healed wounds. They were basically things that people would take with them on a journey. Besides the potions, there were also some equipment inside like weapons and armor.

However, what took Zhao Hai’s interest was a jade slip. This jade slip looked ancient and didn’t emit any energy. Nevertheless, it still managed to attract Zhao Hai. This was because Wan Xiang wouldn’t just bring a random jade slip with him. Moreover, jade slips were very rare in the Machine Field.

In the Cultivation Realm, jade slips were generally used to record things. On the other hand, there was little use for these slips in the Machine Field, and there wasn’t a huge market for it. But one couldn’t deny that jade slips were very convenient. One would only need to use their spiritual force to read everything that was recorded inside these jade slips. And this method was much more effective that reading through text.

Zhao Hai took the jade slip out before tossing the spatial ring to the Space. Then he used his spiritual force to scan it.

But not long after he began, Zhao Hai paused. This was because the jade slip was also protected by a spiritual seal. But this time, Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised. Almost all things connected to the Cultivation Realm had these seals. This was especially true for important items. If one decided to forcefully break through these seals, then they would risk destroying that item.

So when Zhao Hai discovered the seal, his interest was piqued. He immediately took out some everpresent ancient sand in order to remove the spiritual imprint.

Black smoke kept coming out of the jade slip, but the imprint had yet to be removed. This caused Zhao Hai to be more interested. If the jade slip’s seal was this strong, then the thing recorded inside should be valuable. Zhao Hai was getting somewhat impatient as he looked at the imprint being erased.

As the process went on, Zhao Hai also began to discover that the ancient sand was being consumed when it removed the imprint. Each puff of black smoke took some ancient sand along with it. Before long, the amount of sand in Zhao Hai’s hand has vanished. But at the same time, the jade slip’s appearance changed. It now looked more attractive than before.

Chapter 1167: Condensed Astral Qi Art

Seeing what just happened, Zhao Hai knew that the seal has been dealt with. Then he immediately scanned the jade slip with his spiritual force. Just as his consciousness entered the slip, an explosion was heard, shaking his head. Then the five element killing formation activated and kept the danger at bay.

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately understood what just happened. The five element killing formation blocks all kinds of spiritual force that went to his head. It seems like there was something inside the jade slip that triggered the formation.

Zhao Hai took the formation down and allowed the spiritual force from the jade slip to enter his mind. Before long, writings appeared inside his head.

Zhao Hai proceeded to read through the words appearing in his mind, “Condensed Astral Art. The Heavens and the Earth are righteous, evil, arrogant, and divine. The mind should be…..”

As he contemplated on the writings, Zhao Hai finally knew what was recorded inside the jade slip. Inside was actually a secret art. It was an article detailing evil qi and astral qi. And further on, it dictates how to use them to make a life source weapon.

There weren’t only ordinary magic artifacts in the Cultivation Realm. Those that passed through evil qi or astral qi became life source artifacts. Since these artifacts passed through evil qi and astral qi, whether it be defensive or offensive strength, these artifacts were much better than ordinary ones.

It can be said that this art came at a timely moment for Zhao Hai. Both Yellowsand Planet and the Space had a non stop supply of astral qi. If he was able to make use of it, then his body would become more tenacious. And if he was able to join astral qi with his own strength, then his attacks would be more aggressive. And lastly, if he could add astral qi to his own treasures, he would be able to promote them at least a level higher.

Zhao Hai badly needed these improvements. Therefore, he really wanted to find a method to utilize astral qi.

Zhao Hai carefully looked through the secret art and found out that it was very complex. He would introduce astral qi into his meridians, then bit by bit he would merge it with his own spiritual qi.

However, this process came with a huge amount of pain. Most people wouldn’t be able to endure this type of pain. This was the main reason why most people go insane and die once they tried merging evil qi or astral qi to their bodies.

But this issue wouldn’t be a problem for Zhao Hai. He had already experienced something like this before when he was tempering his body. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about introducing astral qi to his body.

After looking through the entire secret art, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go and practice it. This was because there were still dangers in practicing this art. If people were to arrive and disturb him, then his concentration would be broken and the situation might turn sour.

But even if Zhao Hai couldn’t integrate astral qi into his own spiritual qi, he could still practice the art on some magic artifacts. Presently, Zhao Hai had Liquid Silver, which was also a magical artifact. Zhao Hai could definitely use astral qi to improve Liquid Silver. Zhao Hai believed that Liquid Silver could still become stronger.

With this though in mind, Zhao Hai sat down and then took Liquid Silver out. Then he used his spiritual force to temper liquid silver using the astral qi around him.

When Zhao Hai’s spiritual force got in contact with the astral qi, he immediately felt a great pressure pulling at it. Then Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was immediately twisted and shattered by the pressure.

However, Zhao Hai was still fine. After all, he had prepared well for this situation. Although he could feel his head ache, this pain wasn’t uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai calmed himself down and then guided the astral qi using his spiritual force. However, the result was still the same. Zhao Hai slowly learned as he failed time and time again. His failures also reinforced his spiritual force. If his previous spiritual force was a silk thread, now it was already like a metal wire.

Zhao Hai didn’t know for how long he’s been introducing astral qi to Liquid Silver, but suddenly, Liquid Silver shone with light. Then the Space issued a prompt, “New energy has been introduced to the host’s staff. The Space has judged that it is beneficial to the host. The energy’s existence has been approved. The Space will now take over in controlling the new energy.”

After hearing the prompt, Zhao Hai discovered that the astral qi no longer needed his control in order to enter Liquid Silver. Moreover, its progress was much better than when he was the one controlling it.

Zhao Hai was glad with this development. Then he sat in place to recover his spiritual force. And just as he was feeling his spiritual force, Zhao Hai discovered that his capacity had increased. Moreover, his spiritual force was more solid than before. This was completely out of his expectation.

After his spiritual force was fully restored, Zhao Hai was finally able to confirm that his spiritual force had increased. Originally, his spiritual force could support 1000-layer formations at most. But now, he could support 3000-layers with ease. Even if he cast five formations at the same time, it would still be possible for him.

And if his formation sets had supporting formations, he could cast 10,000-layer formations with no problem. And this was without Liquid Silver’s help. If he used Liquid Silver, then he could achieve 30,000 layers.

Seeing his strength increase by more than a single fold, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel ecstatic. He was worried that his spiritual force wouldn’t be able to catch up to his body’s increase in strength. But now it seems like his spiritual force had already caught up. This was absolutely good news for Zhao Hai.

Once Zhao Hai had sorted his spiritual force out, he suddenly discovered that a day had almost passed in Yellowsand Planet. This caused him to be surprised.

A day had passed but he only met Wan Xiang. Wasn’t this too strange? One must know that there were about 100 thousand participants in this region. Moreover, the region wasn’t very large. It would be very easy for two people to meet each other. But ever since the beginning, Zhao Hai had only met Wan Xiang.

At this time, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, while you were practicing, there were 50 people who scanned you with their spiritual force. However, since they don’t pose any danger, I decided not to wake you up.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he began to understand. Then he asked, “There are 50 of them? Who are they?”

Then as he said that, a list flashed inside Zhao Hai’s mind. There were detailed descriptions about the 50 people in the list. The time when they scanned Zhao Hai and for how long they kept scanning him were also listed.

Zhao Hai looked at the list and nodded, “Good. They’re lucky that they didn’t make a move. Otherwise I will have to be impolite.”

Cai’er nodded, “Young Master, there’s no need to worry. If they really dared to make a move, then we can release the Undead you captured from Tyro Planet and the Rainbow Meteorite Field. They should be enough to kill all of them.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right, just like what you said, we can just release the Undead to eliminate them.”

The Undead that Zhao Hai gained from Tyro Planet and the Rainbow Meteorite Field had preserved their original strength. This was to say that Zhao Hai had a few Undead with level 4 and level 5 strength. If people dared to attack Zhao Hai, then these Undead could just kill them.

At this time, Laura said, “Brother Hai, why don’t you try taking a stroll?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Forget it. It’s not easy to survive in this elimination round. If I went to other places, even if I don’t encounter other beasts, I would still see other participants. And in the end, I would have to defeat them. I’ll give them a chance. As long as they don’t make a move on me, then I won’t actively attack them.”

Laura paused for a moment and then she nodded, “In any case, it doesn’t matter if you meet anyone or not. And if you encounter a strong beast, even if you can run away, you would still disturb everyone around you. It would be good if you stay here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s right. I think it would be best for us if I don’t expose my strength. Therefore, we can’t catch any beasts for now. If my abilities are discovered, then I would be at a disadvantage later on. We shouldn’t forget that we cannot guarantee if the other realms are looking into the Machine Field. If they are really monitoring us, then we would be in trouble if they see my strength.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “Brother Hai, you should build a house made out of sand. If there’s an opportunity, we can head out and accompany you.”

Upon hearing Laura, Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Forget it. If we do that, we will only attract unwanted attention. It’s fine like this.”

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, but Brother Hai, you need to at least take out an umbrella and a proper chair. You should be comfortable.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, he said, “That’s a good idea. Get me an umbrella and a recliner. Right, get me some cold fruit juice as well. I’ll take the next few days as vacation time.”

When Laura and the others head this, they couldn’t help but giggle. Before long, everything Zhao Hai requested had been brought over. Zhao Hai comfortably lied down on his recliner as he sipped from his cold drink. He even looked as satisfied as someone who was on a vacation.

As Zhao Hai relaxed, several spiritual forces came to scan him. But after seeing that they weren’t Zhao Hai’s match, they decided to move on.

The day quickly went past and night arrived. Zhao Hai didn’t return to the Space and instead just lied down on his recliner. At this time, a sound was heard. Zhao Hai opened his eyes to see a large group of huge spiders about five kilometers away from him.

These spiders were very huge, each one exceeded five meters tall were eight meters long. Their entire bodies were covered in fur, making people feel dread while looking at them.

There were 40 spiders in this group, both big and small. It seems like they belong to one cluster. Zhao Hai stood up, he knew that this was because the sandworms were already full. Once the sandworms were no longer hungry, their territory would become safe. Because of this, the spiders began to come out.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of these spiders. He would have the spiders come then send them all into the Space, adding new species to the Space.

Before long, the spiders were already close to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his hand and released a 3,000-layer formation, giving the spiders no chance.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai used a 3,000-layer formation set. To be honest, these 3,000-layer formations were very strong, exceeding his expectations. From what Zhao Hai could see, these spiders had about level 4 strength. In this case, capturing them with a 3,000-layer formation was beyond easy.

Of course, Zhao Hai believed that the 3,000-layer formation sets of other people weren’t as powerful as his. It was necessary to know that Zhao Hai’s 3,000-layer formation set included a large amount of supporting formations.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s formation sets were divided into five categories. The first type were defensive formations. It was needless to expand about this since they were just formations meant to defend. The second type were offensive formations. These were formations that focused on very strong attacks. As long as one was hit by these formations, then they would either get severely injured or get killed. The third type were trapping formations. These formation sets don’t aim for killing. Instead, they were used for capturing their targets alive. But sometimes, it was harder to capture enemies than killing them. The fourth type were supporting type formations. These formations weren’t usable during fights. Instead, they were very effective for Mechs and Battleships. The fifth type of formation were weapon formation sets. These formation sets were used for weapons, reinforcing them or giving them attributes. This type of formation set could also be used for defensive equipment, making their defenses stronger.

These five categories were already known in the Machine Field. Moreover, each of these branches were being gradually improved, albeit the very long progress.

Chapter 1168: Violent Aura

The Space didn’t issue much of a response when the spiders were sent to the Space. It only gave simple responses like they were irradiated and were mutated versions of spiders.

Although the Space didn’t level up, the spiders were still quite strong. But this was in the condition that they maintained their current state.

The Space’s prompt informed Zhao Hai that if these spiders were placed in an ordinary environment, then they would slowly turn into ordinary spiders. Although their strength was still stronger than most spiders their size, they were weaker than the spiders who lived within astral qi.

Strictly speaking, this was devolution. Because the environment that they lived in was good, these animals would no longer need their strong abilities to survive. As generations pass, their strength would naturally decrease.

Zhao Hai doesn’t want this to happen. Although the Hell Space was also an  unfavorable environment, it was still different compared to Yellowsand Planet. If he wanted to preserve the strength of these spiders, then he needs to keep their living conditions.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai immediately ordered Cai’er to transform an entire ordinary background into an environment similar to Yellowsand Planet. Then he would make use of it later.

This time, the Space did not’ require Zhao Hai to spend money on the transformation. The Space had already told him that he can transform any environment to be the same as Yellowsand Planet. Because of this, even if he did it several times, Zhao Hai would not need to spend money to transform a background.

Naturally, the Space’s yellowsand environment was different from Yellowsand Planet. Currently, only beasts inhabit Zhao Hai’s yellowsand background. As for plants, he would need to work on it in the future.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried much about developing this yellowsand background. In any case, Yellowsand Planet has already been mapped by the Space. There were a lot of opportunities to come back here.

Actually, the Space now had the ability to improve genes. Zhao Hai could simply take ordinary plants and then modify them so that they could survive in the yellowsand environment. There was no need to take plants from the Yellowsand Planet.

After instructing Cai’er what to do, Zhao Hai returned to his relaxed state. He lied down on the recliner and then folded his umbrella. Since it was already dark, Zhao Hai can only sleep.

But just as Zhao Hai laid down, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, there’s an assassin. They hid very well. They’re currently 5li(2.5 km) away from you. Judging by their strength, they should be level 3.”

Zhao Hai raised his eyebrow. He didn’t expect this night to be lively. There were spiders earlier and now assassins came.

Although he heard Cai’er’s warning, Zhao Hai didn’t do anything. He believed that the assassin had already discovered him, he wanted to see what it would do.

Before long, the assassin was already about two li(.5 km) away from Zhao Hai. He stopped and then carefully sized Zhao Hai up. Zhao Hai looked as though he was asleep. He was lying down on his chair, unmoving.

The assassin couldn’t make up his mind. There were still winds in Yellowsand Planet, yet this person was sleeping peacefully. This was the first time that he’d seen this.

It must be said that Zhao Hai wasn’t the first person that the assassin met in Yellowsand Planet. He had run into other participants before, but all of them were in a critical situation. Their bodies would be covered in protective formations or shields made from battle qi. The others would also have defensive equipment protecting them. Everyone was very cautious, they were guarding against other participants as well as the planet’s beasts. Nobody even dared to think about taking a nap. And now there was Zhao Hai, the sole person who was unafraid in Yellowsand Planet.

It was because of this that the assassin was unable to make a decision. If Zhao Hai was the same as the other participants, then he would have already made a move. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t the same. This made the assassin stuck on what to do.

The assassin stopped two li away from Zhao Hai for one hour. In this hour, Zhao Hai was still lying down on his recliner, looking like he was sleeping soundly. He would even turn once in a while. He looks like he was really asleep.

It can be said that when it comes to the skill of pretending to sleep, if Zhai Hai claimed that he was second, then nobody would dare claim first. This was a skill he perfected back on Earth. He could pretend to sleep for several hours at a time. People wouldn’t be able to see any flaws in his acting.

Zhao Hai would pretend to sleep back on Earth just to curb his boredom. But here, it seems like it was actually useful.

As the assassin was observed Zhao Hai, he was beginning to be convinced that Zhao Hai was really asleep. Then his heart began to stir. He was the same as Wan Xiang, thinking that Zhao Hai’s comfort amidst the astral qi winds was certainly due to some treasure. The thought of this treasure moved the assassin.

Since it was the season for astral winds in Yellowsand Planet, the participants needed to stay in these winds for three whole days. These three days would no doubt be very uncomfortable. Level 4 experts might have a better time, but for level 3 experts, even if they were in a fight, they would still need to allocate some energy inside them to support any protective shield. Even if they drank recovery potions, their strength would still be heavily affected.

And now there was Zhao Hai, who was comfortable despite the harsh winds surrounding him. He didn’t even bother erecting a protective shield. This would allow him to be in his peak condition all the time.

Humans die of greed while birds die in pursuit of food. Since ancient times, people had died because of their greed. This assassin was the same. After he convinced himself that Zhao Hai was truly asleep, he made a move and then took out his dagger before slowly creeping towards Zhao Hai.

Perhaps this was a habit of assassins. When assassins went for the kill, they needed to make sure that they did it in one shot. Therefore, they would usually get closer to their enemies. This habit didn’t change in the Machine Field. The assassin reeled his aura in as he got closer to Zhao Hai.

However, the assassin also knew that he couldn’t fight like he did back in the lower realms. He knew that it was impossible to get really close to Zhao Hai in order to assassinate him. Therefore, he stopped about one li away before he waved his dagger, sending a jet black sword qi flying towards Zhao Hai’s sleeping figure. If it reaches the target, there was no doubt that Zhao Hai’s heart would be pierced.

But at this moment, a sigh was heard, causing the assassin’s hair to stand upright. He stared at Zhao Hai as he gripped his dagger.

And then something strange occurred. Just as the assassin was feeling happy that the sword qi had a hit Zhao Hai, he was suddenly met with a shock.

As the sword qi hit Zhao Hai’s body,  a ‘dang’ sound was heard. And nothing else happened.

Zhao Hai slowly got up from his chair and then turned his head to look at the assassin’s direction. Then he said, “I gave you an opportunity, but you still attacked me. I didn’t want to finish you off, but since you took action, then allow me to retaliate.

The assassin didn’t say anything and just looked at Zhao Hai. Seeing the Assassin’s response, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good, you’re certainly a true assassin. But the most important thing for an assassin is being calm, understanding the opponent’s circumstance in order to judge if then can be killed. If your opponent is strong, then even if your goal is important, you need to accept that it’s impossible. Unfortunately, you failed in this aspect. In any case, this doesn’t matter anymore. Let’s just hope that you learn this in your next life.”

The assassin kept silent, he didn’t relax upon hearing Zhao Hai’s speech. He kept all of his attention on Zhao Hai’s movements. Zhao Hai smiled faintly at the assassin before his figure vanished from the chair.

The assassin’s eyes shrunk. Then he immediately dodged to the side. However, just as he moved, a huge sword appeared on his side. Then the sword hit the assassin’s body.

The assassin discovered the sword too late. He expected that his action would give him enough time to block any attack. The sword stabbed through the assassin’s heart and was immediately killed. The Assassin turned his head for the last time to look at the attacker, but what he saw was actually a dark green skeleton!

“I got killed by a skeleton!” This was the last thought that ran through the assassin’s mind before he died.

Zhao Hai looked at the assassin before throwing its corpse to the Space to be turned into an undead. He had already checked the assassin’s identity. He wasn’t valued that much by his family, so his death wouldn’t be much of a threat to Zhao Hai.

Even if the assassin’s family knew that the killed was Zhao Hai, they still couldn’t do anything. After all, this was a brutal elimination round. Dying was normal. Moreover, the participants were Ascenders from the External Halls.

In the eyes of these families, the people from the External Halls were tools to provide them with benefits. If they died, then they died. They simply weren’t worth going to war on.

After dealing with the assassin, Zhao Hai returned to lie down on his recliner. This time, nothing disturbed him as he slept until dawn.

Zhao Hai woke up and then ate breakfast Meg cooked for him. Then he continued to enjoy the sun. A day had passed, only two days remaining before this round ends.

While drinking his fruit juice, Zhao Hai admired the dancing sands around him. He couldn’t help but sigh deep inside about the beauty of the universe. The universe could actually make something like the Yellowsand Planet. Moreover, there were unique lifeforms living in it.

At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a violent aura coming towards his direction. Although this person had yet to enter the range of Zhao Hai’s spiritual force, this imposing aura allowed Zhao Hai to identify who it was!

Chapter 1169: Meteor Zhu Chen

It was Violent Bear Xiong Li!

Only Violent Bear Xiong Li would have such imposing aura. Although Zhao Hai hadn’t met him before, he had seen Xiong Li’s battles. Zhao Hai’s memory of Xiong Li’s aura was still quite fresh.

Violent Bear Xiong Li, he had the same name as his title. Once a fight begins, he would turn into a violent beast, tearing and shredding the enemy in front of him.

Xiong Li’s weapons were two sledgehammers. Moreover, these sledgehammers were connected by iron chains.  He doesn’t store these sledgehammers inside his spatial equipment and just hung them on his waist.

Zhao Hai considered this person as the most threatening participant. Xiong Li’s offensive power was absolutely strong. Zhao Hai even believed that Streep might not be able to deal with him.

Most Mages have their own bodies as their most vulnerable aspect. If two experts battled with each other, then this physical deficiency might be significant for the result.

Xiong Li’s aura continued to rush over and soon entered the range of Zhao Hai’s spiritual force. Xiong Li was wearing armor while his sledgehammers were hung around his waist. His facial expression was unexpectedly leisurely and free.

But it was obvious that spiritual force wasn’t Xiong Li’s strong point. Because of this, he had yet to discover Zhao Hai. As the distance between the two decreased, Xiong Li finally stopped when he was about five li away from Zhao Hai. It was at this point that Zhao Hai knew that Xiong Li had discovered him.

Zhao Hai continued sitting there without moving. He wanted to see what Xiong Li would do. After staring for a moment, Xiong Li continued flying forward, his speed was quick this time.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it as he continued to relax. Before long, Xiong Li was less than 100 meters away from Zhao Hai. Although there was sand and wind between the two, both sides knew that the other was looking at them. After all, once one reaches their level, spiritual force was no longer different than normal vision.

Xiong Li stayed silent as he stubbornly stared at Zhao Hai. After some time, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Xiong Li, come over. How about we share a cup?” After he said that, Zhao Hai took out another recliner from the Space.

It took Xiong Li some time to process what Zhao Hai said. Then suddenly, he laughed as he flew towards Zhao Hai’s side and sat on the recliner. He looked at Zhao Hai and smiled as he said, “You’re interesting. I didn’t expect to see someone as interesting as you here. Why do you have these things? It looks like you’re prepared to go to the beach.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “When I heard that we’ll have a survival elimination round in Yellowsand Planet, I immediately prepared them. After all, we’re not required to kill other participants in this round. And defeating others also wouldn’t give us any advantages. Therefore, I decided to just spend three days relaxing here.”

Xiong Li stared, then he laughed and said, “Right, right, we’re not required to kill other people. Spending three days relaxing isn’t a bad idea. Hahahaha. But you need to be careful, I heard that brat Zhu Chen has been going around looking for trouble.”

Zhao Hai gawked, “Meteor Zhu Chen? Hmm, that sounds about right. He’s an earth element Mage. Although Yelowsand Planet is filled with astral winds, the sand carry an abundance of earth element. Fighting here would allow him to fight with 120% of his strength. He could use this three days to eliminate some competition. What’s wrong, did he find you?”

Xiong Li snorted and said, “Hmph, if he dared to fight me, then I’ll just drive him away. I heard level 3’s suffering under his hands. He’s quite ruthless, almost everyone he met has died.”

Zhao Hai raised his brows and said, “He’s a bit peculiar. He should hope that we don’t meet. Otherwise, he would have to withdraw from the competition.”

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai. His understanding of Zhu Chen was much deeper than his understanding of Zhao Hai. Although Zhu Chen’s rank was on the bottom end of the top ten experts, this didn’t mean that he was weak. In fact, the ten experts were picked based on their performance during fights. For Zhu Chen, this was because he was very hard to deal with, his defence was just too abnormal.

Zhu Chen seemed to have preference for defense. He has a lot of defensive equipment on his body. And along with his own cultivation, Zhu Chen was the most defensively strong among the top ten.

Naturally, this didn’t mean that since Zhu Chen focused on defense, his offense had suffered. Zhu Chen’s offensive ability was also quite astonishing. However, compared to his defense, his offense fell short. Therefore, people only took note of his defensive abilities.

People who were good at defending generally had a tenacious temperament. Such a person was like a tortoise inside their shell, very difficult to deal with. Because of this, most people would steer clear of these kinds of experts.

Although Xiong Li had a strong temper, he was still aware that if it was any other environment, then he would be able to deal with Zhu Chen. However, they were currently in Yellowsand Planet. Even Xiong Li needed to be careful.

Yellowsand Planet’s environment was special. It had violent astral winds as well as thick earth element energy. In this place, Xiong Li could fight with 80% of his strength. Although Zhu Chen would also be subjected to the same surroundings, his strength would be preserved due to his earth element specialty. So even if Zhu Chen’s increased fighting strength was suppressed, he would still be able to fight with 100% power.

Even if Xiong Li was confident in his ability, a fight between 80% and 100% was something that he wouldn’t go in.

But now there was Zhao Hai who said that he would have Zhu Chen be eliminated in the competition if Zhu Chen decides to attack him. Moreover, Zhao Hai was very confident when he said it. This made Xiong Li look curiously at Zhao Hai.

Although Xiong Li’s character was wild, he actually wasn’t bloodthirsty. This was the reason why he didn’t immediately attack when he saw Zhao Hai.

But at the same time, Xiong Li had some problems regarding Zhao Hai’s strength. Although Zhao Hai had the least information among all participants, his strength could be seen by how he acted.

Xiong Li wasn’t an idiot, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai did something behind the scenes. Xiong Li was well aware that no family would treat the Six Realm Beginner Competition as a joke. This was because the competition was closely tied to their interests. The more achievements the participants get, the more benefits the families would gain. Even the three great powers were tempted by these benefits, much less the Ashley Family.

The Ashley Family attaching great importance to Zhao Hai only meant that Zhao Hai had real skill. Because of this, Xiong Li didn’t underestimate Zhao Hai just because it hasn’t been long since he ascended. So instead of fighting Zhao Hai, Xiong Li decided to join him and drink some refreshing juice.

Now that he knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t weak, Xiong Li was at an impasse. After all, Zhao Hai was still his competitor, so he would like to see Zhao Hai’s strength.

However, Xiong Li didn’t try to spar with Zhao Hai. This was because he might make Zhao Hai misunderstand. They were currently in Yellowsand Planet for the competition. Moreover, he just met Zhao Hai. If he suddenly proposed a fight, then Zhao Hai might see it as aggression. It wouldn’t be good if the two of them were to fight now.

Zhao Hai was strong, while Xiong Li wasn’t weak either. If the two were to fight now, then it was possible for the two of them to heavily wound each other. This wasn’t something that Xiong Li wants to see. If he was injured, then he would find it hard to drive away the other participants. Therefore, he decided to stay on good terms with Zhao Hai and safely survive for three days. Then they would see each other at the arena. Xiong Li was confident that he could reap good achievements the competition.

Xiong Li’s temperament was rough and wild, but he was still clear about his situation. Besides, he was declared as one of the top ten experts of this generation.

At the same time, Xiong Li knew that if he wanted to become a core member of the Wu Family, then he would need to obtain good achievements. So after weighing in on the advantages and disadvantages, Xiong Li didn’t make a move against Zhao Hai.

Xiong Li didn’t react to Zhao Hai’s words as he smiled and said, “How’s your time in Yellowsand Planet so far? Did you meet someone? Did any beast attack you?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The moment I came down, a yellowsand worm attacked me. That thing is really difficult to deal with. I sent a spell over and it just ate it. But fortunately, the worm retreated after eating my attack. I also met a few spiders last night, but they’ve already been dealt with. There are also two other people, they’re gone now.”

Although Zhao Hai’s words sounded light, Xiong Li thought about how hard it was to deal with yellowsand worms as well as astral wind spiders. Hearing Zhao Hai say that the yellowsand worm was difficult to deal with, Xiong Li couldn’t help but agree. Those worms were truly difficult to kill. He just didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong. Yellowsand worms and astral wind spiders weren’t easy to deal with. For Zhao Hai to be this relaxed after dealing with them meant that Zhao Hai was quite strong.

As for what Zhao Hai said about the two people, one wouldn’t be able to see whether they were defeated or killed. But by looking at Zhao Hai’s appearance, it seems like the two were more likely to have been killed. Most importantly, Zhao Hai was able to kill two people with ease. Xiong Li could see that Zhao Hai wasn’t a naive kindhearted individual. He surely had killed some amount of people before. Such a person was most dangerous.

Fighting strength doesn’t only mean one’s strength level, it also included one’s battle experience. From what it looks like, Zhao Hai had rich experience in battles. He wasn’t someone that should be provoked.

Chapter 1170: –  Sun Fei

Xiong Li processed his thoughts and decided to not provoke Zhao Hai. But Zhao Hai didn’t know about this. He just sat there and took sips from his fruit drink. He also talked to Xiong Li from time to time.

When Xiong Li discovered that Zhao Hai didn’t have any evil intentions, he also began to relax. The two continued to lie down on their recliners and chatted.

The two got more comfortable with each other as they talked. Although Xiong Li was wild and was sometimes scheming, he wasn’t that bad. He also didn’t have a tendency to look for fights, which goes very well with Zhao Hai’s character. The two unexpectedly connected.

During the time the two chatted, spiritual force kept sweeping their bodies. However, it didn’t take long before they shifted their attention elsewhere. They actually discovered Xiong Li and Zhao Hai. Nobody dared to make any noise and just immediately went another direction. These two weren’t known for being merciful. And seeing them being merry, nobody dared to disturb them.

Time passed quickly and evening came. Zhao Hai took out some food from the Space and shared it with Xiong Li alongside a cup of wine.

The two drank until midnight and then they fell asleep on their chairs. Spiritual forces kept sweeping them even while they were drinking. Naturally, these people decided to avoid provoking the two.

But not long after the two had fallen asleep, a roar was heard. It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai could see something coming from the direction of the roar.

It was a group of apes, but their heads were actually from a wolf. They looked tall and majestic.

When he saw these beasts, Zhao Hai immediately identified them. These were among the famous beasts in Yellowsand Planet, known as coyote apes.

Coyote Apes were beasts that belong to the earth element. They were super strong and their defense wasn’t something to scoff at. Although they couldn’t fly, the sand carried by the astral winds could actually become their weapon. They were quite formidable beasts in Yellowsand Planet.

After seeing these coyote apes, Zhao Hai turned to Xiong Li and said, “It looks like a pack of coyote apes. Hmm, they seem to be chasing someone.” Zhao Hai could now see a man running for his life. He didn’t fly and just ran. However, his speed seems to slow down, it was clear that he was running out of energy.

Looking at the person’s face, Zhao Hai discovered that he actually knew him. This person was none other than one of the Ashley Family’s participants.

Zhao Hai knit his brows gently, he was thinking that he needs to offer his help. After all, this person was from the Ashley Family. He couldn’t just look at him die without helping.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai turned to Xiong Li and said, “Brother Xiong Li, the man being chased by the coyote apes is from my Ashley Family. I couldn’t just sit here and not help. Wait for me here, I’ll return soon.” Then Zhao Hai moved as his figure disappeared.

When Xiong Li heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare. His spiritual force could only cover the distance of about 3li(1.5km). Naturally, Zhao Hai would have stronger spiritual force, he was a Mage after all.

However, Xiong Li was aware that his spiritual force wasn’t that inferior compared to Mages with the same level as him. In other words, the most a level 4 Mage could see was about 5li(2.5km) away. But it seems like Zhao Hai had much stronger spiritual force than this.

It was through this small matter that Xiong Li was once again reminded that Zhao Hai was worthy to be called the most talented beginner. Most Mages simply couldn’t compare to him.

But Xiong Li didn’t dwell too much on this thought. He let out a long breath and then muttered, “It looks like the realm qualifiers has become even more complicated.”

Actually, before Xiong Li met Zhao Hai, he was very confident about his own strength. But after meeting Zhao Hai, Xiong Li’s confidence began to waver. This was because Zhao Hai’s strength seem to be on a different level. Xiong Li wasn’t able to see how deep Zhao Hai’s skill really was.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about these things. After seeing that Xiong Li didn’t follow, he felt relaxed. Then he reappeared right beside the man and identified him to be one from the Upright Symbol Camp.

When the man saw Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but light up as he said, “Zhao Hai, help me!”

Zhao Hai nodded, “You go first. I’ll deal with these coyote apes.” The man nodded before he quickly ran.

Zhao Hai stood in place and then immediately released five spells. Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s attack, the coyote apes roared.

Unfortunately for the coyote apes, even if they were defensively strong, they couldn’t be regarded as advanced level beasts in Yellowsand Planet. They simply don’t have the body to contend against Zhao Hai. It only took a few rounds before all of them were sent to the Space by Zhao Hai.

Once these coyote apes were sent to the Space, Zhao Hai relaxed. He already knew that the casualties of this elimination round wouldn’t be small. There were no weak beasts in Yellowsand Planet. And there was the astral winds as well.

However, Zhao Hai could also see that the committee had already thought through this point. This place was the domain of the sandworms, so there were no very powerful beasts here. So even if some participants were be killed or would withdraw in three days, the participants still wouldn’t be wiped out.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t like this procedure, he didn’t say anything. After all, he didn’t have the qualifications to express his thoughts. And this was in addition to the fact that Zhao Hai just ascended months ago. He didn’t even have the rights to speak in the Ashley Family. Therefore, he could only endure for now.

Zhao Hai sighed then he headed back. Halfway back to his spot, Zhao Hai saw the man from the Upright Symbol Camp. It was clear that the man was tired seeing how slow he was progressing. After he saw Zhao Hai, the man hastily said, “Upright Symbol Camp’s Tao Li has met Mister Zhao Hai. Thank you for saving my life.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, we’re both from the Ashley Family. There’s no need to be polite. Let’s go.” Then he took the man and flew forward. Before long, the two arrived at Zhao Hai’s spot. Xiong Li was still there, pouring some liquor on his cup and continued drinking.

When Tao Li noticed Xiong Li, he couldn’t help but get startled. Cadjo’s introduction for Xiong Li was quite detailed, so he clearly knew about this person. It wasn’t difficult to think that people would be surprised after seeing Xiong Li.

Seeing Tao Li’s expression, Zhao Hai immediately knew what he was thinking. But he didn’t care as he just smiled and said, “Brother Xiong Li, this is our Ashley Family’s Tao Li. Brother Tao Li, this is Brother Xiong Li. Come take a seat and eat something.”

Although Tao Li doesn’t understand what was going on, he still gave Xiong Li a salute before sitting on the chair that Zhao Hai took out for him. Actually, he was awfully hungry. He had been pursued by the coyote apes the entire evening. If his meeting with Zhao Hai happened much later, then he might have already turned into ape excrement.

Zhao Hai sat dawn as he looked at Xiong Li and said, “Two days have passed and we’ll leave this place tomorrow. Hai, to be honest, I really didn’t want to participate in this round. It just seems unfair. Unfortunately, I need to participate for the family. Once we leave tomorrow, Brother Xiong Li and I would be enemies once more. Hehe, it should be interesting.”

When Xiong Li heard Zhao Hai, he also smiled and said, “We really can’t do much. As an Ascender, if we want to live a good life in the Machine Field, then we could only rely on ourselves. Right, and if we meet at the arena, let’s make sure to have a good fight.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right, a good fight. Let’s drink!” Then he took his glass and downed the liquor. Although it was still wine, it felt like it tasted a bit bitter.

Of course, there was no reason for Tao Li to leave. The three drank liquor before going back to rest. This time, nobody disturbed them. The three slept until noon before they got up.

After the three ate, they continued to chat. Tao Li began to admire Zhao Hai. Everyone who came to Yellowsand Planet were all wary and cautious. On the other hand, Zhao Hai had a recliner out and drank fruit juice.

As the three chatted, Zhao Hai suddenly discovered two people entering his ten li(5km) range. After sweeping them with his spiritual force, he couldn’t help but wrinkle his brows. He knew these two, one was a person from the Ghost Symbol Camp while the other was Fire Saint Sun Fei.

Zhao Hai was already prepared to deal with Sun Fei. However, he didn’t expect to see him chasing someone from the Ashley Family. It seems like Sun Fei had been incited by the Zhang family to assault the Ashley Family.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Xiong Li and Tao Li and said, “I just discovered two people, one of them is from the Ghost Symbol Camp. However, he’s been chased down by Fire Saint Sun Fei. I’ll head over to save him. You two wait here.” Then his body moved as he flew east.

When Tao Li heard Zhao Hai, his expression changed, but he just sighed and didn’t say anything. Xiong Li looked at Tao Li and said, “You won’t help?”

Tao Li forced a smile and said, “Help? I’ll just be a deadweight if i go. I would just divert Zhao Hai’s attention if I went with him.” Xiong Li smiled faintly and said, “So the Ashley Family and Zhang Family is actually at war? Otherwise Sun Fei wouldn’t just chase your people.”

Tao Li coldly snorted and said, “Let’s see how long the Zhang Family can get arrogant. Sun Fei is really unlucky to meet Zhao Hai today. He’d be lucky if Zhao Hai didn’t peel off his skin.”

When Xiong Li saw how confident Tao Li was in Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but curiously ask, “You’re very confident in Zhao Hai, is he that strong?”

Tao Li smiled faintly and said, “Of course I’m confident. His reputation has already spread throughout the Ashley Family’s external hall. He’s stronger compared to most established level 4 experts. The family is very confident in him.”

Xiong Li nodded. He also knew that Tao Li wouldn’t say anything else, so he didn’t ask for more information. But at the same time, his mood got heavier. He thought that he would really win in the competition. But now, his confidence wasn’t as big.

While the two were talking, Zhao Hai appeared in front of Sun Fei and the person from the Ghost Symbol Camp and then shouted, “Stop!” Then he sent a spell to block Sun Fei’s magic.

When the person from the Ghost Symbol Camp saw Zhao Hai, his expression lit up, then he said, “Zhao Hai, you’re here, great. This guy has already killed three people from the Ashley Family. He’s chasing me now. He also said that he will kill everyone from the Ashley Family.”

Zhao Hai turned to Sun Fei and then smiled faintly, “Does Mister Sun Fei really want to kill us all?”

When Sun Fei saw Zhao Hai, his expression tightened up. As someone from the Zhang Family, it was impossible for Sun Fei to not know about Zhao Hai. The Zhang Family had already listed Zhao Hai as the most dangerous person from the Ashley Family. He didn’t expect to meet Zhao Hai here. After he heard Zhao Hai, Sun Fei quickly answered, “That’s right, as long as I see anyone from the Ashley Family, I’ll immediately kill them.”

Instead of being angry at Sun Fei’s response, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “When did the Ashley Family have enmity with the Zhang Family? Why does Mister Sun Fei need to be this violent?”

Sun Fei coldly snorted and said, “Offending the Zhang Family will incur generations of enmity. Zhao Hai, there’s no need to waste your breath. It’s your fault for running into me today. Go die!” Then he began to make a move.

However, Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Mister Sun, please wait. Even if this is the elimination round, it wouldn’t be good for the two of us to fight. I’m not afraid of fighting you, but Xiong Li is close by. If we injure each other, then we’ll just be giving ourselves to him. How about we resume our fight in the arena.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei couldn’t help but stare. Then he used his spiritual force to find Xiong Li who wasn’t far away. His expression changed, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You’re quite lucky. I’ll see you at the arena.” Then he turned around and left.

Sun Fei wasn’t a fool. Upon seeing Xiong Li drinking juice with someone from the Ashley Family, he knew that he couldn’t fight Zhao Hai. If he did, and was grabbed by Xiong Li, then the Zhang Family wouldn’t let him off.

On the other hand, the reason why Zhao Hai didn’t fight against Sun Fei was precisely Xiong Li. Although he was happily spending his time with Xiong Li, Zhao Hai was still aware that Xiong Li was someone from another family who was also fighting to change his position. Sun Fei wasn’t someone who could be easily dealt with. With Xiong Li nearby, Zhao Hai couldn’t easily deal with Sun Fei with all of his strength. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to endure, surprising both Xiong Li and Sun Fei.

Before joining the Six Realm Beginner Competition, Zhao Hai wouldn’t show his full strength. He needs to keep his cards hidden for as long as possible.

Chapter 1171: Invincible Enemy

A day passed by in a blink of an eye. Zhao Hai’s group now had four people in it. Such group couldn’t be looked down on. Because of this, nobody dared to annoy them. Moreover, there were no beasts around, allowing Zhao Hai and the others to spend the time in peace.

This peace went on even during the night. As if knowing that this place was forbidden, no beasts dared to walk into the area. Zhao Hai and the others had a good rest that night. On the morning of the next day, the group ate their breakfast while waiting for the time to run out.

After eating their breakfast, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t immediately leave. Instead they sat down and drank fruit juice until noon. When time was up, Zhao Hai sighed and then turned to Xiong Li and said, “Brother Xiong Li, it’s time. We should head back. It’s my luck to meet you here. Unfortunately, after we leave, we would become opponents once again.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, it’s true that we would fight once we leave this place. But as long as we qualify for the Six Realm Beginner Competition, we would be considered allies. My Wu Family and your Ashley Family doesn’t have any enmity. We’ll be able to walk together in the future.”

When he heard Xiong Li, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right, just like you said. Once we go to the Six Realm Beginner Competition, then we’ll be friends.”

Tao Li and the other person looked at Zhao Hai and Xiong Li with envy. They were being tactful and didn’t speak. They were clearly aware that they couldn’t interrupt Zhao Hai and Xiong Li’s conversation. After all, they didn’t have any qualifications to discuss friendship with the two.

Who were Zhao Hai and Xiong Li? One was a gifted talent while the other was a famous existence in the Machine Field. Although Xiong Li had ascended quite some time ago, he was still someone that was above their current position.

After he heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li nodded and said, “Then it’s time to leave.” Zhao Hai nodded and then stored the tables and chairs before leading everyone out of Yellowsand Planet.

It was more difficult to leave a planet than entering it. But fortunately, the participants were strong enough to easily fly out of the planet’s atmosphere.

They also discovered people going out of the atmosphere from time to time. Zhao Hai greeted a few of these people before flying towards his assigned ship.

Zhao Hai entered the ship through the decompression chamber. Upon entering, Zhao Hai felt the pressure slowly become normal. Then he exited the decompression chamber and went towards the main room.

Upon entering the main room, a Mage met him and said, “Leave your transmitter here. Then you can go.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he took his transmitter out and gave it to the Mage. Upon receiving Zhao Hai’s transmitter, the Mage nodded and said, “Your transmitter is in perfect condition. You pass this round. You can go take a rest or explore the ship.” Zhao Hai nodded before he left.

When Zhao Hai returned to the room he stayed in before, he discovered that his three other roommates had yet to come back. Since it might take them some time to return, he entered the Space to take a bath. Then after he freshened up, he went out and then ate some lunch in the ship’s dining room. After eating, he returned to his room to take a rest.

When evening came, a person entered the room. This person’s body was very wounded. He was quite dirty as well, it was clear that he didn’t have a good time.

When the person saw Zhao Hai, he gave a slight nod before entering the bathroom to wash himself. The man didn’t eat and immediately went to sleep. It was clear that he hasn’t slept in the past three days.

The night passed by, Zhao Hai’s two other roommates still haven’t returned. Zhao Hai knew that those two wouldn’t return. Although Zhao Hai didn’t have any relationship with them, he still couldn’t help but grieve for their loss.

Another day passed and the two still haven’t come back. Moreover, the fleet had made the decision to wait one more day. If nobody else came back, then they would no longer wait.

Even if he didn’t know whether Zhao Hai had suffered a life and death situation, Zhao Hai’s roommate still began to chat with him. Although he didn’t say much, Zhao Hai’s room was no longer as boring as before.

…..

It’s been three days since Zhao Hai returned to the ship. This was also the last day for the participants to return. If the participants couldn’t return, then they would lose their opportunity to join the next round.

While Zhao Hai was chatting with his roommate, the ship’s alarm suddenly began blaring up.

Zhao Hai and his roommate stared, then their expressions changed. They knew that this was the ship’s warning alarm for an enemy approach. The ship immediately took action, crew and staff scampered towards their own posts.

However, this was a Machine Field Planet fleet, who would dare attack a Machine Field Planet fleet? Space pirates? While he thought of this, Zhao Hai heard an announcement, “All participants pay attention, all participants pay attention. We ask everyone to stay in their rooms and don’t leave without instruction. I repeat, don’t leave without instruction. Thanks for cooperating.” Then no other announcement was heard.

At this time, Zhao Hai learned from Laura and the others that the fleet wasn’t being attacked. Instead, they were being alert because they came upon a certain group. And this group was no other than people from the Cultivation Realm.

When he heard that it was a group from the Cultivation Realm, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get curious. He wishes to enter the Space to take a look. But since his roommate was still with him, he couldn’t just disappear.

But on the other side, Laura and the others were very excited to see people from the Cultivation Realm. They told Zhao Hai that the group seems to be from a big power in the Cultivation Realm and were performing a smelting trial in Yellowsand Planet. The group were riding on a huge ship. But compared to the Machine Field’s spaceships, the Cultivation Realm’s ship looked like a huge ancient boat. Moreover, this ship wasn’t big. Comparing the size of the two ships was like comparing a watermelon to a soybean.

However, this tiny ship actually caused the Machine Field’s fleet to be anxious. They sounded out warnings to everyone. On the other hand, the boat didn’t seem to care about the huge ships. They swaggered through the fleet and then entered Yellowsand Planet.

When the ship finally entered Yellowsand Planet, the warnings from the fleet died down. Then the fleet immediately took off and left the area.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a long breath. He can see from this point how overbearing those from the Cultivation Realm were. They didn’t even spare a glance towards the Machine Field’s fleet.

Hearing Zhao Hai sigh, the roommate thought that he was relieved that everything went back to normal. Therefore, he didn’t feel anything strange about it. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, who do you think attacked the fleet? Nobody in the Machine Field would dare come and attack the Machine Field Planet’s fleet. I reckon they’re space pirates.”

Although he knew that the alarms were due to the Cultivators, Zhao Hai couldn’t just say it. So he shook his head and said, “I don’t think that it’s the space pirates. Otherwise they wouldn’t be able to stay in the Machine Field anymore. This is Yellowsand Planet. Although it is part of the Machine Field’s territory, there are people from other realms that come here. It’s possible that it’s those people from the other realms. Otherwise the fleet wouldn’t be so nervous.”

As soon as he heard Zhao Hai, the roommate thought that what he said was reasonable, so he nodded and said, “That’s true. After all, our Machine Field is the weakest among the six realms. It’s no wonder why the fleet got nervous.”

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t speak about the topic anymore. However, the roommate opened his mouth and said, “I ran into those people just a few days after I ascended. Whenever they see someone from the Machine Field, they would always point their noses up high. At that time, I really wished that I could punch them in the face.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Did you manage to fight them?” The roommate shook his head and said, “I didn’t. However, I’ve seen a sword cultivator from the Cultivation Realm fight. With just his own strength, he was able to fend of an entire pirate fleet of 30 ships. Every time he waved his sword down, a ship would be cut in half. It was too scary!” After he said this, the roommate couldn’t help but recall the horror of that time.

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai knit his brows and asked, “The  people from the Cultivation Realm are that strong? And how come they’re in the Machine Field’s territory?”

The roommate shook his head and said, “From what I heard, they were here because some pirates snatched something from their sect. That sect issued a mission and that person was the one who took it. He interrogated the pirates and found out that they didn’t intend to get that item. They only thought that they were attacking a small merchant fleet. They didn’t know that there was a special relic inside. It seems like that relic was an important item between the Machine Field and that sect. Therefore, they sent someone to find it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he let out a long breath and said, “If I have the opportunity, then I’ll try going to the Cultivation Realm to take a look. I reckon they have much more splendid things compared to the Machine Field.”

The roommate smiled and said, “There have been a lot of people with the same idea. However, there were plenty of them who weren’t able to return. Nobody knows whether they died or became a member of a sect. As for those who managed to come back, they actually kept silent about their journey to the Cultivation Realm. It seems like something happened to them that they can’t say.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “No matter what, we’re people from the World of Cultivation. Sooner or later we would have the urge to travel to other realms. At the very least, I would like to understand the other realms more. If I’m able to explore the Cultivation Realm, I would want to find out how strong they really are.”

As soon as he heard Zhao Hai, the roommate couldn’t help but smile bitterly. However, he didn’t try to stop Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1172: Becoming Friends With The Wu Family

In the next couple of days, Zhao Hai stayed in his room and rarely went out. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s greatest harvest weren’t the things he gained from Yellowsand Planet, but instead his meeting with the cultivators.

These Cultivators were so arrogant in front of the Machine Field’s fleet. This caused complex feelings inside Zhao Hai’s heart. He was able to take a glimpse of the Cultivation Realm’s rules. Actually, it can be said that there were no rules in the Cultivation Realm. Whoever had the biggest fist gets the last word.

If there were any rules in the Cultivation Realm, then it would be the law of the jungle. The weak were prey to the strong. Everything depended on strength.

The Cultivators just had a small boat, but they were still able to plunge the Machine Field’s fleet into a state of alarm. One could see the strength of the Cultivation Realm from this point.

This also made Zhao Hai more eager to get stronger. Unfortunately, his situation was different from the others. His strength was closely related to the Space. It was almost impossible for him to have the same path of progression as the others.

If others were to know that Zhao Hai wasn’t satisfied with his speed of cultivation, then they would certainly be furious. It was good that Zhao Hai wouldn’t reveal this thought to the others.

Ten days quickly flew past. Zhao Hai spent most of the ten days inside his room, but he was also chatting with Xiong Li using their computers. Naturally, their relationship was getting better.

On the other hand, when Zhao Hai’s roommate saw Zhao Hai casually chatting with Xiong Li, he couldn’t help but feel envious. One must know that Xiong Li was one of the ten great experts. He was an idol to many people.

The fleet arrived at Machine Field Planet after ten days of travel. When Zhao Hai got down from his ship, he immediately saw Cadjo, Desbarres, Luke, and Margaret. They were standing beside a car waiting for Zhao Hai and the others.

And just as Zhao Hai took a step forward, Margaret immediately dashed towards him. She hugged Zhao Hai and didn’t say anything else. On the other hand, Zhao Hai just chuckled.

Zhao Hai let go of Margaret after some time. They haven’t seen each other for ten days. Even if Margaret was inside the Space, she still wasn’t able to meet Zhao Hai.

After Zhao Hai let go of Margaret, Cadjo approached him. Cadjo inspected Zhao Hai before he nodded and said, “Good, very good. I heard that only 2 out of ten participants in this round managed to pass. And aside from the two participants that you saved, nobody else from the family was able to survive. It seems like the family would have to rely on you from this point on.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “General Manager, rest assured. I’ll certainly bring in achievements.”

Cadjo nodded. At this time, the other two participants from the Ashley family arrived. They gave Cadjo a salute before Cadjo led them towards the car. After doing this, Cadjo turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I heard that you got to know Xiong Li?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I did meet him in Yellowsand Planet. Then we chatted the whole time. But we didn’t try to spar since it might give others an advantage.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “That’s good. Xiong Li is from the Wu Family. We didn’t have any relationship with them before. But a couple of days ago someone from the Wu Family came to visit me. He was very polite. This is all because of you. This is a great contribution for the family.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s nothing. I just thought that it wouldn’t be good for me if I fight Xiong Li. I even let Sun Fei go since the situation isn’t appropriate. I’ll wait until the official battles. I’ll waste his cultivation in front of everyone.”

Cadjo patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder before they boarded the car. Since there were only a few participants left, the entire group rode on one car. Zhao Hai and Margaret were in the middle seats while Tao Li and the person from the Ghost Symbol Camp were on the back.

After boarding, Cadjo turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “I heard that Zhu Chen has offended a lot of people. Did you run into him?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I didn’t  But I heard from Xiong Li that he has been terrorizing level 3’s. But he’s trained by the Divine Earth Palace, his backing should be strong. Is there a problem?”

Cadjo coldly snorted and said, “Problem? Yes, but not for us. Although Churches are very powerful, the influence of other families aren’t something to be trifled with. Zhu Chen’s wanton slaughter attracted the ire of these families. At this point, no matter which power Zhu Chen faces in this competition, all of them would go all out.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he also thought that Zhu Chen had been excessive. They were only competing for slots, they weren’t personal enemies. There was no need for slaughter. It seems like Zhu Chen was one of those bloodthirsty people.

Before long, the car arrived at the Ashley Family’s office. Cadjo brought everyone to the dining hall and treated everyone to a delicious meal. When the group arrived at the hall, everything was already prepared. After everyone had sat down, Cadjo lifted his wine glass and said, “This glass is dedicated to the three who survived the elimination round.” Then he downed the liquor in the cup. Naturally, Zhao Hai and the others followed after.

 After drinking from his cup, Cadjo poured himself another glass before turning towards Tao Li and the person from the Ghost Symbol Camp, “Tao Li, Xue Zhong, the family has decided to withdraw your participation in the qualifiers. It’s too dangerous. The casualties in Yellowsand Planet caused a heavy atmosphere in the competition. If you enter the arena, you might not be able to survive. You’re also talents from the family and we don’t want to lose you as well. The Patriarch said that even if you were saved by Zhao Hai, this proves that you have luck on your side. You won’t be treated badly when you return. What do you think? If you still want to participate in the competition, then the family wouldn’t stop you.”

Tao Li and Xue Zhong looked at each other, then they nodded. Tao Li stood up and bowed to Cadjo and said, “General Manager, please convey our gratitude to the Patriarch. Actually, when the two of us got out of Yellowsand Planet, we already thought of withdrawing from the competition. However, we’re afraid that the family wouldn’t allow us to, so we didn’t say anything. General Manager just told us what we wanted to hear. To be honest, back when we first arrived at Machine Field Planet, we thought that we might have some chance. But after this elimination round, we realized that continuing would just be courting death. We really thank the family for this.” Then the two bowed towards Cadjo and Desbarres.

Cadjo waved his hand and said, “It’s good that you can still think clearly. Although you can get more rewards if you participate, it’s not worth it for the risk. Alright, sit back down and continue drinking.” Then the two sat down.

Cadjo turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, since they won’t be participating anymore, we only have you left. You’re the hope of the family.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “General Manager, rest assured. The first place is already mine.”

When they heard this, everyone laughed. Nobody thought that Zhao Hai was bragging. After all, Zhao Hai’s strength was the real deal. Even Xiong Li recognized his strength. This caused the Ashley Family’s  confidence in him to increase.

After everyone drank another cup of wine, Tao Li and Xue Zhong lifted their glass and turned to Zhao Hai. Then they said, “Sir, if it weren’t for your help, then we might not have been able to get out of Yellowsand Planet. Please accept this toast of our heartfelt gratitude.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he raised his glass and said, “We’re from the same family, so it’s natural that we need to help each other. Before going to Yellowsand Planet, I initially wanted all of us to be in a team. But unfortunately, the committee didn’t allow us to do so. Meeting you two could be considered fate. There’s no need to be polite to me in the future. Let’s drink.” Then the three downed the liquor in their glass.

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai’s performance and smiled. He didn’t say a word. He was quite satisfied with Zhao Hai’s actions. It can be said that Zhao Hai was doing a huge favor for the Ashley Family’s External Halls. Saving Tao Li and Xue Zhong was a huge favor to the Upright Symbol Camp and the Ghost Symbol Camp.

Thunder was also satisfied that Zhao Hai managed to save two talents. He was happy that Zhao Hai was being considerate towards the family. Although he didn’t follow this time, he was still talking with Cadjo and Desbarres. And there were no lack of boasting about Zhao Hai in these conversations. Thunder was also praising Desbarres. He thought that if Desbarres didn’t snatch Zhao Hai soon, then Zhao Hai might have already been taken in by the other families. Thunder was happy with Desbarres’s initiative to recruit Zhao Hai.

The group happily ate their meal. Although seven people died in the elimination round, this was something that Cadjo and the others already expected. Therefore, they weren’t very sad. Conversely, they were ecstatic that Zhao Hai had become friends with Xiong Li.

Naturally, becoming friends with Xiong Li wasn’t significant. However, drawing a relationship with the Wu Family through Xiong Li was something extraordinary. The Wu Family’s position in the Warrior Association wasn’t low. Their strength and influence was also formidable. They weren’t any less compared to the Ashley Family. In the past, since one of them was a Warrior Family while the other was a Mage family, it was hard for them to establish a connection with each other. It can be said that the two were completely strangers to one another.  And now, because of Zhao Hai’s actions, a bridge had appeared that could connect the two families together.

After the meal, Zhao Hai returned to his room. Of course, Margaret also came in with him. Then the two immediately entered the Space. Zhao Hai was quite anxious because he wants to take a look at the Cultivators currently in Yellowsand Planet. He wanted to see what kind of trial they would do. And maybe he could gain some information just in case he met someone from the Cultivation Realm later on.

Chapter 1173: Sword Pavillion Concentrating Astral Qi

As soon as Zhao Hai and Margaret entered the Space, Laura and the others immediately greeted them. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, we’re ready.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I want to see what makes these people so arrogant.” After he said that, Zhao Hai and the others sat down in the living room.

Once everyone had sat down, Laura immediately opened the monitor. Displayed on the screen was a boat. This wooden boat wasn’t small nor big. It didn’t have an oar. And on its side was an insignia. The insignia showed an unsheathed sword pointed towards an expansive sky.

Then Laura said, “We checked online, this is the insignia from the Sword Pavilion. It is a medium-sized sect in the Cultivator Realm. The people in this sect lived by the sword for their entire life. Once someone joins the sect, an elder would make a sword that went along with that person’s characteristics. This sword would be made from the best materials. However, this sword would practically be a blank. Then the person would place the sword in their dantian to be slowly nurtured. In turn, the person would become the sword and the sword would become the person. It was a state of unity between man and sword.”

Laura took a deep breath before she continued, “But because of their unique way of doing things, the sect was stuck in being a medium-sized sect. However, this didn’t mean that their status in the Cultivation Realm was low. It was said that their offensive strength is second to none in the Cultivation Realm.”

Zhao Hao nodded. The sword was the lord of killing. So it wasn’t a wonder for a person who studied the sword their entire life to have strong offensive abilities.

Laura added, “When they reach core formation, they could use other magic treasures. But before core formation, they can’t use anything else than their swords. Reaching core formation would transform their sword into a sword pill. The sword is the pill and the pill is the sword.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. It seems like the Sword Pavillion isn’t simple. Their cultivation method is pretty rare.”

Laura agreed, “And the strength of the Sword Pavillion could only get stronger as time passes. Although everyone in the Cultivation Realm lived long lives, they were still mortal unless they reach the realm of Immortality. Unless they encountered some accident, members of the Sword Pavillion who were at the end of their lifespans would go to the sect’s ancestral grounds and spend the rest of their lifetime there. Once they die, they would leave their swords behind, along with a trace of their spiritual force. These life source swords would then exist in the ancestral grounds. Actually, every time the Sword Pavillion accepts a student, they would take them to the ancestral grounds first to pay respects to the swords of their ancestors. It might even be possible for these swords to choose a new master.”

Laura drank some water and continued, “These swords have traces of their original owner’s spiritual force, allowing a sliver of the original owner’s consciousness to  exist inside. However, this consciousness couldn’t function like a normal human. But even so, this spiritual force could still choose a person that has the liking of the original owner. And since these swords had been nurtured for a long time, their strength was greater than newly made swords. This would increase the chosen person’s strength very quickly. It was precisely because of this accumulation that the Sword Pavillion gets stronger and stronger as each generation passed. Even top sects in the Cultivation Realm couldn’t easily provoke them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but his eyes were stuck on the monitor as the Sword Pavillion’s people entered Yellowsand Planet. Upon entering the planet, the small boat suddenly changed course and headed straight towards something. When he saw the trajectory of the small boat, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare as he said, “They’re heading towards Astral Wind Canyon?”

The reason Zhao Hai gawked was because Astral Wind Canyon was quite a famous place in Yellowsand Planet. Yellowsand Planet’s years comprises 12 months. Ten of these months would have extreme winds blowing through it. As for the remaining two months, there would be rain. This rain is filled with astral qi. If one was exposed to this rain for a long time, then their bodies would wither until they die.

This event happens everywhere in Yellowsand Planet except one place, Astral Wind Canyon. In other places, once the rainy season began, the winds would stop. But in Astral Wind Canyon, the winds would continue all year round.

At the same time, the winds in Astral Wind Canyon were much stronger than the ones outside. Because of these strong winds, only a few people dared to go there. Before long, Astral Wind Canyon became one of the forbidden lands in Yellowsand Planet.

Sword Pavillion’s destination was very easy to guess. After all, they were travelling in a straight line towards Astral Wind Canyon.

Laura nodded and said, “Right, they seem to be heading towards Astral Wind Canyon.” Then Laura controlled the monitor to show the small boat just right outside the canyon.

However, this small boat didn’t just stop at the mouth of the canyon. Instead, it went directly to the middle. The terrain of Astral Wind Canyon was very special. All around were gray and yellow rocks. These rocks stood upright looking like stone pillars, they looked quite ugly.

However, nobody dared to underestimate these rocks. These rocks stood for tens of millions of years amidst the harsh astral winds of the canyon. Its degree of hardness couldn’t even be compared to iron and steel. Even the Cultivation Realm’s artifacts would find it hard to contend against these rocks in terms of hardness.

The canyon looked like a river. However, it didn’t go straight. Instead it wound down through some sort of pattern. And instead of being obstructed by these curves, astral winds coming through the canyon were actually strengthened.

But when Zhao Hai looked at the canyon more carefully. He found out that although it looked terrifying, the middle of the canyon actually had the weakest astral winds. Moreover, due to their placement, winds coming through this section weren’t amplified by the canyon’s curves.

However, one should know that even if the winds were weak, they were still astral winds. It was still more dangerous than ordinary winds. And these winds were the most ideal for concentrating astral qi as well as refining weapons.

It can be said that in the entire Yellowsand Planet, no other place was better in concentrating astral qi than this section of Astral Wind Canyon.

Zhao Hai found out about these points using the silver needles. Since these needles were made by the Space, where a yellowsand environment existed, they weren’t affected by the astral winds. But after looking at the Sword Pavillion, it seems like they knew about this place. Their visit this time was probably to let their disciple concentrate some astral qi for themselves.

When Laura saw Zhao Hai frown, she quickly knew what he was thinking. Although Zhao Hai hadn’t been inside the Space these days, he still knew about things inside. This was because Laura and the others could just talk to him wherever he was. Even if Zhao Hai couldn’t see anything, he could still hear things.

Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, the Sword Pavillion, it seems like they’re here to condense astral qi. We don’t know how they knew about this place, but if the Sword Pavillion knew about it, then others might also be aware of it. It seems like we need to rethink our estimation of the Cultivation Realm’s strength.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Astral Qi’s biggest benefit is increasing one’s offensive strength. If the Cultivation Realm knew about this spot in Yellowsand Planet, then they could send people en masse to condense astral qi. This would provide a huge increase of collective strength for the Cultivation Realm.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai said, “It  shouldn’t be that huge a problem. Astral Qi doesn’t only exist in the form in has in Yellowsand Planet. After all, the wind is just a form the astral qi used in order to flow. The essence of astral qi doesn’t change itself. Condensing it shouldn’t be that easy.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “Right. But even if that is the case, in the last few days, we were able to find out that people from the Cultivation Realm have a higher chance of condensing these special energies inside their bodies compared to other people. Brother Hai, we cannot take this issue lightly.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured. Now that the Space has its own yellowsand environment, we now have control over how intense astral winds could be. With this ability, we should have no problem condensing astral qi of our own. Right, how about we have some undead try concentrating astral qi. This way, we could see if they could get stronger.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others’s eyes turned bright. Then Cai’er immediately answered, “Young Master, I’ll get on it.” Zhao Hai nodded, then Cai’er’s body disappeared as she left.

Zhao Hai was still looking at the cultivators from the Sword Pavillion. These people were really here to condense astral qi. But when Zhao Hai saw the group heading out of the small boat, he couldn’t help but stare. There were a lot more people than he expected!

Although the Space was formidable, since the small boat was a magical artifact, the silver needles couldn’t go inside. Therefore, Zhao Hai was unaware of the boat’s internal situation.

So when Zhao Hai saw more than a hundred people going out of the small boat, he was stunned. But after some thought, he concluded that the small boat had a spatial expansion ability. Only through this method could a small vessel like this hold that much people.

Before long, the group got out of the small boat. Then under the leadership of five people, they flew over towards a spot in the canyon to condense astral qi. As for the five elders leading them, they positioned themselves in five directions to protect everyone from unexpected events.

Everything was calm when the Sword Pavillion’s people began absorbing astral qi. But it didn’t take long before they started sweating and their faces turned red and then paled. Nevertheless, everyone clenched their teeth and persevered. But soon enough, someone started spurting out blood and then start falling down.

When this happened, one of the five protectors swept down and went to that person’s side. Then he fed the person a medicinal pill. He broke the pill in his hand before shoving it inside the patient’s mouth.

Naturally, this pill wasn’t any ordinary pill. After consuming it, the injured person began to slowly look better. However, the person was still dazed from the experience. The protector who fed him the pill quickly sent the disciple to the small boat before returning to his post.

After that first incident, more and more people began spurting out blood. They were also fed a medicinal pill before being sent to the small boat to rest.

Seeing this happen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown as he said, “It looks like the Cultivation Realm has found out a way to treat the backlash caused by astral winds. However, those who failed still looked very terrible. They would need some time before they could fully recover. This allows us to have a faint idea of the Cultivation Realm’s talents.”

Laura and the others nodded. Of the hundred people that tried to absorb astral qi, 70 people were already eliminated. However, the five protectors seemed to be unfazed by it. They kept looking after those who were left. As if everything was within their expectations.

As more and more people failed, five people were left in the end. These five were sweating hard and their faces were terrifyingly red.

However, these five people endured. As for the five protectors, their expressions began turning bright at the sight of these remaining disciples. They were experienced people, and they were already aware that it was highly probable for these five remaining disciples to succeed.

Sure enough, after five hours of waiting, the five disciples stopped absorbing astral qi. By this point, their own spiritual qi has astral qi merged with it.

Although these five people were in extreme pain and were very weak, all of them were ecstatic. The same was true for the five protectors. They immediately took the five and then led them to the small boat. Then they quickly operated the boat to leave the planet. From the beginning up to the end, the group didn’t fight any beast in Yellowsand Planet. Moreover, their time spent here was very short, only a few couple of hours.

When he saw the cultivators leave, Zhao Hai frowned for a moment before he chuckled and said, “It seems like astral qi isn’t easily absorbed. Those five might have succeeded, but they still haven’t fully digested the astral qi. This shouldn’t be able to dramatically increase their strength. Hmmm. It seems like I have overestimated them.”

Laura shook her head and said, “Brother Hai, you still need to be careful. You shouldn’t just look at them at their current state. Since they were able to absorb astral qi, then it would be easier for them to absorb more in the future. After absorbing astral qi a few times more, their offensive strength would be much more powerful. As for those who failed, they could no longer absorb astral qi. We’ve checked this information with Margaret. The Ashley Family’s files have information about this. Therefore, it shouldn’t be false.”

When Zhao Hai turned to Margaret, she nodded and said, “It’s true. The first time condensing astral qi is a dividing line. Once you succeed, then condensing more astral qi in the future would be easier. But if you failed the first time, it would no longer be possible for you to absorb astral qi. Even if you can bear the pain, as long as astral qi enters your body, you will immediately be injured. This isn’t something that can be avoided.”

Chapter 1174: Practice

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “No matter what, we know that the Cultivation Realm is much stronger than the Machine Field. It’s quite clear seeing how the fleet reacted to the small boat. They couldn’t do anything else other than turn around and flee. We need to increase our strength if we want to win.”

Laura nodded and then she said, “There’s still a few days before the start of the next round of the qualifiers. What does Brother Hai want to do?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll be closing up. Margaret, when you leave, please tell the General Manager that I’ll be closing up. Tell him that I’ll need some food and drinks delivered to my room and that I’ll have you take care of me. This way, nobody should disturb us. Then you can head to back here as I try to condense astral qi in the yellowsand background.”

Laura and the others weren’t surprised to hear Zhao Hai trying to absorb astral qi. They also weren’t worried about him. Now that the Space has its own yellowsand background, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be in any danger at all. Therefore, none of them stopped Zhao Hai from doing so.

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she immediately nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll take care of it.” Then her body flashed as she left the Space. Then she promptly reported that Zhao Hai was going to do closed door cultivation.

Zhao Hai didn’t leave. Instead he turned to Laura and said, “I’ll be heading to the yellowsand background to practice. If I hadn’t come out when the round is about to start, have Cai’er call me.”

Laura and the others nodded. Then Zhao Hai’s body flashed as he reappeared inside the yellowsand background. Upon appearing, Zhao Hai once again felt the winds of Yellowsand Planet. Since the background took after the planet, it wasn’t strange that the two places were quite similar.

Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to the surroundings. To be honest, there wasn’t much to see in the yellowsand background. Zhao Hai sat down on the ground and controlled his breathing. Once he reached a comfortable state, Zhao Hai stood up and began performing the body tempering fist.

But this time, as Zhao Hai was using the fist techniques, he also tried using the astral qi concentrating art. This wasn’t an easy task. One must know that the Stellar Transformation Body Tempering Technique was a special technique for body tempering. The main function of this method was attracting the power of the stars into the user’s body.

However, the power of the stars was quite powerful. It can be said that it was much more powerful than astral qi. The energy between the two was just different. In such a case, using the technique in order to attract astral qi instead would be very difficult.

But just like the Stellar Transformation Body Tempering Technique, the most important and most difficult step for condensing astral qi was introducing it into the body. It was essential for the user to be sober during this process since they need to quite the astral qi using their spiritual force. Otherwise, the astral qi would rampage. Astral qi wasn’t a docile type of energy. If one loses control over it, then their body would certainly be damaged.

Zhao Hai was much more uncomfortable when concentrating astral qi. This was because the body tempering technique was already a painful process. Adding astral qi to the mix made the process much more painful than before.

However, since Zhao Hai had already underwent body tempering before, his capacity for pain has been increased. But even if this was the case, Zhao Hai was still sweating buckets. His entire body hurt so much.

Fortunately, the body tempering technique didn’t let Zhao Hai suffer for long. In less than an hour, he was able to do one circulation of the technique. When this was completed, a bit of astral qi had been completely integrated into Zhao Hai’s body.

Once Zhao Hai discovered that the astral qi had been integrated into the body tempering technique, he began to do his second cycle. But this time, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to absorb any astral qi. This was because he saw that even if the astral qi had entered his body, it had yet to be fully absorbed. Therefore, Zhao Hai needed to refine it more to make the astral qi his own.

So in his second go, Zhao Hai didn’t use the astral qi concentrating art. He still used the separation between body and mind, which he used when practicing the stellar body tempering technique. This way, he could feel less pain. Zhao Hai knew that he just absorbed astral qi into his body and he needed to digest it. This way he would truly refine the astral qi.

If people from the Cultivation Realm knew about Zhao Hai’s plan, they would definitely be surprised. This was because Zhao Hai’s method wasn’t the same as theirs. Their method was combining astral qi to their spiritual qi. This way, whenever they attack, its offensive strength would be more powerful.

However, what Zhao Hai was doing wasn’t like the ordinary method. Not only did Zhao Hai absorb astral qi to combine with his spiritual qi, he was also using astral qi to temper his body.

If the Cultivation Realm heard about this, they would certainly think that Zhao Hai was crazy. Astral qi combining with spiritual qi was already very painful. The pain from using astral qi to temper one’s body should hurt a lot more.

And Zhao Hai did it the first time. But to be honest, the process hurt so much. It almost reached the limit that Zhao Hai could bear. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t let more astral qi enter his body. Instead, he decided to digest it first.

After separating his consciousness from his body, Zhao Hai began using his body to perform the fist techniques. But as he continued to perform the techniques, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel puzzled. This was because he discovered that his body seems to be faster at performing the body tempering technique.

But even if this was the case, Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t stop. If he suddenly stopped in the middle of the routine, all of the previous results would be wasted. Therefore, he continued. And while he was doing so, he discovered that as he refined his astral qi, his spiritual force was getting consumed more and more.

When the routine ended, Zhao Hai let out a long breath. Then he had his spiritual force inspect his body. This was his most strenuous body tempering routine yet. After the routine, Zhao Hai felt that his spiritual force had been exhausted. This caused Zhao Hai to feel strange. One must know that Zhao Hai’s spiritual force was fully capable of supporting three routines of the body tempering technique.

And as Zhao Hai continued inspecting his body, he couldn’t help but stare. This was because the current situation wasn’t something that he expected.

When he absorbed astral qi into his body before, he could feel that there were traces of astral qi that hadn’t been fully combined with his spiritual qi and body. But actually, these traces were very faint. If Zhao Hai didn’t use his spiritual force to feel them, he couldn’t feel their presence.

Zhao Hai knew that even if he was able to digest astral qi into his spiritual qi and body, then he still wouldn’t be able to feel a thing. But now, when he scanned his body, he discovered that this wasn’t the case at all. His spiritual qi was improved, his spiritual force had become tougher as well. Most importantly, Zhao Hai could feel that the amount of astral qi in his body was far more than he imagined. It was more than what he calculated before.

Zhao Hai paused for a moment before thinking about why this was the case. Then in the end he thought of an answer. It might be related to the Stellar Body Tempering Technique.

The body tempering technique was beyond formidable. And after separating his consciousness and body, the Stellar Body Tempering Technique would draw in stellar energy in order to temper the body. And in the process of drawing the power of the stars, it also reinforces the user’s spiritual force. So as Zhao Hai uses the tempering technique, both of his body and spiritual force were enhanced.

This was the reason why Zhao Hai felt that there was more astral qi inside his body than he expected. Moreover, it was completely unified with his body and spiritual qi. It can be said that concentrating astral qi had been more than a success.

But what made Zhao Hai even more surprised was the fact that some astral qi had integrated into his spiritual force. Zhao Hai discovered that his spiritual force now had some elements of astral qi, even if it was a very small amount. Zhao Hai just didn’t know what this development would entail.

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind in the end. This astral qi wasn’t astral qi that existed outside, it was astral qi produced by the Space. It was impossible for the Space to harm the host. Instead of being harmless, this union would instead be beneficial.

Zhao Hai inspected his spiritual force and discovered that it was tougher than before. If it was a silk thread before he underwent the body tempering technique, then it became like a steel wire after the tempering technique, it was now an alloy steel wire after being merged with astral qi.

When he discovered this, Zhao Hai was elated. But even if he was happy, he didn’t immediately go back to practice. This was because his spiritual force had dried up. Even if a depletion of spiritual force wasn’t harmful to his body, one shouldn’t forget that the Stellar Body Tempering Technique and the Concentrating Astral Qi Art needed to be carefully controlled. Otherwise, it would be easy for him to go crazy.

Although these things had been curated by the Space and were deemed non-harmful to Zhao Hai, this didn’t mean that the Space could protect him if he practiced wrong. After all, Zhao Hai’s spiritual qi was inside his body, only he could affect it.

Zhao Hai went out of the yellowsand background and then went to the hot spring to take a bath. Then after he was refreshed and relaxed, he returned to the villa. At this time, Margaret had already come back. Meanwhile, Laura and the others were looking into news regarding the Machine Field. This was because the elimination round had a lot of casualties. The machine field was currently in a depressive atmosphere.

These deaths were talents that were nurtured by small influences. Resources and time were poured into them. But then, they just died in Yellowsand Planet. This caused these small powers to get angry and start to question the fairness of the elimination round.

Chapter 1175: The Perverse Yin Yang Sect

 When the elimination round started, Zhao Hai thought that it was very unfair. There were only a few who spoke up about this at that time, so Zhao Hai’s concern was not very effective.

But now, the situation was different. In order to gain benefits for their family, small powers cultivated talents using their resources. But in the elimination round, almost all of them lost every talent they invested time and resources in. Because of this, these small powers were very unsatisfied with the result. They thought that this was the huge powers trying to suppress their growth.

It wasn’t only these small powers were unsatisfied, medium powers didn’t like the results as well. In fact, the Ashley Family was one of them.

Although they had Zhao Hai, the Ashley Family still couldn’t accept the results. They lost 7 people in the elimination round. And if it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then they might have lost even more. Because of this, every one of these groups lodged complaints towards the qualifier committee. They wanted to form an investigation team to see who proposed the survival elimination round. They wanted to know why it was proposed and for what purpose it was approved.

This matter escalated to the point where the three major powers could no longer control it. Although it can be said that the Machine Field was mostly controlled by the three major powers, one shouldn’t forget that these powers were formed by a collective of groups. And these collective comprised of large and small powers. Majority of which were the medium and small-scale powers. Normally, these medium and small powers operated independently. Some of them even had grudges against one another. Because of this, the three major powers were able to trump against these powers.

But this time, these small powers were all agitated. They managed to form an alliance to pressure the three major powers.

With this situation in hand, the three major powers couldn’t do anything else other than to relent to their request. The small and medium powers formed an investigation team to look into this matter. The Ashley Family also joined this investigation team.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t have anything to do with this matter. After all, he was closing up. Zhao Hai practiced his stellar body tempering technique and would also absorb some astral qi from time to time.

Not only was Zhao Hai absorbing astral qi for himself, Liquid Silver was also improving itself. Zhao Hai didn’t have to worry about controlling Liquid Silver since the Space can already handle it. After all, Liquid Silver was something that was made by the Space.

While Zhao Hai was practicing, another huge matter exploded in the Machine Field. Up until now, the investigation team formed by the small and medium powers had little progress. But suddenly, a person emerged, he was the person who proposed the elimination round.

The investigation team initially wanted to find him, but this person disappeared. Even after looking for a long time, he was still nowhere to be found. This time, he appeared on his own initiative. The reason for his emergence was to ask for protection from the investigation team.

Right, he wanted protection because he was being chased down. According to him, some people wanted to get rid of him since he was a potential witness. His proposal for the elimination round was under the command of some people. He said that these people were from the Divine Earth Palace and the Fire Temple. Besides these two churches, there were also several famous Warrior Clans. It can be said that these groups were large influences in the Machine Field.

The information he brought to light caused huge ripples throughout the Machine Field. They didn’t expect an evil manipulator behind the scenes.

The small and medium powers immediately formed an alliance. And then they collectively went against these several huge powers.

The exposure of this matter severely damaged the reputation of these huge powers. After all, the small influences respected these huge powers. Although it was mainly because of their strength, they were also looked up to because they could offer protection. They could represent the small powers and fight for benefits on their behalf.

But this exposure caused the small powers to see these huge powers in a new light. In a word, these huge powers were playing dirty!

Correct, now, in the eyes of these small powers, the great powers were actually playing dirty! These small powers clearly knew that they couldn’t take the lion’s share of benefits away from these huge powers. It was already certain that these huge powers would get most of the benefits. But these small powers were also aware that they couldn’t get everything or else they would have problems digesting it. Therefore, they allowed these huge powers to get the most things. But these huge powers actually withheld everything from them. This was unacceptable for the small powers.

The huge influences didn’t expect that the strength of the alliance would actually be so tremendous. All of a sudden, the huge forces found out that their products could no longer be sold, causing their factories to stop production. Their incomes dropped sharply. At the same time, their fleets and Mechs no longer had freedom they once enjoyed. This was because they discovered that their enemy was a hundred times stronger than themselves!

Whether it is quality or quantity of mechs and battleships, the alliance of small forces far surpassed those of the big powers. Before long, the Machine Field’s ecosystem changed.

Nobody thought this matter to evolve into the big thing it was now. There were many significant events in history that was caused by the littlest of things. And it was clear that this was one of those events.

Because of the event that happened in the Machine Field, the Six Realm Beginner Competition had to be postponed. In the beginning, it was postponed for ten days, then it became a month, and then it was postponed even more. At this point, there was no definite match date for the competition. It can be seen from these points that the three major powers had completely lost control of the Machine Field.

The smell of gunpowder in the Machine Field got stronger and stronger. It seems like even the smallest of sparks would ignite the entire realm. It wasn’t only the huge influences that sensed this, the small and medium powers could also feel it. If any one of them makes a move, then the others would make sure to not elevate the situation.

And because everyone had the same thought about this, the Machine Field was able to keep its peace. However, the huge influences decided to make a concession. They began sending representatives to the small and medium powers in order to perform a joint investigation.

With more people working on this matter, a result was found before long. Upon seeing this result, every single power in the Machine Field, including the three major powers, were shocked. What they found out that this event wasn’t accidental. Behind this event was an evil power in the Cultivation Realm.

The core of this matter included famous families in the Fire Temple, among them was the Zhang Family that was hostile towards Zhao Hai. The same was true for the Divine Earth Palace as well as the Warrior Families. As it turns out, these people were controlled by a fairly known sect in the Cultivation Realm, the Yin Yang Sect!

The Yin Yang Sect was quite famous in the Cultivation Realm. This wasn’t because they were well-respected by the Cultivators. Instead, it was because they belong to the evil faction. At the same time, they also have some forces in the Devil Realm. What they liked to do was to sabotage other forces. Their cultivation method was very strange, they practiced the Dao of Ruthlessness!

Ruthlessness was the core of the Dao of Ruthlessness, there was nothing else that needed to be said about it. The ruthlessness of this dao wasn’t the same as ordinary ruthlessness. The people in the Yin Yang Sect believed that if one wanted to be ruthless, then they must feel emotions first, and then they would use this emotion to cultivate their ruthlessness.

There were quite a number of people in the Cultivation Realm that cultivated the Dao of Ruthlessness, most of them were from the evil faction. In order to cultivate this dao, they would select a child with a good aptitude and then accept them to their sect. When these children had grown up, a person from the sect would take them back to their families and then kill them in front of their eyes. This would break the child’s emotions.

Seeing their family being killed, these children would have their emotions riled up. This was the optimum condition to cultivate the Dao of Ruthlessness.

But even among the ones who cultivated the Dao of Ruthlessness, the Yin Yang Sect was a special case. Although they practiced the same dao, the way they cultivate it was different from the other sects.

When they select their disciples, the Yin Yang Sect did the same thing as the other sects. They would find children with good aptitude and then train them. However, what happened next was different. Other sects would take the children back to their homes and then kill the child’s parents in front of the child. On the other hand, the Yin Yang Sect would have the child kill their family personally!

If these children couldn’t do it, then the sect would take action. However, they wouldn’t kill the child. Instead, they would torture the family members up until the point where death was their only release. Then they would have the child kill their family members.

Because of this conduct, the disciples of the Yin Yang Sect grew abnormally, allowing them to be the best candidates for the Dao of Ruthlessness. It was because of this that the people from the Yin Yang sect enjoyed upturning other groups and sects. And this time, the Yin Yang Sect had their eyes on the Machine Field.

After investigating the suspected groups, the investigation team found out that there were saboteurs from the Yin Yang sect among them. Moreover, these saboteurs were in important positions in these families. For the Zhang Family, it was the most beloved wife of the Zhang Family’s Patriarch. This meant that Zhang Mingyue was the son of the Zhang Family and the Yin Yang Sect!

The Machine Field was in an uproar immediately after finding out of this situation. Although these people from the Yin Yang Sect were strong, it was still difficult for them to escape upon being besieged by mechs and battleships. At the same time, all those who had any relations to these saboteurs were executed. And the families that were involved in the matter were being heavily punished!

Chapter 1176: Seeded Participants

As the clouds in the Machine Field settled down, the people from the Machine Field were finally able to see something they never expected. A lot of families including the Zhang Family disappeared like smoke. Even the Fire Temple and the Divine Earth Palace needed to reorganize themselves after the event.

Although there were a lot of things left to do in the Machine Field, the time needed to accomplish them wasn’t that much. It took two months for all sides to settled down. And all these days Zhao Hai didn’t appear. Not only Zhao Hai, the other ten great experts were nowhere in sight. After all, they didn’t have any place to participate in this matter.

However, two of the ten experts were implicated in this wave that crashed down in the Machine Field. One of them was Meteor Zhu Chen. Zhu Chen was from the Divine Earth Palace. And in the recent elimination round, he was seen slaughtering people, incurring the discontent of many powers. As it turns out, this was another plot by the Yin Yang Sect. Zhu Chen became the Yin Yang Sect’s blade. At the same time, he was also a victim of their plot.

Another expert that was implicated was Fire Saint Sun Fei. He was a candidate trained by the Zhang Family. His situation was the same as Zhu Chen, he was being used as a blade.

However, unlike their patrons, the two were treated differently by the Machine Field. Even if the Machine Field exterminated the Zhang Family’s core members, Sun Fei was from the External Hall. The Machine Field already treated these ascenders differently, therefore, the two weren’t treated as harshly as the family they belonged to.

This wasn’t out of Zhao Hai’s expectation. After all, from the perspective of the Machine Field’s forces, Sun Fei and Zhu Chen were useful tools, like sharp knives. Would you punish a knife that was used to commit sin? Of course not. The knife was just a tool. The person who used it was the guilty party.

This was the case with Sun Fei and Zhu Chen. The two killed a lot of people, yes, but they had the strength to make the other powers think about recruiting them.

As long as those two join any power, that power would instantly get a place among the 100 participants of the Six Realm Beginner Competition. In this case, nobody would want to pass up on them.

However, an issue came up when there were a lot of people who wanted to get the two of them. In the end, nobody was able to properly recruit them. This matter became the center of the Machine Field’s attention. Even the Ashley Family participated in this competition.

Although Sun Fei has killed a lot of the Ashley Family’s participants, these participants were from the External Hall. If the family could trade a few talents for a true talent, then they would do so without hesitation.

Zhao Hai knew about these matters, but he didn’t do anything about it. This was because he was still closing up. But his practice session was about to end. At fixed times, he would go to the yellowsand background and then practice his body tempering technique. He already stopped absorbing astral qi, this was because his astral qi had already reached a saturated state.

At this point, his body, spiritual qi, and even spiritual force had astral qi in them. Because of this, even if Zhao Hai deliberately absorbed astral qi, there would be no place in his body to place it, making his efforts useless. Therefore, Zhao Hai would just go to the yellowsand background in order to digest the astral qi he had accumulated.

Zhao Hai also tried to see the strength of astral qi. During that time, Zhao Hai was given a scare. Whether it be his magic formations or his sword qi, its offensive power had been increased by about five to ten times. Things would get even more insane if Liquid Silver was added to the mix.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect astral qi to be this strong when he started. Moreover, he discovered that, besides the first time, his digestion of astral qi was getting faster and faster. This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled.

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind when he understood what was happening. The first time he absorbed astral qi, he needed to maintain sober in order to guide astral qi using his spiritual force. At the same time, he also needed to perform the stellar body tempering technique. This amount of pain was something that no other man could endure. Because of this process, Zhao Hai was able to make his body much more suitable for astral qi. Although Zhao Hai separated his consciousness and body on his next session to escape the pain, the amount of astral qi he managed to absorb at that time was a lot.

And after Zhao Hai separated his consciousness and body, things became different. He could still practice, but this time he didn’t torture himself with the pain. With this situation, it would naturally speed up Zhao Hai’s absorption and digestion of astral qi.

Zhao Hai estimated that his current offensive strength wouldn’t be any worse than Cultivators of his level. If he used all of his strength, then he might even compete against Nascent Soul experts.

Naturally, this was just Zhao Hai’s own estimate. He had yet to fight a Cultivator, so a lot of factors were still unknown.

As for the matters of the Machine Field, Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. He doesn’t have the strength to affect the big picture, so he could only observe from the Space’s monitor.

The disturbance in the Machine Field didn’t last very long. The Patriarchs of the families in the Machine Field weren’t stupid. They clearly knew that if the realm were to turn chaotic, the Cultivation Realm may use the opportunity to make a move.

Besides their fear of being attacked by the Cultivation Realm, the reason these heads of the powers decided to solve the matter quickly was because of the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

If they didn’t deal with this matter soon, then they would only be harming their benefits in the competition.

Although the Machine Field hasn’t been getting good results in the Six Realm Beginner competition, there were still rewards for participating. And the competition this time was much more important, given how much talent the Machine Field has been able to produce. Therefore, nobody in the Machine Field would want to miss the opportunity to join the competition.

Since there had been a reshuffle and even elimination of some great families, this meant that the smaller powers would be getting a bigger slice of the pie.

Sun Fei and Zhu Chen’s assignment had already been determined. Zhu Chen was still under the Divine Earth Palace while Sun Fei was taken in by the Fire Temple. The two became direct members of the churches and weren’t under any family.

Zhao Hai agreed to the arrangement made by the Machine Field’s higher ups. Due to the recent scuffle, the Divine Earth Palace and the Fire Temple had been heavily damaged. It was proper for Zhu Chen and Sun Fei to gain benefits for them. This would allow the two churches to restore their strength.

This decision was most likely influenced by the Mage Church Alliance. The three major forces of the Machine Field, Church Alliance, Mech Army, and the Warrior Association needed to be balanced. This way the realm would maintain its peace.

The Fire Temple and the Divine Earth Palace had lost so much. And since these two were important pillars of the Church Alliance, they needed to regain their strength or else they would weaken the Alliance. Because of this, the Machine Field’s high-level figures went on with their decision.

However, another matter occured that surprised Zhao Hai. The small influenced began to discover the power they had when they united. They saw that they now had enough influence to talk with the major powers.

There were thousands of small forces in this alliance. They also elected leaders to fight for them. They had the intention of being equal to the three major powers.

But since this alliance was still on its starting stages, they didn’t have much to work on. Moreover, the three major powers couldn’t just leave them be. Therefore, even if these small forces were happy with their current state, they still couldn’t get whatever they wanted.

As things went on, the date for the Six Realm Beginner Competition was finally set. And because of this, the Machine Field’s qualifiers needed to change. What differs the Machine Field from the other realms this time was the existence of seeded players. All of these seeded players were geniuses with a level no lower than level 4.

There were a total of 20 seeded players, ten of them were from the ten great experts. Nobody objected to this decision. As for the next ten, the committee as well as the top ten experts nominated participants. And ranked on the 11th spot was Zhao Hai!

The first person to nominate Zhao Hai to be a seeded player was Xiong Li, and the second was Sun Fei. Although it can be said that Sun Fei’s reputation had taken a huge dive recently, he was still quite a famous individual in the Machine Field. Additionally, he was a strong competitor. Therefore, there were a lot of people who favored his nomination. His proposal for Zhao Hai to be a seeded participant was a huge surprise to everyone. Everyone knew that he had been enemies with Zhao Hai. Moreover, they heard that he and Zhao Hai had clashed back in Yellowsand Planet. Although the two hadn’t fought, their meeting was still bad. Sun Fei nominating Zhao Hai was quite unexpected.

Of course, Xiong Li’s nomination for Zhao Hai also gave people some surprise. But after some time, people found out that Xiong Li and Zhao Hai were friends. Xiong Li’s nomination for Zhao Hai wasn’t strange, he just wanted to help a friend.

In the beginning, only a few people heard about this information. However, as time passed, people found out about it. This caused a huge pressure for the qualifier committee. After all, the committee hasn’t handled the qualifiers that well. Although the members of the committee had long since been changed, the trust to the organization remained negative.

But at this time, Xiong Li defended his stance. He stated that his friendship with Zhao Hai in Yellowsand Planet had nothing to do with his nomination. Moreover, Xiong li openly admitted that even he might not be able to win against Zhao Hai.

Xiong Li’s admittance caused the Machine Field to pause. There were very few people who saw Zhao Hai make a move. Zhao Hai’s ascend and his rise to power was something that surprised many people. And now, Xiong Li admitted that he wasn’t sure of winning against Zhao Hai. This caused more interest towards Zhao Hai.

But when these people tried to look into Zhao Hai, they discovered that Zhao Hai acted very low-key. He had already ascended for quite a few months already, but he spent most of his time closing up. There were very few people who saw him coming out, so there were so few records of his appearance. This caused even more interest to gather towards him.

Very soon, Zhao Hai’s place as the 11th seated candidate was settled. Xiong Li and Sun Fei’s recommendation as well as the committee’s investigation determined that Zhao Hai was qualified to be seeded.

Naturally, Zhao Hai’s wasn’t clueless about these matters. He stayed inside the Space all this time as he watched the changes happening in the Machine Field. At the same time, he was settling matters inside the Space.

Karen’s laboratory has been churning out significant results. Since they learned magic theory, their study towards magic formations went on the right track. It can be said that their experiments weren’t as simple as before. At this point, those kinds of research no longer interested them. What they liked to do now was to research new magic formations.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything regarding Karen’s current actions. He decided to just let them be and perhaps they might bring him a pleasant surprise.

The other races in the Space were also doing very well. Even if they didn’t have much changes, this didn’t mean that they were slow in their development. After all, they hadn’t been inside the Space for long. Undergoing a huge change in a short time was almost impossible.

On the other hand, Margaret became even busier than Zhao Hai. In the past, Margaret just had a general understanding of the Space. But as she knew more and more about it, she became awed by the mystery of its existence. Margaret now preferred to stay inside the Space instead of going outside.

As for Zhao Hai’s closed door cultivation, the Ashley Family did their best so that nobody would disturb him. No matter what happens outside, the Ashley Family guaranteed that Zhao Hai was not to be disturbed. To be honest, Zhao Hai appreciated their efforts.

The Ashley Family did this also because Zhao Hai was their hope to gain benefits. Therefore, no matter what Zhao Hai wants to do, the Ashley Family would give him their full support.

Moreover, the Ashley Family truly hoped that Zhao Hai would close up all this time, This was because the current Machine Field was too chaotic. It wouldn’t be good for Zhao Hai to participate in it.

After the seeded participants were selected, the date for the competition was decided, and the groupings were prepared, the only thing that everyone needed to do was wait for the next round to start!

Chapter 1177: Heading Out

Zhao Hai finally went out of the Space. Although Margaret liked to stay inside the Space, she had to come out with Zhao Hai since the next round of the qualifiers was about to begin.

But since Zhao Hai was a seeded participant, he doesn’t need to participate in the beginning stages. At this point, there were 20 thousand people left who were qualified for the next round. Although some of them had withdrawn, there were still more than 10 thousand people left who would participate.

About more than 10 thousand people competing for 100 spots. One could imagine how fierce the competition would be. But things were much easier for seeded participants like Zhao Hai. They wouldn’t need to participate in the beginning rounds.

Nobody objected to this system of having seeded participants. This was because these seeded participants were the powerful experts the Machine Field had. They already had some reputation in the Machine Field, so everyone knew that they were strong. Also, this was the smart thing to do. And even if one was a seeded player, they would still face the more powerful participants in the final rounds.

The reason for seeded positions was the fear of two powerful experts meeting in battle prematurely. If there were no seeded participants, then all remaining participants would be in the pool for selection. It might be possible for Xiong Li to meet Streep in the first round. This means that one would be eliminated while a lucky level 3 would defeat their opponent and progress to the next round. Naturally, those who weren’t strong wouldn’t be able to reach the top 100. However, if either Xiong Li or Streep were eliminated and couldn’t join the Six Realm Beginner Competition, it would be a huge loss for the Machine Field.

Because of this consideration, the Machine Field chose 20 people to be seeded. They also want to see how this would go. If it had great results, then they would select seeded participants for every qualifiers from now on.

Upon hearing that Zhao Hai had come out, Cadjo took Desbarres and Luke to Zhao Hai’s room. While Zhao Hai was closing up, only Luke was in the building since Cadjo and Desbarres returned to the family. They were Elders of the family. Moreover, due to the restless state of the Machine Field in the past few days, they were needed to help settle things.

The Ashley Family wasn’t implicated by the situation in the Machine Field. On the contrary, they benefited a lot since they participated in the investigations. Because of the Ashley Family’s position, they were able to lead teams and gain benefits for the family.

The Ashley Family’s time had truly come. They no longer needed to deal with the Zhang Family. And now that the Zhang Family has been eliminated, the Ashley Family were able to absorb some of the members of their camps and they were even able to get several factories. These gains were certainly good for the family.

Then there was Zhao Hai being nominated for a seeded position. This caused the family to be ecstatic. It can be said that the Ashley Family was in a festive mood. So upon hearing that Zhao Hai had come out, Cadjo immediately took Desbarres and Luke to visit him.

Seeing that the three had come to see him, Zhao Hai immediately asked them to sit down. Margaret offered some them some tea before sitting beside Zhao Hai.

Cadjo looked at Margaret and Zhao Hai’s intimate appearance and didn’t give a comment. For three months, Margaret had been inside Zhao Hai’s room while Zhao Hai was closing up. By this point, their relationship had gone public. Moreover, Thunder didn’t object to the two of them. It was as if he already gave a nonverbal agreement to their relationship.

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, did you benefit a lot from your cultivation?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “My harvest isn’t small. The reason I closed up is because I had been contaminated by astral qi back when I was in Yellowsand Planet. I only noticed it after coming back. Therefore, I closed up so that I can refine it. Fortunately, I was able to succeed.”

As soon as Zhao Hai said this, Cadjo and the other stared for a moment before their expressions changed. Cadjo quickly said, “Little Hai, you’re able to refine astral qi? You’re kidding right?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I won’t joke about this. Don’t forget, I’m both a Mage and a Warrior. If I wasn’t, then it would be impossible for me to refine astral qi. But since I’m a Mage and a Warrior, I had the chance to successfully refine it.”

When he heard this, Cadjo laughed out loud and said, “Good, that’s fantastic. Fortune is really looking down on the Ashley Family. Little Hai, how is your offensive strength now? I heard that as long as one concentrates astral qi, their offensive strength would be outstanding.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, as long as it is absorbed by my body, the offensive strength of my attacks are enhanced. My formations are now much more powerful than before, even if I use the same amount of spiritual qi.”

Cadjo’s smile turned brighter, then he said, “That’s good. It seems like the seat of this qualifier’s champion is already reserved for you. Perhaps you might even get a good place in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. Our Ashley family will then be praised by the entire World of Cultivation.”

Desbarres nodded, he was also smiling as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you’ll have to work hard this time. Make the Cultivation Realm know that our Machine Field couldn’t be bullied.”

A lot of things happened in the Machine Field in the past few days. But in the end, all of the blame fell into the Yin Yang Sect. The Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm had always minded their separation. Although there were some scuffles from time to time, these were small conflicts. But this time, the Yin Yang Sect caused a huge chaos to descend into the Machine Field. Even if they didn’t know the stance of the other sects in the Cultivation Realm, the Machine Field still decided to be on guard.

Although it can be said that the Machine Field really wanted to retaliate against the Yin Yang Sect, the individual strength of the Machine Field is just too low. If the Machine Field sent battleships to the Cultivation Realm in order to deal with the Yin Yang Sect, the Cultivation Realm’s sects would certainly stop them.

Because of this, Desbarres and the others could only suppress the anger in their hearts. They were born and raised in the Machine Field. Because of this, they had a very strong sense of belonging towards the realm. The Machine Field had always been held down by the Cultivation Realm. Whenever Cultivators looked at the people from the Machine Field, all of them would raise their noses up high. There was no way for Desbarres and the others to agree to this.

Therefore, the Six Realm Beginner Competition has given them the opportunity to vent their anger. If Zhao Hai didn’t make any breakthrough, then Desbarres might not be this confident. But after Zhao Hai was able to concentrate astral qi, Desbarres was even more certain of Zhao Hai’s success.

Most of Zhao Hai’s understanding of the Machine Field had come from the computer.  But in the end, a computer was just an inanimate object, there were a lot of things that weren’t true in it. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t know what impact someone who absorbed astral qi to the people in the Machine Field.

The Machine Field didn’t have any way to absorb astral qi. This has restricted the individual ability of the soldiers in the Machine Field. To be honest, the magical spells of the Machine Field weren’t any weaker than any other attacks in the Cultivation Realm. Once someone was able to layer 1 thousand formations, they would have the same strength as a Core Formation Expert.

However, the Machine Field didn’t have any technique to absorb astral qi and evil qi. Because of this, they didn’t have any way to increase their offensive abilities.

Naturally, after many years, it was impossible for the Machine Field to have no way to absorb astral qi and evil qi. However, there were extremely few people who were able to do it. This has a lot to do with the current system of the Machine Field.

The Machine Field’s practice gave priority to the battle qi and magic. However, both battle qi and magic weren’t suitable for absorbing astral qi into the body.

Battle Qi specialized in refining the body from outside in. And when the blood was activated, it would produce energy, which was battle qi. Magic specialized in spiritual force. Instead of working on the body, it specializes in the mind. This made it hard to prepare the body for the introduction of astral qi.

And since battle qi specializes in the body, battle qi became tightly knit with the Warrior’s body. There were similar methods in the Cultivator Realm, but this method made it very hard to attract astral qi to one’s body. This method was just like Zhao Hai’s stellar body tempering technique. To be honest, if Zhao Hai couldn’t separate his body and consciousness, it would be impossible for astral qi to be digested into his body.

Practicing stellar body tempering technique was in itself very painful. Zhao Hai’s body had been adapted to the pain, allowing it to take in astral qi. If it were any other Warrior in the Machine Field, then they would not be able to endure the pain.

There was no need to talk about Mages. Mages specialize in spiritual force. Spiritual force was linked with the brain. Therefore, Mages needed to be careful whenever they cultivate their spiritual force, or else they would succumb to insanity. If their brains were to be heavily damaged, they would definitely turn into complete idiots in vegetative states.

It was for this reason that Mages wouldn’t dare combine astral qi with their spiritual force.

The reason why Zhao Hai was able to combine astral qi with his spiritual force was because of his ability to separate his consciousness and body. Actually, this method was truly ingenious.

It separates one’s mind to their body, turning them into spectators of themselves. So even if the mind was attacked, the body would stay in perfect condition. Additionally, with how strong Zhao Hai’s body was, nothing would be able to hurt him.

At the same time, since the astral qi that Zhao Hai absorbed came from the Space, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to be harmed. Because of this, Zhao Hai was able to succeed in absorbing astral qi!

Chapter 1178: Let’s Go Drink

Zhao Hai was calmly sitting on the arena’s stand. In the middle of the stadium was a huge platform. Its length and width exceeded 200 meters. It was made out of something that looked like bluestone. But actually, this bluestone was called bluesteel. It was a mineral that was very hard and heavy.

Ordinarily, this stadium was used for sports events. Although a lot of people cultivate magic and battle qi here, there were still some people who devoted their lives into sports. However, these sports weren’t ordinary sports. The sport was either formations or some wrestling matches. In addition to Mage and Warrior-related sports, there were also some competition about Mechs. These Mech competitions were quite popular in the Machine Field.

And since Mech matches happen here, the stadium needed to be very big. And this time, the realm qualifiers would be held here.

As for seeded participants like Zhao Hai and the others, since they wouldn’t fight in the first rounds, they had been given seats by the committee. These seats would be reserved for them so that they could watch from the sidelines and then understand the strength of their opponents.

Zhao Hai sat on his chair with Xiong Li next to him. Xiong Li looked for Zhao Hai several times these past few days. But every time he went to the Ashley Family’s building, Zhao Hai was in closed-door cultivation. This was the first time the two had met since Zhao Hai went out of the Space.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was staring at the platform, Xiong Li opened his mouth and said, “Brother, there’s nothing else to watch here. I can beat all of these people with one hand.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s true. Hahaha. Brother, let’s head out a get a drink.”

When he heard that Zhao Hai was asking him to drink, Xiong Li’s eyes shone as he said, “Good, good. Let’s have a drink. Right, wait for me here, I’ll introduce you to someone.” Zhao Hao nodded. Then Xiong Li left. Before long, Xiong Li came back alongside another person. Upon seeing the person Xiong Li brought along, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. He knew this person.

It was one of the ten great experts, Fire Dragon Sword Dongfang Yu! The person famous for his fire dragon sword as well as his fire dragon technique. It was said that every time this person went out for a mission, the result was complete destruction of the surrounding area. It was even rumoured that the money he gained from the mission wasn’t enough to compensate for the damage he did.

Upon seeing Dongfang Yu, Zhao Hai immediately gave his salute and said, “So it’s brother Dongfang. This one is Zhao Hai.”

Dongang Yu was a slim person. He wore Warrior clothing that was longer than average. His face was also quite dark, perhaps because of his long exposure to fire.

Dongfang Yu also returned Zhao Hai’s gesture as he laughed and said, “Hahaha, I’ve been hearing good things about Brother Zhao Hai from Brother Xiong Li. Brother Xiong Li rarely praised others. It seems like you’re also someone with real skill.” His voice was loud and clear. His straightforward manner of talking makes other people look favorably towards him.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brother Xiong Li is overly praising me. Let’s go and have a drink.” Then Zhao Hai led their group out of the stadium. Naturally, Zhao Hai’s group of three weren’t able to leave the area without being spotted. The other people looked at the three with gazes filled with envy, jealousy, and disdain. As for those participants who weren’t seeded, they couldn’t help but look at the three in envy.

At this time, a voice was suddenly heard, “Mister Zhao Hai, please wait.” Zhao Hai turned his head and saw that it was unexpectedly Fire Saint Sun Fei. The two didn’t have any friendly relationship. They also were no longer hostile to each other. The Ashley Family didn’t seek revenge since Sun Fei now belonged to the Fire Temple. The Fire Temple was also depending on Sun Fei to help them regain their strength. If the Ashley Family decided to retaliate against Sun Fei, then the Fire Temple would interfere. And it wasn’t a good time to have a conflict in the Machine Field.

Therefore, Cadjo told Zhao Hai that if he met Sun Fei, then he should spare his life unless it was under extreme circumstances. Not only Sun Fei, he was also told to spare the other 20 seeded participants. If he killed ordinary talents, then their families might let the matter go. But if a seeded participant dies, then it would be equivalent to breaking the benefits of their family. And naturally, the affected family would retaliate. However, if Zhao Hai was provoked, then he would certainly be impolite.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about this matter. Moreover, Sun Fei didn’t have a grudge against him, only the Ashley Family. In essence, this matter doesn’t have anything to do with him.

Therefore, upon seeing Sun Fei, Zhao Hai said, “So it’s brother Sun. Does Brother need anything from me?”

Sun Fei bowed towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, I have offended you back in Yellowsand Planet. Please excuse me.”

Upon hearing Sun Fei, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Brother Sun is too polite. At that time, you and I are under the command out our families. After all, we’re from the External Halls. What authority do we have to disobey orders? Brother Sun doesn’t need to apologize, it’s nothing.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei gave Zhao Hai a bow. Meanwhile, Xiong Li and Dongfang Yu sighed deep inside. This was because Zhao Hai just said what was inside their hearts. They were outsiders to this realm and they could only obey the commands of their patron. They were treated like weapons by their families, weapons that can be discarded at any time.

After Sun Fei gave a bow, he stood up. Then he looked at the three and said, “If you don’t have anything to do, then how about having this little brother treat you to a few drinks?”

Upon hearing Sun Fei, Xiong Li couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Kid, Brother Zhao Hai just beat you. Since this is the case, then you might as well come with us to share a few drinks. Let’s go.”

Upon hearing Xiong Li, everyone laughed before they walked out of the stadium. Seeing the four men, those who saw them couldn’t help but stare.

People already knew about Zhao Hai and Xiong Li’s friendship. As for Zhao Hai and Sun Fei, they two didn’t have any form of friendship. When Sun Fei nominated Zhao Hai to be a seeded participant, Zhao Hai was still closing up at that time. It can be said that the two didn’t have any friendship up until now.

And now, they were together to have a drink? This was the question on everyone’s mind.

Zhao Hai and the others proceeded to leave the stadium’s area. Outside, a car was waiting for Zhao Hai. This was a car that Cadjo had given Zhao Hai to use.

Once they got into the car, Zhao Hai turned to Xiong Li and said, “Brother Xiong, do you know of any place that has very good wine in the area? I have been closed up for a long time, I need something good to drink.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Since you asked me, then let’s go to Delin’s Barbecue. You need to taste their barbecue and liquor.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then let’s go with Brother Xiong’s suggestion. Take us to Delin’s Barbecue.” Zhao Hai didn’t tell the instruction to the car. Instead, this car actually had a driver. It was an assistant that was assigned to Zhao Hai in order to cater to his needs.

The driver nodded and then drove the car towards Delin’s Barbecue. Dongfang Yu looked at the driver before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “It seems like Brother Zhao is the most comfortable out of all of us. Not only do you have a car, you even have an assistant. I’m truly envious.”

Dongfang Yu wasn’t wrong at all. One must know that most families would only treat their core members like this. Members from the External Hall wouldn’t be treated like this. Unless you lead a battalion, is a Camp Lord, an Elder of the Family, or a functioning core member, you won’t get the same treatment as Zao Hai.

Upon hearing Dongfang Yu, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m just borrowing this in the meantime. Right, is this the place?” Zhao Hai looked at the building outside the car. The small building was made entirely out of wood. It looked much like a cabin in the forest, but much larger at four stories high.

Xiong Li nodded and said, “Right, we’re here. Their barbecue is roasted on top of high grade charcoal. It’s flavor is completely out of this world. It’s very delicious.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go have a taste.” Then the group got out of the car and then entered the building. Upon entering, they were immediately welcomed by someone. Much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, they weren’t served by a robot. Instead, it was a real person who met them. This made Zhao Hai even more curious about the owner of the establishment.

It was clear that this wasn’t Xiong Li’s first time in this place, so when he saw the waiter, he immediately said, “Prepare a private room for us.” The man nodded before leading the group further into the building.

The first and second floor of the building were public areas. The private rooms were placed on the third floor. These private rooms weren’t large. And since there were only four people in Zhao Hai’s group, they were settled inside a smaller private room.

After entering their room and then ordering their food and liquor, Xiong Li turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao, I heard that you’ve just ascended recently. Also, I heard that you’ve snagged a lady from the Ashley Family. And that you might become a core member of the family in the future. Are all of these true?”

Zhao Hai Hai smiled and said, “It’s true, I’m currently in a relationship with the Ashley Family’s Miss Margaret. She’s Patriarch Thunder’s daughter. But since her relationship with her father wasn’t good, she doesn’t rely on the family for her income. Therefore, she became an instructor at the Ascender Academy. She used to be my instructor, but now she’s my girlfriend.”

Xiong Li sighed and said, “You really move fast. Hahaha. But you are also talented. Who would expect you to reach level 4 in such a short time.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s nothing. I just have an innate talent for magic formations. Moreover, I already have strong spiritual force when I ascended. This is the reason why I improved so fast.”

After Zhao Hai said that, a disturbance was suddenly heard outside. Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but stare. One must know that they were in Machine Field Planet. Who had courage big enough to cause a huge disturbance here?

Chapter 1179: Rampant Machine Field Army Soldiers

Xiong Li also stared, then he frowned and said, “What’s happening? Someone actually dared cause trouble? I heard that Delin’s Barbecue is backed by the Fire Temple. Sun Fei, aren’t you from the Fire Temple? Do you know anything about this?”

Sun Fei shook his head and said, “I don’t know. I haven’t been in the Fire Temple for long. But Brother Xiong is correct. The major churches have businesses in the Machine Field Planet.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s very likely that Delin’s Barbecue has a powerful backer. The area it covered isn’t small. Moreover, it has four stories fully made out of wood. It’s impossible to do this if they didn’t have any backers. Let’s head out and see what’s happening. If the Fire Temple is in trouble, we’ll try our best to help.”

Xiong Li and the others didn’t object and just nodded. Then they all stood up and walked out. Just as they exited their room, they heard sounds coming from the second floor. As the group went downstairs, they saw people in military uniforms. These people didn’t have any imposing aura around them. However, they all stood straight and it seems like they knew some fighting techniques.

When Zhao Hai saw these people, he couldn’t help but raise his brow. Then he said, “Aren’t they Mech soldiers? Why are they causing trouble?”

Xiong Li and the others also looked over. When they saw the Mech soldiers, they couldn’t help but gawk. No ordinary person in Machine Field Planet would dare offend those from the Machine Field Army. The status of these soldiers were higher than Mages and Warriors.

Zhao Hai listened in on the conversation. After some time, he finally understood. These mech soldiers were here for a meal. But while they were ordering their food, one of them tried to hit on the waitress. Unfortunately, this waitress was the irritable type. As the soldier continued to flirt with her, the waitress gave him a slap. This caused the soldier to hit the waitress, causing the current disturbance.

Upon understanding the situation, Zhao Hai’s expression sank, then he coldly snorted. Zhao Hai’s snort wasn’t loud, but it was heard clearly throughout the floor. It was like a thunderclap on everyone’s ears.

Even Xiong LI and the others were shaken by Zhao Hai’s little snort. They couldn’t help but faintly smile. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong.

Naturally, these mech soldiers were also shaken. When they got their bearings back, all of them turned to Zhao Hai. Their leader was a burly man with short hair and was also wearing a military uniform. He looked quite strong. However, there was a slap mark on his face, which ruined his image.

This mech soldier looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Kid, what are you snorting at? Do you have indigestion? Why don’t you mind your own business?”

Zhao Hai looked at the mech soldier, then he smiled and said, “I was just eating upstairs and then I heard some wild dogs barking. It disturbed my appetite so I came down to see what is going on. Now I know that it’s not just dogs barking, but one of them actually tried to seamlessly extend their paws to someone else. Only wild dogs would dare bully a woman. It seems like the quality of the Machine Field Army soldiers are getting lower and lower.”

After Zhao Hai said that, Xiong Li and the others laughed out loud. The Mech soldier’s face turned red. But just before he was about to say something, a person behind him whispered something in his ear. The mech soldier’s face changed and he shifted the way he looked at Zhao Hai.

Upon seeing the soldier’s change in expression, Zhao Hai coldly smiled and said, “What? You know us? Why don’t you report us and see if your brothers will retaliate. If they would, then that’s fine. We can just report this matter and say that the law and order of this planet isn’t very good. There’s no guarantee for us to participate in the competition and we’ll just quit. You can find our replacements and I wish that they can get good results.”

The more these mech soldiers heard Zhao Hai, the more sweaty their backs became. They were mech soldiers who had higher status that ordinary Mages and Warriors, but who were Zhao Hai and the others? They were Machine Field’s highly-valued seeded participants. They would represent the Machine Field and compete against the other participants from the other realms.  There were only 20 people in this seeded list. It can be said that Zhao Hai’s group of four weren’t people anyone could offend right now. If Zhao Hai and the others really did what Zhao Hai said, then these mech soldiers would be dead.

While he was thinking about this, the mech soldier wiped sweat off his face. Then he calmed down as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So it is MIster Zhao Hai, Mister Xiong Li, Mister Dongfang Yu, and Mister Sun Fei. I’m a soldier from the 9th squad of the 4th company, 3rd battalion, 36th regiment, 2nd Division, 5th Corps of the ascender army, Wan He. It’s a pleasure to meet you gentlemen.”

The man gave Zhao Hai a greeting but he also expressed his identity. This caused Zhao Hai to raise an eyebrow. Then he said, “So you’re from the Machine Field Army. No wonder you’re so rampant. So you people came here to humiliate us now that the Church Alliance has been weakened? Do you know who opened this shop? This is the Fire Temple’s establishment.”

These mech soldiers were truly unaware of the owner of this shop. After all, they were just ordinary mech soldiers, they didn’t have any significant background. So after hearing Zhao Hai, they knew that they were wrong. The leader looked embarrassed, then he quickly said, “Please excuse our actions. We really don’t know who this shop’s owner is. We are willing to compensate for any damages we caused.”

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and knew that they were truly clueless. If they knew that this was Fire Temple’s establishment, then they wouldn’t have any courage to cause any trouble.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Since you’re not aware, I’ll let this matter go. I’ll leave it to you to settle things with the restaurant’s manager.”

The soldier quickly replied, “Of course. Please excuse us for disturbing your meal.” Then Zhao Hai nodded before he left along with Xiong Li and the others.

Once the group had returned to their room, Xiong Li smiled and said, “Brother Zhao, you’re good. Those mech soldiers are usually very prideful. But this time, they had to retreat. They looked like small puppies. Hahahaha. It’s satisfying!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They aren’t afraid of me, they’re just afraid of our current reputation. We’re seeded participants of the Machine Field. In the eyes of the higher-ups, one of us is more important than one hundred ordinary mech soldiers. They’re too scared to offend us. Hahaha.”

However, Sun Fei frowned and said, “Brother Zhao, we’ll have to thank you for your efforts. But I’m afraid that now that you have offended them, you’ll have more trouble in the future. After all, mech soldiers have great status in the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s true that he’s a mech soldier. However, he is just an ordinary mech soldier. Meanwhile, I’m an important member of the Ashley Family. He cannot do anything to me.”

Dongfang Yu said, “There’s no need to be afraid of those mech soldiers. But Brother Zhao, you have truly slapped their faces today. If they head back and talk to their brothers, I’m afraid those from the Machine Field Army would cause you some trouble. This time, 15 of the 20 seeded participants are from the Warrior Association and the Church Alliance while 5 of them are from the Machine Field Army. Moreover, those five aren’t weak. I’m afraid they will try to make trouble for you.”

Zhao Hai seemed to not care, he just smiled and said, “I’ll just hope that they won’t bother me. After all, all of us are from the same realm. But if they did come looking for trouble, then I’ll have to teach them a lesson.”

When Zhao Hai said this, he let out some of his killing intent. This caused Dongfang Yu and Sun Fei to stare. Then they felt the hair on their backs rise up. They had killed people before, moreover, their slaughters were quite frequent. Therefore, they were sensitive to killing auras. Because of this, they were able to feel Zhao Hai’s killing intent. The thickness of Zhao Hai’s killing aura was something that they had never seen before.

Actually, Sun Fei and Dongfang Yu still had some doubts about Zhao Hai’s strength. When Zhao Hai met people, he was very casual and didn’t have any imposing aura at all. If he wasn’t wearing mage robes, then people wouldn’t even think that he was a Mage. Additionally, Zhao Hai spent most of his time closing up. In their opinion, Zhao Hai was an ascetic Mage who didn’t have rich combat experience.

But after Zhao Hai’s short release of killing intent, Sun Fei and Dongfang Yu began to think that not only were they wrong about Zhao Hai’s lack of experience, they were also made aware that Zhao Hai had killed more people than they expected. Being able to hide his aura to an untraceable level was a very fearful ability to have.

On the other hand, Xiong Li wasn’t surprised. Xiong Li had much more experience in combat compared to Sun Fei and Dongfang Yu. He knew very well how dangerous of a person Zhao Hai was.

Just as Zhao Hai said that, the group suddenly heard someone call him out from outside, “Zhao Hai, come out here!”

Zhao Hai stared, then he looked at Xiong Li and the others as he smiled faintly and said, “Interesting, let’s head out and take a look.” After he said that, Zhao Hai stood up and left their private room for the second time.

After going down the stairs, Zhao Hai discovered a person on the first floor. His stature was tall and big, making him look strong. However, this person was actually wearing mage robes. He looked 40 years old with his beard and ferocious face. This was the person who was shouting out his name.

Zhao Hai looked at the man and said, “This one is Zhao Hai. Are you the one looking for me?”

The huge Mage looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You’re Zhao Hai? Kind, you’re quite arrogant, aren’t you? Do you even put our Machine Field Army in your eyes?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Mage and said, “The Machine Field Army hasn’t done anything worthy of my notice yet. And who are you? You didn’t even introduce yourself. You don’t have the qualifications to call me out.”

As soon as the Mage heard this, his killing aura couldn’t help but flare up, then he coldly snorted and said, “Kid, listen carefully. I’m Captain Tao Ke of the Machine Field Army’s External Hall’s Spear Camp. Now tell me whether I have the qualifications to call you out.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “So it is Captain Tao. So does being a captain give you the qualifications to call me out? Am I someone from the Machine Field Army? Am I your subordinate? If not, then you don’t have the rights to call my name out loud.”

Tao Ke paled from anger upon hearing Zhao Hai. He thought that bringing up his status would make Zhao Hai afraid. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to actually retort.

Zhao Hao looked at Tao Ke’s expression and said, “Captain Tao, you’re asking me if I placed the Machine Field Army in my eyes? Let me ask you this. Your people ate at this restaurant and then bullied the waitress. Your Machine Field Army is truly magnificent. I didn’t expect you to act like space pirates. Why would you want to bully a waitress? Now ask me again why I don’t place the Machine Field Army in my eyes. Also, Captain Tao, I don’t know if your brothers told you about the background of this restaurant. I really respect your loyalty to each other, but you’re just used as a tool. This isn’t something that a mere captain like you could shoulder.”

Tao Ke looked at Zhao Hai and then coldly snorted and said, “So what? Isn’t this place just a business of the Fire Temple? What’s so great about that? Are you saying that my Machine Field Army should be afraid of the Fire Temple?”

Zhao Hai seem to stare when he heard Tao Ke. Seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Tao Ke laughed and said, “What? You think the Fire Temple is anything in the eyes of the Machine Field Army? Let me tell you, Zhao Hai, we aren’t afraid of the Fire Temple. Even if someone from the Fire Temple is here, I still wouldn’t be afraid of them!”

“Really?” A calm voice was heard. Zhao Hai looked at the source of the sound and saw people wearing red robes walk in from outside. The one who just talked was an old Mage. He looked close to 100-years old, and his hair was fully grey. However, one could see that the old man’s eyes were still as sharp as the eyes of an eagle.

The old Mage arrived in front of Tao Ke. He looked at the Machine Field Army Captain, then he sneered and said, “Little External Hall Captain, what gave you the courage to be so arrogant in my Fire Temple’s territory? Do your words represent the Machine Field Army? Are you the commander-in-chief? And since you aren’t afraid of the Fire Temple, then does that mean that the Fire Temple should be afraid of you?”

Tao Ke stayed in place as he stared at the old Mage. Sweat began trickling down his cheek. This was because he recognized who this old Mage was. This person was a Bishop of the Fire Temple, famously known as Blazing Condor Ma Fenglei. This Bishop wasn’t exactly known as an amicable gentleman. All those who offended him ended up dead. Moreover, he wasn’t afraid of anyone. It was even rumored that he cursed the Machine Field Army’s Commander-in-Chief right to his face. He caused headaches to anyone he encountered. A person like this wasn’t someone a small Captain could offend.

Tao Ke immediately felt his throat dry up. Cold sweat began building up on his back. He didn’t expect that such a trivial matter in a small Fire Temple shop would cause this grandfather to appear. Tao Ke couldn’t help but think about his dark days ahead!

Chapter 1180: Aren’t You Just Looking For A Woman?

After speaking to Tao Ke, Ma Fenglei turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You’re Zhao Hai? Good, very good. Let this old Ma express his gratitude.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Bishop Ma is too polite. Sun Fei and I are friends. And since Sun Fei is from the Fire Temple, it’s natural that I would help him. I hope that Bishop Ma wouldn’t think that I’m budging into your matters.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Ma Fenglei laughed and said, “Kid, you’re quite interesting. Why would I think that? There are some people in the Machine Field who think that the Magic Church Alliance had become weak. They’re like dogs and cats that can’t wait to urinate on our territories. What a joke. Even ants from the Machine Field Army dared to spit on our faces. Hahaha. And he doesn’t even represent the army. Even if those old commanders come here, they would still need my approval to do anything.”

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything as he just smiled. But on the other hand, Tao Ke turned pale white. If other people have said this, then he might not care. However, it was Ma Fenglei, often called Crazy Ma by a lot of people. There was nothing that he wouldn’t dare to do.

Seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t respond, Ma Fenglei turned his eyes back to Tao Ke. He sneered and said, “What? You want to test my patience? Captain Tao Ke, right? I’ll start with you.” Then he waved his hand, causing Tao Ke to be held down by one of the Fire Temple’s men. Tao Ke was pinned to the ground, but he didn’t do anything to resist.

After taking Tao Ke down, Ma Fenglei said, “Find those people who came here earlier. Then send word to the Machine Field Army about what happened. Have them deal with their own men. If they can’t do it, then this Ma Fenglei will discipline them myself!” After Ma Fenglei said this, one of his men immediately complied and left to do the task.

Seeing that the situation has been handled, Ma Fenglei turned to Zhao Hai as he smiled and said, “Zhao Hai, you did well. However, this matter will bring you quite the trouble. How do you plan to deal with it?”

Zhao Hai nonchalantly smiled and said, “How to deal with it? I’ll do the same as Bishop Ma. In the competition, I’ll make sure to erase any person from the Machine Field Army unlucky enough to face me.” Zhao Hai was smiling the entire time he said this line. He didn’t have any hint of killing aura on him at all. His tone was natural and peaceful, it was as though he was talking with some folks while eating some steamed buns.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Fenglei’s pupils shrunk for a moment, then he laughed and said, “Good, good. Hahaha. So Zhao Hai, why don’t you join my Fire Temple? If you do, I’ll make you a Camp Lord.”

Upon hearing Ma Fenglei, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but suck in cold air. There were no ascender Camp Lords in the entire Machine Field. Ma Fenglei’s appreciation for Zhao Hai actually made him invite Zhao Hai to be a Camp Lord. This was a very important matter.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Fenglei, then he smiled faintly and said, “Bishop Ma must be joking. You should be aware of my relationship with Margaret. How could I join the Fire Temple?”

Ma Fenglei looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I see no reason why not. Aren’t you just looking for a woman? As long as you join the Fire Temple, you can have all the women you want.”

Zhao Hai stared at Ma Fenglei, then he laughed and said, “Bishop Ma, you think this Zhao Hai is lacking women? Aren’t you looking down on me too much?”

Hearing Zhao Hai’s  response, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but get nervous. Ma Fenglei’s temperament was very infamous in the Machine Field. Zhao Hai was probably the first person to talk to Ma Fenglei like this in the past several years.

However, their worries were blown away when Ma Fenglei suddenly burst out laughing as he said, “Good, good. I haven’t misjudged you.” Then he turned his hand before throwing something towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai caught the object and saw that it was a small badge.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Fenglei in confusion. Ma Fenglei smiled faintly and said, “It’s a Guest Badge of the Fire Temple. We have a lot of guest experts in the Temple. Since you don’t want to join us, take that instead.”

Upon hearing Ma Fenglei, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then I’ll be impolite and take this. This Zhao Hai thanks Bishop Ma.” Ma Fenglei laughed once more before he waved his hand and left the restaurant.

When Ma Fenglei left, Zhao Hai turned to look at Xiong Li and the others and said, “We haven’t eaten yet but people have already been disturbing us. But it seems like nobody will disturb us now. Let’s eat! We’re not leaving this place until we’re drunk.”

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and then he suddenly laughed and said, “Brother Zhao, I really admire your courage. Did you know that nobody talks to Ma Fenglei like that? Even Machine Field natives wouldn’t dare, much less ascenders.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t say anything. He believed that Ma Fenglei wouldn’t move against him. Moreover, the Fire Temple was currently at its weakest point. If Ma Fenglei decided to attack Zhao Hai, then he’s not worthy of the position of Bishop.

The reason why Ma Fenglei dared to publicly berate the Machine Field Army was because he didn’t only have the Fire Temple at his back, the Church Alliance would also support him.

Because of the recent event, the Divine Earth Palace and the Fire Temple were heavily damaged. It can be said that their vitality had suffered an injury. These two churches were very important pillars of the Church Alliance. Damage to these two would also damage the alliance. Because of this, the Alliance has to be united at this time. Whether it be the Warrior Association or the Machine Field Army, the Alliance would certainly counter-attack if either of these two dared to move against them.

Therefore, Ma Fenglei dared to offend the Machine Field Army at this time. However, Ma Fenglei wouldn’t offend Zhao Hai. This was because Zhao Hai held a very special status in the Ashley Family. Ma Fenglei also received information that the Ashley Family had withdrawn all of their participants save for Zhao Hai. In this case, if Ma Fenglei dared to touch Zhao Hai, then the Ashley Family would certainly retaliate heavily.

Actually, even if the Fire Temple was damaged, it was still not afraid of the Ashley Family. However, the Ashley Family was an important pillar of the Dark Church. If they fought with the Ashley Family, the Dark Church would certainly insert themselves. This was something that the Fire Temple would never want to happen.

Due to these considerations, Zhao Hai determined that Ma Fenglei wouldn’t do anything to him. Moreover, from what Zhao Hai can see, Ma Fenglei wasn’t the sort of person to do that.

The group returned to their private room. When they got settled in, the staff immediately brought in meat and wine. Moreover, it can be seen that the items they brought in were the best quality goods. It was obvious that they were very thankful for what Zhao Hai and the others did.

After the staff left the room, Dongfang Yu looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao, are you really planning to erase the Machine Field Army’s people in the qualifiers?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I am, but I’ll have to look more into the matter. After all, I don’t just represent myself, I’m also carrying the Ashley Family’s name. I don’t want to cause trouble for the family. If the Machine Field Army is really concerned about their pride, then I’ll have no choice but to be impolite.”

Dongfang Yu looked at Zhao Hai then he laughed and said, “Good, good. Hahaha. If they really hold on to their pride, then make sure to inform me. If I meet anyone from the Machine Field Army, I’ll also destroy them.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Why are you two making plans on your own? Count me in!”

“Me too!”, Sun Fei said as he lifted his wine glass. Everyone laughed before they clinked their glasses and downed their wine in one go.

The group ate meat and drank wine until they could no longer consume anything. When they wanted to get the check, the restaurant staff told them that their meal was free of charge.

Zhao Hai wasn’t too polite and expressed his thanks before leaving the restaurant. Just as Zhao Hai got outside, his driver greeted him and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, the General Manager want me to tell you that he has something to talk to you about.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to Xiong Li and the others and said, “Brother Xiong, Brother Dongfang, Brother Sun, I’ll have to leave first. Let’s share more drinks in the future whenever we’re free.”

Xiong Li and the others held their fists to salute Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai returned the gesture before he got into the car. Looking at Zhao Hai’s car quickly speeding out of sight, Xiong Li sighed and said, “Brother Zhao is truly not an average person. I can’t compare to him.”

Dongfang Yu smiled bitterly and said, “Not just you. Even those old foxes wouldn’t compare to Zhao Hai. It’s ridiculous to think that I expected him to be someone who only knows how to cultivate. He certainly wasn’t an ordinary person back in the lower realms.”

Sun Fei nodded, “Brother Hai is strong. However, he wouldn’t kill people easily. But if you become his enemy, then your future won’t be bright. It’s fortunate that I was able to meet you outside the stadium. If I didn’t apologize, then I might suffer in the future.”

When Xiong Li and Dongfang Yu heard Sun Fei, they couldn’t help but laugh. They knew that what Sun Fei said was right. If he didn’t meet them, then he would certainly suffer under Zhao Hai. After all, they were in a hostile relationship before.

But what the three didn’t know was that they were beginning to subconsciously think that they were no match against Zhao Hai. It was only a matter of time before they would truly be defeated.

The three exchanged a few more words before bidding each other farewell. They needed to find a place to digest their experiences today. They also needed to tell their groups about what just transpired so that they could make the right preparations. After all, this incident involved a lot of big groups. And they believed that this incident was the exact reason why the Ashley Family called Zhao Hai back.

Chapter 1181: Suppression Using a Magnificent Cover

After Zhao Hai boarded the car, he immediately took out some spatial water and then drank it. So after the car arrived at its destination, Zhao Hai was refreshed.

Upon getting off the car, Zhao Hai directly went upstairs before he was led to Cadjo’s room by a robot.

When they arrived outside Cadjo’s room, the robot knocked twice and said, “General Manager, Mister Zhao Hai is here.”

Cadjo quickly replied, “Come in.”

Zhao Hai pushed the door and walked in. He saw Cadjo, Desbarres, and Luke inside. Zhao Hai gave the three men a salute. Cadjo waved his hand and said, “Little Hai, I just received a message from Old Ma Fenglei. He expressed his gratitude and said that he made you a guest expert of the Fire Temple. What is going on?”

Zhao Hai smiled and then told everyone about what just happened while in Delin’s Barbecue. Cadjo and the others were intently listening. After Zhao Hai finished talking, Cadjo nodded and said, “So it’s like that. Good, very good. Although you offended the Machine Field Army, you managed to hook the Fire Temple in. We already established a connection with the Wu Family, and now there is the Fire Temple. This is going to be good for us. After all, the Fire Temple has a huge influence in the Church Alliance. With our relationship with the Warrior Association and the Church Alliance, offending the Machine Field Army is nothing.”

Desbarres nodded and said, “I also think that today’s matter isn’t an accident. It’s possible that the Machine Field Army sent those people to probe us. Otherwise, those Mech Soldiers wouldn’t have been that courageous. They should be the first ones to know what would happen if they caused any disturbance in Machine Field Planet.”

Luke nodded as well and added, “Delin’s Barbecue is a very famous establishment in the planet. Almost everyone knew that it belonged to the Fire Temple. However, those mech soldiers actually dared to cause trouble there. This matter isn’t simple. Cadjo, I think we should report this matter to the Patriarch. This way, he would make some preparations.”

Cadjo nodded, “I’ll send word to the Patriarch. At the same time, I’ll get in contact with the Wu Family and the Fire Temple. It’s best if we can contact the other Churches as well, just to make sure.”

Luke nodded and said, “The Machine Field Army has five seeded participants in the competition. Little Hai, they might try to deal with you. You should prepare.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and nodded. Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If the Machine Field Army doesn’t go too hard, let them go. However, if they dared to be excessive, you don’t have to be polite. Just kill them!”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “You can rest assured, General Manager. I know what to do.”

Cadjo nodded, “Alright, you can go take a rest. Although the Machine Field Planet looks very calm, you shouldn’t underestimate the undercurrents happening within. You need to be more careful.” Zhao Hai nodded, before he bowed and left the room.

After Zhao Hai left, Cadjo smiled faintly and said, “Hmm, I didn’t expect the Machine Field army’s action to give the Ashley Family an opportunity. If we can make the Wu Family and the Fire Temple our allies, then it would be very good for the family.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “To be honest, this is due to Little Hai’s luck. If it weren’t for him, then we wouldn’t have been able to establish a connection with the Fire Temple. He actually managed to become a guest expert of the temple. It seems like Old Ma Fenglei really appreciated Zhao Hai.”

Cadjo nodded and said, “I didn’t expect Little Hai to amuse Ma Fenglei. Also, Little Hai actually refused a Camp Lord position. That’s quite a rich offer.”

Desbarres smiled and said, “Old Ma didn’t expect Zhao Hai to care little about money and status. He’s more concerned about sentiment. Little Hai already connected himself with the Bone Symbol Camp. As long as the family doesn’t harm him, I believe he wouldn’t leave.”

Luke sighed and said, “Little Hai is just too strong. I’m afraid the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to keep him. Our Ashley Family is just too small. A character as great as him would leave sooner or later.”

Cadjo replied, “If he leaves, then we can’t do anything about it. As long as the Ashley Family is in his heart, we could still rely on him when we encounter any trouble.”

Desbarres nodded, “Right, I have the same thought.’

….

By this time, Zhao Hai had already returned to his room. As soon as he entered, Zhao Hai immediately went to the Space. Margaret already went ahead of him.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Margaret and the others immediately welcomed him. Especially Margaret, whose face was full of worry. After some time, she said, “Brother Hai, you’re being too risky this time. Ma Fenglei is a difficult person to face. If he decided to deal with you, then it’ll be huge trouble.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I know where things stand. He wouldn’t deal with me. It’s fine.” Laura and the others knew that Zhao Hai said was right. However, they were still nervous upon seeing Zhao Hai talk with Ma Fenglei. This was because the old man’s reputation in the Machine Field was too well known.

Before this, Laura and the others didn’t know about Ma Fenglei. But when Margaret saw Zhao Hai speaking with the Fire Temple Bishop, her expression changed. Then she told Laura and the others about Ma Fenglei, which caused Laura and the others to be nervous as well.

Since the matter has been settled, the group relaxed and then went to the living room. After everyone had sat down, Zhao Hai turned to Margaret and said, “Actually, I was thinking about the Ashley Family during that time. The family needed several allies. I couldn’t stay in the Machine Field all the time, perhaps I might leave after the competition.  Margaret, will you follow me or stay here?”

Margaret shook her head and said, “It’s fine. I don’t have much connection to the family anyway. But this doesn’t mean that I will abandon the family. Brother Hai, if the Ashley Family were to meet any problems, we need to help them. Even if we can’t save everyone, we should still make sure that Camp Lord and the others are safe.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, if anything happens, I will certainly offer my help.”

………………

The day quickly went past. The next day, Zhao Hai decided to stay inside the Space. After all, he didn’t have any fights today, there was no need to go to the stadium.

Moreover, the two days didn’t have anything worth looking at. The level of those competing simply weren’t enough to gain Zhao Hai’s attention.

Zhao Hai thought that after what happened to Yellowsand Planet, the battles further on wouldn’t be too bloody. However, he didn’t expect the fights to be bloodier than before. Those who were eliminated had suffered injuries. There were even some people who were killed on the stage. Some were also cripplied and there was even an instance where both participants mutually wounded themselves.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, then his expression turned difficult. When Margaret looked at Zhao Hai’s expression, she couldn’t help but ask, “Brother Hai? What’s wrong?”

Zhao Hai sighed and then said, “It seems like the people in the Machine Field really don’t regard Ascenders as proper equals. Have you ever thought of how many Ascenders would die after the qualifiers? There are nearly 100 thousand people in the beginning, and there are also those who were crippled. No wonder the Mages and Warriors of the Machine Field couldn’t compete against the Cultivators. You should know that those who are killed in the qualifiers are elites of their respective families. If they were trained well, then they might turn out to be powerful experts. They might even be able to fight against the Cultivators. But now, their lives ended in this competition. In this case, how could Mages and Warriors get powerful? It seems like there are some people in the Machine Field that doesn’t want Ascenders to get powerful.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others stared, then their expressions changed as well. Margaret couldn’t believe it, “Brother Hai, how is that possible?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Why would it be impossible? Think about it, which people have the most power over the Machine Field? Its the battleships and the mechs. If Mages and Warriors get stronger, then their control over the Machine Field would be affected. Do you think those who control the battleships and the mechs would accept having their benefits taken? In this case, it’s impossible for Mages and Warriors to rise up. And there’s also the way the Machine Field natives discriminate against Ascenders. It’s natural for them to suppress Mages and Warriors. However, since they couldn’t blatantly reveal the suppression, they needed to find a way to hide it. So isn’t this competition a perfect way to hide it? This competition gathered every single talented ascender in the realm. Even if some geniuses were left in the end, the other realms would take care of them. In the Six Realm Beginner Competition, not only would Mages and Warriors get injured, only very few of them manage to survive. With so few numbers left, there would be no way for them to influence the Machine Field.”

Laura and the others couldn’t help but unconsciously nod. They thought that what Zhao Hai said was reasonable. If what Zhao Hai said was true, then it would be too scary. This was basically the Machine Field getting rid of their capable subordinates.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and then said, “Meanwhile, the Cultivation Realm has a different idea. Since Great Sects absorb ascenders, as long as one of them becomes powerful, the sect would gain a powerful expert. Because the Cultivation Realm talk using strength, they couldn’t suppress ascenders. For them Ascenders are another source for powerful experts. They wouldn’t threaten the benefits of ascenders. Conversely, they would cultivate ascenders so that they could provide more benefits to their sect. This allowed the Cultivation Realm to progress quickly. But in the Machine Field, Mages and Warriors were kept powerless. The potential of Magic Theory is truly wasted.”

Chapter 1182: Circulating Rumor

Laura and the others were earnestly listening. Zhao Hai looked at them and then said, “At this time, you should already have some understanding about Magic Theory. Magic Theory is very formidable and special. Once you reach a very high level, 10 thousand layer formations could allow you to fight battleships. If you continue to get stronger, then there’s no reason for you to be any weaker than Cultivators. At high levels, Magic Theory might even win. As for mid and early stages, it’s possible to compete at an equal standing. But as you can see, Mages and Warriors are being suppressed. They have no way to fight back at all. Isn’t this wrong?”

Bang! Margaret pounded on the table. Then with clenched teeth, she said, “Shameless, those shameless people!”

Zhao Hai stared at Margaret, he didn’t expect here reaction to be this big. Zhao Hai looked at Margaret in confusion and then said, “Margaret, why are you so agitated? You’re a Machine Field native?”

Margaret breathed in twice to calm down, then she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, my mother is also an Ascender. Moreover, I have worked in the Ascender Academy for many years. I saw the hope in the eyes of each Ascender as they venture out to the Machine Field. For them to suffer such a fate is very hateful. Those behind this matter are bastards.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, we can’t do anything about it for now. If we get an opportunity later, I’ll try to fix this matter. But now, I’m completely helpless.”

Margaret smiled and said, “I don’t expect you to do anything now. I’m just angry. The Machine Field has been suppressed by the Cultivation Realm for many years because our low-middle level experts couldn’t compare to the Cultivators. But as it turns out, the Machine Field has been suppressing itself.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Alright, thinking about this right now is just useless. Instead, let’s prepare. The Six Realm Beginner Competition would give us the opportunity to come in contact with the other five realms.”

Margaret nodded. At this time, Laura said, “Brother Hai, do you think we would be recognized by Lu Wei because of this?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “So what if we get recognized? I’m no longer afraid of him. Lu Wei and the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor are no longer threats. What we need to worry  about is the Myriad Treasure Pavillion. Compared to the two, the Pavillion is more dangerous. It’s fortunate that the pavillion doesn’t know what we look like. Until they find us, nothing should happen to us.”

Laura and the others nodded. They agreed to Zhao Hai’s words. At this point, Lu Wei and the Yin Wind Ghost Emperor are no longer Zhao Hai’s enemies. What Zhao Hai needed to worry about right now was the Myriad Treasures Pavillion.

Time passed by and soon the qualifiers were about to reach its final rounds. At this point, the original 100 thousand participants had been whittled down to 1 thousand.

And this was also the time where the 20 seeded participants would enter the competition. 19 of these participants had no issues to them whatsoever, the only exception was Zhao Hai.

There were people who suspected Zhao Hai’s strength. The core of this rumor was the fact that nobody saw Zhao Hai make a move. Although Xiong Li and Sun Fei were giving Zhao Hai’s praises, the matter with Zhao Hai, Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, and Sun Fei drinking together nullified their recommendations. Because of this, people began to think that Xiong Li and Sun Fei were recommending Zhao Hai just because they were friends.

During the time when Xiong Li said his nomination, the voice of this rumor was very small. But this time, for some apparent reason, the voices were getting louder.

Naturally, Zhao Hai knew that the Machine Field Army was behind this. Even if it was Ma Fenglei who slapped their faces, the army couldn’t do anything about his due to the Fire Temple. However, they could move against Zhao Hai. In the eyes of the Machine Field Army, Zhao Hai was nothing more than an Ascender of the Ashley Family. Even if it were the Ashley Family’s core members, the Army would still dare to kill them. Therefore, what could the Ashley Family do?

These questions about Zhao Hai’s abilities were just the beginning. It seems like the Machine Field Army was not yet ready to give up. Upon thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sneer, he thought, ‘Alright, Machine Field Army, let’s play.’

The battles between these top 1000 were still decided by electronic drawing of lots. The Machine Field prepared ten arenas for this event so that ten battles could happen at the same time. The Six Realm Beginner Competition is fast approaching, there’s no need to waste time.

Of the first 20 people drawn, Zhao Hai and Xiong Li weren’t among them. On the other hand, Dongfang Yu and Sun Fei went on to fight their matches. Zhao Hai and Xiong Li didn’t bother looking at the fights, their opponents weren’t strong, there was nothing to see.

Zhao Hai sat beside Xiong Li in their assigned seats. All those around them were looking in their direction, most of the looks were heading towards Zhao Hai. And these gazes were filled with suspicion.

Upon seeing these people, Xiong Li said, “These bastards. They actually suspect your strength. Little Hai, when your time comes, don’t hold back. Kill your enemy in one shot.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, I’ve already prepared a list. As long as I run into those in my list, I wouldn’t let them off.”

Xiong Li asked, “List? What list?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’ll know when the time comes. Right, Brother Dongfang fights quickly. He should be back soon.” When Zhao Hai told Xiong Li this, Dongfang appeared.

When Zhao Hai saw Dongfang Yu, he shouted, “Brother Dongfang, aren’t you too quick? Did you surrender?”

Dongfang Yu sneered and said, “Get lost. When will your dog mouth spout good words? When my enemy saw that he was against me, he immediately surrendered.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright. Come take a seat. Since you won, today’s your treat.”

Dongfang Yu laughed and said, “Only you is this cheap to take advantage of this. Alright, let’s wait for Little Fei to return. Oh, he’s back. Little Fei, you’re quite fast.”

Sun Fei smiled and said, “I’m just lucky to meet a level 3. That fellow is very lucky. He actually reached the top 1000 while being level 3.”

As he said this, an announcement was heard, “Xiong Li, prepare for the next battle in Arena 5.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Xiong Li and said, “Brother Xiong, it’s your turn.” Xiong Li laughed as he stood up and left. Seeing Xiong Li leaving, Donfang Yu turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, how long do you think Big Brother Xiong would take?”

Zhao Hai and the others already knew about each other’s ages. Xiong Li was the oldest, followed by Dongfang Yu, then Zhao Hai, then Sun Fei. This is the reason why Dongfang Yu called Xiong Li ‘Big Brother’.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, Big Brother Xiong wouldn’t take long. Brother Xiong is fierce when he goes to battle. As long as he is in battle, there’s no need to worry about him. It’s his enemy who needs to be afraid of being destroyed.”

Sun Fei nodded, “Right, there’s no need to worry about him. On the other hand, we need to talk about Brother Hai. There are many bad rumors circulating around nowadays. I’m afraid people would try to deal with you. Be careful.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m actually hoping that people would disturb me. It just so happens that my Undead Army needed powerful experts. I’ll just use them to add to these numbers.”

Sun Fei smiled faintly and said, “Right, how strong is your Undead Army? I’d like to see them one day.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Forget it, you don’t want to see them. Those who see my Undead army would become one of my Undead. Do you still want to see?”

Sun Fei smiled bitterly and then shook his head as he said, “Alright, just forget it. I haven’t lived long enough. Big Brother Xiong is back, it seems like his opponent surrendered as well.”

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “Right, if he fought somebody, he would look very happy. But look at him now, he looks dejected. He definitely haven’t fought someone.”

Dongfang Yu laughed and said, “Big Brother Xiong, why the long face? Did you lose?”

Xiong Li stared, then he said, “Get lost. When did this grandfather lose? The coward surrendered the moment I began to power up. It was boring. I thought I could have a good exercise. But in the end, I wasted time.”

As soon as they heard Xiong Li, Zhao Hai and the others laughed. At this time, another announcement was heard, “Zhao Hai, prepare to fight in Arena 3.”

Zhao Hai stretched his body and then said, “Finally, it’s my turn. Let’s see who I’m up against. If it’s from the Machine Field Army, then that fellow is truly unfortunate.” Then Zhao Hai stood up and then left.

Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Xiong Li looked at Dong Fangyu and said, “Dongfang, what were  you talking about with Little Hai just now? Did the Machine Field Army offend him?”

Dongfang Yu’s eyes flashed lightly and said, “Big Brother Xiong, don’t you think that the recent rumors about Little Hai appeared too sudden? Back when you said your nomination, not a lot of people doubted Little Hai’s strength. But now of all times, these rumors became louder and louder. Isn’t it strange?”

When Xiong Li and Sun Fei heard this, they stared for a moment before they understood. Then they turned to Dongfang Yu and said, “Are you talking about the Machine Field Army?”

Dongfang Yu nodded, “Right, the Machine Field Army. Little Hai offended the Machine Field Army before. I heard that even if Ma Fenglei was the one who slapped the army’s face, the Army couldn’t do anything to him. Because of this, they could only deal with Little Hai. I reckon they are the one who spread these rumors. Moreover, this could only be their first step. They should have something else planned.”

Xiong Li’s expression changed. Then he said, “Then isn’t this a problem? What do we do if they deal with Zhao Hai?”

Dongfang Yu shook his head and said, “Relax, if they want to take action, they wouldn’t be able to do it outside. Otherwise, the Machine Field would turn into chaos. They can only deal with Little Hai in the arena. However, those idiots in the Machine Field army underestimated Little Hai’s strength. Wanting to kill him on the area? Hahaha. Even if they sent in Streep, they still wouldn’t be able to do it.”

Xiong Li’s expression loosened up, but he still coldly snorted and said, “If the Machine Field Army decided to do this, then as long as I meet anyone from the army, I will kill them immediately.”

Dongfang Yu smiled faintly and said, “I’m afraid they wouldn’t give us that opportunity. Except the five seeded participants from the army, all other participants would just surrender immediately.”

Xiong Li’s face turned ugly, then he sneered and said, “But we would still meet sooner or later. As long as the Six Realm Beginner Competition ends, I can just go after them.”

Dongfang Yu smiled bitterly and said, “Let’s think about how to survive the Six Realm Beginner Competition first. This time, the other realms also had genius-level characters. We have no advantage over them at all. In this case, it would be difficult even for us to survive.”

Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “Hmph. At worst, I can just go all out and kill as many people as possible before I die.”

At this time, somebody shouted, “Zhao Hai is fighting someone. Everyone, let’s go take a look.” Then after that, a surge of people began going towards Zhao Hai’s arena.

Upon seeing this, Xiong Li couldn’t help but stare. Then the three of them shook their heads as they bitterly smiled. Xiong Li muttered, “Which idiot believes such rumors? If it’s possible, let’s figure out which people spread it. Alright, let’s take a look at Little Hai’s opponent. If it’s from the Machine Field Army, then Dongfang might be able to save himself from treating everyone to a meal.”

Dongfang Yu laughed and said, “Alright, although I really don’t care about saving money, I’d like to be treated by Little Hai.” Then the three laughed before walking towards Arena 3.

Upon arriving at Arena 3, the three stared. This was because there was a sea of people present. Compared to their own matches, Zhao Hai’s had much more attention.

The three looked at the stage and saw two people on it. One of them was Zhao Hai while the other was a Warrior. The Warrior was very tall at about two meters high. His skin was completely covered with iron. He also had a bald head. His weapon was quite special as well. On one hand, he has a huge tower shield while the other hand held a thick broadsword!

Upon seeing this, Xiong Li couldn’t help but gawk. Then he forced a smile as he said, “Damn, it’s really someone from the Machine Field Army. Isn’t that the famous Iron Tower? He’s very famous for being hard to deal with. He almost got into the 20 seeded participants. But because of mine and Sun Fei’s recommendation, the spot went to Little Hai. I didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s first opponent to be him. Isn’t this too suspicious?”

Dongfang Yu frowned and said, “Suspicious, it is very suspicious. Is it possible that this is arranged by the Machine Field Army? Who would have thought that Zhao Hai’s first opponent to be someone who is qualified to be on the top 20?”

Chapter 1183: Am I Unqualified?

When Xiong Li and Sun Fei heard Dongfang Yu say this, Xiong Li said, “Dongfang, what are you saying? Are you saying that the random lot is being manipulated?”

Dongfang Yu coldly snorted and said, “Those fellows from the Machine Field Army are getting more and more arrogant. It wouldn’t be impossible for them to manipulate the random lot. If we let the Machine Field army go on like this, we would only suffer. If those Machine Field Army bastards let us go against Zhao Hai, what do we do?”

Xiong Li and Sun Fei stared for a moment upon hearing Dongfang Yu. Then their expressions changed. They knew that the consequences of this matter is very serious. If they were to meet Zhao Hai, then their future opportunities would certainly be stopped.

Xiong Li immediately said, “Let’s go now.”

Dongfang Yu stopped him and said, “There’s no need to be anxious. In any case, a fight will happen today. We should wait until tomorrow. After Little Hai’s fight, we should go together and do something about it.” Xiong Li nodded, then he turned his head to the arena.

Zhao Hai was standing there and facing his enemy. He knew about Iron Tower of the Machine Field Army’s External Hall. This man was known for his height as well as the giant tower shield that he held. His cultivation method was also very special. In three words, his cultivation method was, work hard, work hard, work hard. It was a type of cultivation method that refined the body. This body refining method was very formidable. If it was practiced to a very deep state, one’s body would become very resilient. Most swords and spears wouldn’t be able to pierce through the skin.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also knew that Iron Tower had the opportunity to be a seeded participant. It’s just a pity that he went up against Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at his opponent, then he smiled and said, “Interesting, I actually met you in my first fight. Hahaha. The Machine Field Army’s plans are very good.”

Iron Tower coldly snorted and said, “You can still afford to smile? Today, I’ll let you know who is more qualified to be a seeded participant.”

Zhao Hai looked at Iron Tower and then he smiled and said, “Being a seeded participant isn’t necessarily nice. Alright, it’s useless to talk anymore. Let’s just prove it!”

Iron Tower coldly snorted and said, “I have the same idea!” Then after he said that, he slammed his tower shield in front of him and then roared towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai just smiled and then waved his hand, casting a 5-layer magic formation. Iron Tower quickly braced his tower shield in order to block Zhao Hai’s spell. However, the formation suddenly exploded, surrounding the arena with black mist. This caused the spectators to be clueless about what was happening in the arena.

But Iron Tower quickly found something strange. Although they were surrounded by dark smoke, the arena was free of any obstruction. He could still see properly inside. The dark mist looked like a shield that covered the arena.

Iron Tower didn’t know what Zhao Hai’s plan was. He looked at Zhao Hai warily. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You think I’m unqualified to be a seeded participant. I’ll let you see why I was chosen instead of you.” Then Zhao Hai made a move. He took out his own tower shield and on his other hand was a giant hammer.

Iron Tower couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai. Seeing his opponent’s reaction, Zhao Hai smiled, “Come, let me see if you have any skill.”

Iron Tower regained his clarity. He stared at Zhao Hai before breathing in cold air, then he said, “You’re also a Warrior?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Correct. I’m both a Mage and a Warrior. Hahaha. Here I go.” Then his figure moved as he charged towards Iron Tower.

Iron Tower immediately recovered. He roared as he prepared to defend against Zhao Hai. He settled his tower shield to his shoulder as he braced for impact.

Boom! A loud sound was heard as the two parties collided with each other. Because of their collision, the entire arena fiercely shook.

In this collision, both Zhao Hai and Iron Tower were subjected to a massive seismic force. However, when this force entered Zhao Hai’s body, it merely rippled out before it vanished completely. The bluesteel by his feet was just cracked and he wasn’t blown away.

On the other hand, Iron Tower suffered a different fate. He was shaken by the force and had to retreat a few steps. Every step he made caused an indentation to appear on the bluesteel arena.

Iron Tower was only able to stabilize himself after retreating eight steps back. Just as Iron Tower regained his position, Zhao Hai rushed over with his tower shield, looking much like a giant charging elephant.

Iron Tower saw this and knew that if he were to get hit, he would be finished. He roared and then held his shield up high before slamming it firmly straight into the ground.

Iron Tower’s shield was specially-made. Below the shield was a sharp point. With Iron Tower’s immense strength, a third of the shield easily sunk into the bluesteel floor. Iron Tower wanted to stop Zhao Hai’s charge using this method.

However, Iron Tower underestimated Zhao Hai’s strength. During their first collision, Zhao Hai didn’t even use his full force, only about a fourth of his strength.

It can be said that Zhao Hai’s present strength was terrifying. In the past, Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t this huge. However, after absorbing astral qi, Zhao Hai’s strength skyrocketed. Don’t forget, Zhao Hai uses the stellar body tempering technique. No matter what he does, his body would certainly get stronger as time goes by.

Zhao Hai saw Iron Tower’s move, but he didn’t care. This time, he was charging over with 80% of his strength. After a bang, Iron Tower’s body flew. Meanwhile, his tower shield was broken. It was clear that Zhao Hai had put much more power in this charge.

Since Iron Tower’s body was in the air, there was no way for him to stabilize his body. Zhao Hai took a few steps forward before jumping. Then he waved his hammer and smashed it straight down towards Iron Tower.

Clang! Iron Tower was like an iron ball dropped from a plane. He fell to the arena, his broadsword had already been bent by Zhao Hai.

Bang! Iron Tower’s huge figure fell into the arena. At the same time, blood spurted out of his mouth. Although it can be said that Iron Tower was truly strong, he was still human in the end. This fall, along with Zhao Hai’s powerful strength, shook Iron Tower’s internal organs violently.

At this time, Zhao Hai fell back to the ground and then he immediately rushed towards Iron Tower. Iron Tower knew that Zhao Hai was about to kill him, but he didn’t shout his surrender. He knew clearly that shouting at this point was useless.

Zhao Hai being both a Mage and a Warrior, this was information that the Machine Field Army’s intelligence division failed to collect. Naturally, this was because Zhao Hai had been keeping it a secret all this time. Now that he knew about Zhao Hai’s secret, Zhao Hai would certainly make sure to get rid of him. It was already certain that he would die today.

Nobody wanted to die, the same was true for Iron Tower. He rolled on the ground before doing his best to stand. However, since he stood too quickly, he couldn’t help but spurt out blood.

Zhao Hai looked at Iron Tower, then he smiled faintly and said, “Iron Tower, now do you still think that I don’t have the qualifications to be seeded?”

Iron Tower coldly snorted but he didn’t say anything. When he saw that Zhao Hai was a Mage and a Warrior, he knew that he could no longer win. Not only was Zhao Hai qualified to be seeded, it was even possible for him to be the strongest participant in this qualifier.

Zhao Hai looked at Iron Tower, then he smiled faintly and said, “I decided that if the Machine Field Army really wants to deal with me, then I would kill every participant they have in this competition. So die!” Then he moved as fast as a cheetah. But this time, he didn’t have a shield and hammer in his hand. Instead, Zhao Hai took out a large glaive!

Iron Tower’s eyes shrunk, he didn’t notice when Zhao Hai traded his weapon. Moreover, he had no idea what Zhao Hai’s weapon was. But he knew that Zhao Hai’s weapons weren’t normal. And from the looks of this weapon, its purpose seems to be cleaving people in two!

With this thought in mind, Iron Tower quickly lifted his tower shield. Although the tower shield only had two-thirds of its body left, it was still a huge piece of steel. Iron Tower had just managed to recover, so holding up the shield wasn’t a problem.

Just as Iron Tower lifted his shield, Zhao Hai’s glaive arrived. After a ‘ka’ sound, Zhao Hai stepped on the arena again, his glaive in his hand. On the other hand, Iron Tower stood in place with his tower shield in his hand. After some time, the tall shield fell to the ground, Iron Tower’s hand fell along with it. Then shortly after that, Iron Tower’s body seemed to lean on one side before it began falling on the ground.

At this time, a red line appeared across Iron Tower’s body. The wound went from his left shoulder to his right waist. Zhao Hai’s glaive actually split him in half.

Zhao Hai looked at Iron Tower then he stomped his feet. The broken half of the tower shield that was embedded into the arena flew over. At the same time, Zhao Hai waved his hand as Iron Tower’s other part of the shield as well as broadsword flew over. Then after turning Iron Tower into an Undead, Zhao Hai repaired the tower shield as well as the broadsword.

After taking care of these, Zhao Hai withdrew the dark mist surrounding the arena. When the mist dissipated, Zhao Hai saw an indignant crowd. However, he didn’t care as he turned his head towards the referee.

The referee was blankly staring at Zhao Hai. At the same time, he also swept his gaze towards the arena. It’s obvious that he was looking for Iron Tower.

When Zhao Hai saw that the referee didn’t announce anything, he said, “Referee, could you announce the result?”

The referee stared, then he said, “Zhao Hai, where’s your opponent? Why is he not here? Without him here, I cannot announce anything.”

Zhao Hai just met the referee’s response with a smile. This caused the referee to feel uncomfortable. He received a bribe from the Machine Field Army to help Iron Tower. But since the arena was covered, he couldn’t do anything. Therefore, he could only give Zhao Hai a hard time now.

Chapter 1184: New Rule

Zhao Hai looked at the referee and knew that the man was planning to make things hard for him. This was because there were a lot of instances in this competition where the outcome of the fight was unnatural. Therefore, referees were in place to dispute and decide the winner and loser of the match.

If this was other people, then the people on the stands would have berated the referee. But since it was Zhao Hai, nobody spoke. They also wanted to know where Iron Tower went.

Zhao Hai looked at the referee, then he smiled faintly and said, “He vanished, is that an issue? Since he’s gone while I stayed, should I be the winner? Why is the referee delaying the result?”

The referee couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai’s question. According to the rules of the competition, the winner of the competition was decided by who remained standing in the arena. Even if Iron Tower wasn’t killed by Zhao Hai, he wasn’t on the arena, so he lost.

The referee was somewhat angry. He looked at Zhao Hai and coldly snorted as he said, “I’m the referee, and this is my requirement.”

Zhao Hai looked at the referee, then he suddenly laughed and said, “Alright, you are the referee. But don’t forget, you’re under the control of the committee. Do you remember what happened to the past members of the committee? Do you understand what I’m saying?”

When the referee heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare. Then his expression changed. He really wanted to make things hard for Zhao Hai, but after hearing Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but hesitate. Just like Zhao Hai said, referees still answer to the committee. When the last committee members tried to suppress the participants, they were removed. The referee even heard that all of those members had already died, killed by the vengeful small families.

As for the referee, he was just a small element in the competition. If he dared to cause trouble this time, he would definitely be killed. Upon thinking about this, the referee shivered inside. At this moment, he wanted to punch himself for accepting the bribe from the Machine Field Army.

The referee was truly in a hard place. One must know that among all of the arenas, Zhao Hai’s arena had the most attention right now. Because of the recent rumors circulating around, everyone’s curiosity was directed at Zhao Hai. All of them wanted to see how strong Zhao Hai really is.

It was because of this that the referee was afraid to make a decision. If he makes it hard for Zhao Hai, then he would be removed as the referee.

At this time, someone from the crowd suddenly shouted, “Zhao Hai, stop talking nonsense. What did you do to deceive Iron Tower? You’re unqualified to be seeded. You took Iron Tower’s spot!”

As soon as this person’s voice was heard, more and more complaints came in. All of these voices hinted that Zhao Hai was very suspicious. Zhao Hai looked at the direction of the voices and knew from Laura and the others that these people had connections to the Machine Field Army. Their complaints cause everyone around them to get agitated. This caused a disturbance in the area.

Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised at all. He looked at everyone and said, “Does everyone really want to see Iron Tower?”

The stands bursted with conversation. Zhao Hai didn’t care, he just smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll let you see Iron Tower.”

Everyone looked at Zhao Hai. They were wondering about what he would do. Will he take out a handful of ash, pick up a stone, or get a lump of charcoal?

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their reaction. He just smiled before waving his hand. A man appeared next to him. This man had green skin. He held a giant tower shield on one hand and then a broadsword on the other. He stood beside Zhao Hai for everyone to see.

All the spectators stared. They didn’t expect Iron Tower to really appear. Moreover, he seems to be intact.

The referee still didn’t know what to do up to this point. So when he saw Iron Tower, he immediately asked, “Iron Tower, where were you? Did you admit defeat?”

Iron Tower didn’t make any noise, he just stayed in place. Zhao Hai suddenly laughed, causing those under the arena to wonder.

Zhao Hai looked at the referee and said, “Mister Referee, you really need to practice your eyesight. At your current level, you shouldn’t be a referee. If a misjudgement happens, things would get serious.”

When the referee heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he inspected Iron Tower once again. And this time, he discovered an issue, Iron Tower wasn’t breathing.

Even if the referee was an idiot, he would still know what was going on. At the same time, he was shocked by what Zhao Hai did. He actually killed Iron Tower and made him into an Undead.

Zhao Hai looked at the referee. Then he smiled faintly and said, “Mister Referee, can you announce the result now?”

When the referee saw Zhao Hai smile, he felt his heart turn cold. He just found out how ruthless Zhao Hai was. It would be unwise to go against such a person. It wouldn’t be good if he doesn’t declare Zhao Hai a winner. Therefore, he immediately announced, “Zhao Hai is the victor!”

Zhao Hai smiled, then he got down from the arena. Although the arena had stairs designed into it, none of the participants used it. They would show their magic and just jump down or fly away from the arena. It was rare for people to walk down the stairs like Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai calmly walked down the stairs step by step. Moreover, he didn’t store Iron Tower and just had him follow behind.

As for the people from the Machine Field Army, they were far away from the arena so they weren’t able to see Iron Tower’s appearance. Because of this, one of them shouted, “Why did you announce the winner? Iron Tower is still on the stage!”

The referee wasn’t a fool. He knew who were making the disturbance just now. However, he knew that he couldn’t offend Zhao Hai. Moreover, those sent by the Machine Field Army were idiots. Creating a disturbance at this time wasn’t useful.

The referee gazed coldly at the person on the crowd and said, “Are you blind? Can’t you see that Iron Tower has been turned into Undead? And who are you to judge my decision? Are you the referee?”

As soon as these people heard the referee, they couldn’t help but pause. Then they turned their gazes towards Zhao Hai and then to Iron Tower behind him. It didn’t take long for them to discover that the huge armored man was not breathing.

The area turned silent immediately. Everyone was staring at Iron Tower and Zhao Hai. Even those who were somewhat familiar with Zhao Hai couldn’t help but retreat upon seeing this sight.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone’s reaction and suddenly laughed, then he continued to walk forward. Everyone stared at Zhao Hai’s back and then looked at each other in horror, especially those from the Machine Field Army. They saw that Zhao Hai’s eyes stayed the same, which made everyone even more shocked. Each one of them felt shivers running down their spines.

Zhao Hai quickly met with Xiong Li and the others. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li patted his shoulder as he laughed and said, “Little Hai, good job. Beautiful. Let’s leave this place and have a drink.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, let’s go have a drink.” The group laughed before they headed out of the stadium. Everyone’s gazes were on them, but they seem to not care at all.

Zhao Hai only put Iron Tower away when they were about to ride the car. Then the group proceeded towards the restaurant. This time, they didn’t go to Delin’s Barbecue, instead they visited a different place. After everyone had placed their orders and had settled down, Sun Fei turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, Second Brother Dongfang said that your match may have been tampered with. He wants us to act on it so that the Machine Field Army wouldn’t pit us against each other. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It definitely is the case. But it’s not good to complain against the Machine Field Army right now. We have Iron Tower as a witness. He should be able to know what is going on. When the time comes, he will be a witness against the army. We have to follow the proper procedures. Let’s have our families formally protest against the competition. I want to see how these things end.”

Xiong Li’s expression turned ugly, “Hmph. The Machine Field Army should hope that I don’t meet their people. I’ll definitely kill them all.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright. These are struggles of the higher-ups. It’s something we cannot control. Let’s drink! We still have battles tomorrow.” At this time, their dishes and liquor were delivered.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Ashley Family’s building, Cadjo and the others immediately made an official protest. However, Cadjo didn’t target the suspicious drawing of lots. Instead, he complained about Zhao Hai having an unfair referee. This should be enough to keep the Machine Field Army in line.

Also, the Ashley Family weren’t the only ones to issue a protest. The Wu Family, Fire Temple, and Dongfang Yu’s Yan Family also lodged a protest. But instead of the referee, their families targeted the suspicious drawing of competitors. The protest of these families turned into a very serious matter. It provoked a chain reaction, causing every influence to turn their heads to this matter. Another investigation began.

The Machine Field Army suddenly found themselves playing a dizzy game of chess. The current Machine Field was in a very sensitive state. And during this time, they actually dared to do so many things. They were truly asking for trouble. They immediately made countermeasures but the effect wasn’t great. In the end, the investigation found some clues and these clues were pointed directly at the Machine Field Army.

However, the huge powers knew that this matter couldn’t be made public. If the small powers were to catch wind of it, then the Machine Field would be plunged into chaos once more.

The entire matter caused the Machine Field Army to pay a heavy price. In the end, the matter was successfully suppressed. This also made the Machine Field Army hate the Zhao Hai even more.

After this matter, the committee announces a new rule. To better ensure the fighting prowess of the Machine Field in the upcoming Six Realm Beginner Competition, the seeded participants would no longer be chosen to fight against each other. This rule would also extend to the top 100 talents in the Machine Field.

This new rule caused waves in the realm. But after being pressed by the three major powers, everything calmed down. At the same time, Zhao Hai and the others felt relieved.

Chapter 1185: Provocation

Iron Tower died without much attention. And besides a few unlucky referees, almost nothing happened.

The Machine Field just passed through a huge chaotic event. They wouldn’t want to enter another one at this time. Whether it be the Machine Field Army, Church Alliance, or the Warrior Association, nobody wanted to see the Machine Field turn chaotic. Because of this, everyone took a step back. The Machine Field Army was hit with light sanctions while the Church Alliance and Warrior Association stopped making noise.

But in this small event, the Machine Field Army managed to lose the most. While they were able to keep their five seeded participants, they didn’t manage to gain anything. On the other hand, they lost a lot due to the penalties. This caused them to hate Zhao Hai even more. After all, he was the reason why their two plans failed.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this. The Machine Field Army would no longer dare to make a move on him now. If the Machine FIeld Army decided to make another move, then the Church Alliance and the Warrior Association would no longer let them off.

If it was a one-on-one fight against either the Church Alliance or the Warrior Association, then the Machine Field Army would have no reason to be afraid. However, if the two groups were to work together, then the army would have a hard time. Therefore, they wouldn’t dare to make a move at this time.

Zhao Hai was well aware of these matters. The entire Machine Field had already been mapped by the Space. He can see whatever he wanted to see and there were no equipment nor magic that can stop him. Because of this, he was able to know the decision made by the various powers.

Zhao Hai wasn’t disappointed with the verdict. This was within his expectations. If the Machine Field didn’t do it this way, then that would be very suspicious. After all, these people weren’t idiots. They were still on guard against the Cultivation Realm. The Cultivation Realm had no comments about the Yin Yang Sect’s actions. So if the Machine Field Army suddenly turned chaotic, the Cultivation Realm’s Cultivators would certainly make a move. In this case, all three major powers would suffer the same bad luck. Therefore, they had to find a peaceful way to solve this matter.

But in the end, none of these matters affected Zhao Hai. If he met people from the Machine Field Army, he would still kill them.

Since the Army already hated him, there was no need to curry favor with them. It was better to be ruthless to them since they were already on bad terms. But there was one thing that made Zhao Hai disappointed. He could no longer meet the people from the Machine Field Army who were among the seeded ones as well as those in the top 100.

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind after thinking about it. If he could still meet those from the top 100, then this meant that he might be setup to meet Donfang Yu or Xiong Li. It would be troublesome when that time comes.

Another three days of competition passed by and the final 100 have already been chosen. And as expected, the 20 seeded participants were among these 100 people. And at this point, nobody dared doubt Zhao Hai’s strength.

After the top 100 were selected, the following event would be the ranking tournament. In this ranking competition, no casualties were allowed. If one kills or severely injures someone, then that person would be removed from the top 100. They would then be replaced by those who were close to being in the top 100.

This rule was kept in place in order to protect the top 100 strongest people. This would ensure that the Machine Field would be in its best combat state during the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Zhao Hai had no objection to this new rule. After all, he was now considered to be a participant of the Machine Field. Moreover, it can be said that the top 100 were the most powerful beginners in the Machine Field in the past five years. Each injury to these 100 people was an injury to the Machine Field’s benefits.

But even if Zhao Hai didn’t object to this rule, this doesn’t mean that he appreciates it. In fact, Zhao Hai despised the rule. This rule was mainly enforced so that the ascenders would work harder for the Machine Field. If they were truly afraid of loss, then they wouldn’t have made such brutal elimination rounds.

Compared to these 100, the 100 thousand participants should also be paid attention to. Relative to the strength of the Cultivation Realm, the power of these 100 participants was simply meaningless. On the other hand, if those 100 thousand people were trained well, then they might provide ample strength to the Machine Field.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t voice these thoughts for now. Because even if he did, people wouldn’t listen. On the contrary, it would just attract the attention of everyone in the Machine Field. With the Machine Field Army being the main combat arm of the realm, the benefits involved was too great. This cannot be changed in a short time.

While the undercurrents was till surging, the 100 ranking competition finally started. This was one of the liveliest days in the stadium. This was because these 100 people represented the strongest beginners in the past 5 years. And this ranking competition would decide on who the strongest one of them was.

People seem to be born with a hint of competitive spirit. This was more evident in this ranking competition, which ignited the enthusiasm within everyone. This caused the ranking tournament to be the liveliest part of the realm qualifier.

Most importantly, the top 100 ranking tournament would be broadcasted to the realm. This was because there wouldn’t be a lot of bloody accidents that would happen. This would allow the majority of people to be able to watch it.

Not far from the arena, the 100 strongest participants were assigned their own special seats. Xiong Li, Zhao Hai, and the others were sitting together. Xiong Li turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you excited to face Streep and the others?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Not really. What I want to fight are those from the other realms. Fighting Streep and the others is simply useless.”

Xiong Li glared at Zhao Hai and said, “Get out. Are you saying that you aren’t taking us seriously? But since you’re powerful, then you might as well help us when we face the other realms.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, then he turned to look at Dongfang Yu. Seeing Zhao Hai, Dongfang Yu smiled and said, “The Six Realm Beginner Competition starts just like the realm qualifiers. It would also start with an elimination round. But this time, the scale is much smaller. After all, each realm could only have 100 participants each. Generally, they would find a place and then give each person a number plate. Then the participants would snatch each other’s number plates. These number plates would decide the seeded participants of the competition. Those who reached the top ten would be seeded while the others would become ordinary participants. Seeded participants would be exempted from the first and second round of the competition, they would enter in the third. The first two rounds would be the elimination battles while the third round is the battle for points. And the one with the most points wins the first place.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “And those placed beyond 100 would also be ranked?”

Donfang Yu nodded and said, “Right. Everyone from the first to the 600th will be ranked. From 600-500th position, they would obtain some consolation prizes like weapons as well as pieces of precious ores, herbal medicines, and so on. 500-400th position would obtain ten of these items, 400-300 will get 50 precious items, 300-200 will get the rights to some mines. The prize gets more valuable as the rank gets higher. Naturally, the most valuable prizes belonged to those ranked 100 and higher. These rewards include mineral rich planets, and things of equal or greater value. However, it must be said that the most money one could make in the Six Realm Beginner Competition wasn’t in these prizes. Instead, it was from betting!”

Zhao Hai gawked and asked, “Betting?”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “Yes. There’s a huge gambling scene whenever the Six Realm Beginner Competition draws near. Some of these gambling centers offer their services to individual bets. They would bet on players and see how long they could last. Naturally, the odds for each participant is different. There’s also gambling for major powers. A group from the Machine Field, say the Ashley Family, could send a representative to bet using some planetary resources or other valuable items. If they win, then they would gain a lot. Actually, we, the top 100, already have some bets placed on us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So it’s like that. Interesting. It seems like the other realms are going to bleed a lot this time.”

Dongfang Yu understood what Zhao Hai wanted to say. He looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but gently shake his head. He really didn’t know where Zhao Hai got his confidence. Although he knew that Zhao Hai could almost dominate the Machine Field qualifiers, it was a different story when it comes to the experts from the other realms. The other 5 realms were on a completely different level compared to the experts of the Machine Field.

At this time, the computer had made its pick. Zhao Hai looked at the display to see who the two competitors were. One of them was a seeded participant from the Machine Field army. While the other person wasn’t seeded, he was still a level 4 expert. In fact, almost all of the top 100 participants were level 4.

The sight of so many level 4 experts was also the reason why Zhao Hai believed that the Mages and Warriors could have the power to fight those in the other realms. With 4 years of practice on average, these people were able to reach level 4. If they kept practicing in optimum conditions, then who knows what they can achieve.

It’s just a pity that nearly a hundred thousand Ascenders had either been killed or crippled with no hopes of recovering.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel anger deep in his heart. This was a complete suppression of the Ascenders by the Machine Field Natives. And since the Ascenders were the minority, they simply had no way to rebel.

At this moment, the fight had begun. The seeded participant from the Machine Field Army was a Warrior who had a long spear his hand. He was nicknamed Iron Lancer!

The reason why he was called this name was because he was a rare cavalry Warrior!

And since Iron Lancer was a cavalry warrior, he also had his mount from the lower realm. This magic beast was a special species of horse that had formidable strength. Iron Lancer’s strength as well as his mount made him a famous expert in the Machine Field army, which allowed him to be selected as one of the seeded participants in this competition.

In the previous matches, Zhao Hai was able to see Iron Lancer’s strength. He looked formidable, especially when he was on top of his mount. The mount wasn’t any worse than magic beasts from the Machine Field. The result of the coordination between beast and man was more than adding the two together.

Iron Lancer’s opponent was a Mage. This Mage was wearing dark robes, it seems like he was a Dark Mage. The Mage was thin, almost as though he was a skeleton. From what Zhao Hai saw in the previous battles, this Dark Mage specializes in summons. He could use 100-layer formations that could summon dark creatures to fight for him. His strength was also very formidable.

The current arena was now 500 meters long and 200 meters wide. This way, everyone could exert their full strength.

Iron Lancer and the Dark Mage were now about 300 meters away from each other. Iron Lancer was already on top of his mount. His mount looked very special. It had a horn on its head, a long and black body covered in scales, hooks on its tail, and fangs in its mouth. It doesn’t look like a horse, more like a wolf-horse hybrid.

When the signal to begin the fight was heard, Iron Lancer immediately held his lance and pointed it towards the Dark Mage. Then he tapped his horse’s belly twice with his foot, causing him to careen towards the Dark Mage.

At the same time, the Dark Mage held his hands to release a layered formation. Then in front of him, a giant wolf immediately appeared. This giant wolf wasn’t any smaller than Iron Lancer’s mount. Seeing the enemy, the giant wolf roared and charged.

After releasing the giant wolf, the Dark Mage quickly retreated. Simultaneously, he also waved his hand as he mumbled. Another magic formation appeared, this time it was a 30-layer formation. A rhinoceros appeared from this formation. However, the rhinoceros didn’t immediately charge towards Iron Lancer. Instead, it stood before the Dark Mage, acting as a hulking shield.

When the Dark Mage was about to chant another incantation, Iron Lancer had already dealt with the giant wolf. Iron Lancer waved his lance and then sent sword qi towards the rhinoceros. The rhino roared and released a dark shield to cover itself. And at the same time, it lowered its head and charged towards Iron Lancer.

But at this moment, Iron Lancer clamped his mount with his two legs, causing the horse to neigh and leap. It caused Iron Lancer to vault over the rhino and appear directly in front of the Dark Mage. The Dark Mage didn’t move. This was because Iron Lancer’s lance was already pointed at his throat. The Dark Mage was defeated.

After defeating the Dark Mage, Iron Lancer withdrew his weapon and then turned his gazes towards the stands. Nobody knew who he was staring at except for Zhao Hai. Iron Lancer was looking straight into Zhao Hai with a heavy look of provocation.

Chapter 1186: Wind Sword Zheng Yu

Zhao Hai looked at Iron Lancer’s departing back. Then he smiled as he turned to Xiong Li and said, “This guy. He actually dared to provoke me. It’s a shame that I’m not allowed to kill people. Or else he won’t survive.”

Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “Just wait, an opportunity will definitely come. Aren’t we all going to the Six Realm Beginner Competition? Judging by their skill, they wouldn’t be able to survive the elimination round. We can make our move then.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Let’s see when we arrive at the elimination round. To be honest, I really want to see how strong the other realms are. Big Brother Xiong, it’s your turn.” Xiong Li was picked, his opponent was a Warrior not from the 20 seeded but from the top 100 participants.

Xiong Li glanced at the list and his eyes couldn’t help but light up. He stood up and said, “Yes, I finally get to play. Brothers, I’ll head out first.” Then he immediately rushed towards the arena. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile after seeing this.

Xiong Li’s fight ended very quickly. Although his opponent wasn’t weak, he was still not a match against Xiong Li. In the following fights, nothing managed to attract Zhao Hai’s attention. Most of these fights ended quickly, long drawn out battles rarely happened.

Zhao Hai knew that all of the participants wished their fights to end quicker. After all, the longer one fights, the more flaws they would reveal.

For experts, the line between life and death was very thin. This was the truth that everyone understood. This was like wars where there were spans of days or even weeks where nothing happens. And then there would be a sudden fight to end it all.

The first day of battle ended quickly. On this day, a total of 30 battles had been organized. Of Zhao Hai’s group of four, only Xiong Li was able to fight, the others had yet to be selected.

On the next day, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the arena. But compared to the relaxed attitude on the first day, Zhao Hai and the others were more tensed. This was because they were worried that they might meet each other in the arena.

At exactly 8:00 am, the computer began to draw names. The first batch of fighters were soon selected. Upon seeing this list, the audience couldn’t help but get into an uproar.

There wasn’t anything strange on the list, nor did the four brothers manage to go up against each other. On the contrary, the list was quite common. The first on the list was Zhao Hai. But the one he was up against was Machine Field Army’s Wind Sword Zheng Yu, one of their five seeded participants.

Ever since Zheng Yu ascended, he used his sword as well as his technique in order to gain the title of the fastest sword among the beginners of the Machine Field.

And with Zheng Yu’s fast sword, he was considered to be the nemesis of Mages. Since his attacks were quick, his sword qi was also quick to hit the enemy. This timing would disrupt any Mage trying to cast magic. This caused Mages to be unable to use their skills and end up getting defeated.

It was precisely because of his talent that the people were in an uproar upon seeing the matchup. Although ordinary people didn’t know about the relationship between Zhao Hai and the Machine Field Army, just like the Machine Field Army they initially suspected Zhao Hai’s selection as a seeded participant. But after several fights, this idea soon vanished. Zhao Hai had proven to them that he had the qualifications to be seeded.

Those who were skeptical at first became supporters. After all, besides Zhao Hai, the top 20 seeded participants were well known characters in the Machine Field. It can be said that Zhao Hai was a dark horse. Everyone hoped to see him show his might and overthrow the established strong participants.

This was the reason why people become chaotic upon seeing Zhao Hai go against the nemesis of Mages, Zheng Yu.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this as he slowly approached the arena. At this time, Zheng Yu was already on the arena, staring at Zhao Hai with a cold gaze.

When Zhao Hai got on the arena, the arena’s shields immediately rose up. Zhao Hai gave Zheng Yu a salute. However, Zheng Yu didn’t return the gesture. Instead, he looked coldly at Zhao Hai and said, “Don’t think that you’re amazing just because you defeated Iron Tower. That guy is just someone who has thick skin. If you met me earlier, then you have already been killed. You should thank the committee for saving you.”

Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Yu, then he smiled faintly and said, “And why did you only tell me this now that the top 100 has been selected? The words you said just made you look bad.”

Zheng Yu looked at Zhao Hai and then said with disdain, “If you still depend on your cheating method of reaching the top 100, then you can only be at the bottom of this ranking competition. You’ll never be able to defeat another seeded participant.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Then let’s see.” At this time, the ring sounded out marking the start of the fight. Zheng Yu quickly waved his hand and taking his sword out. Then almost instantly, he waved it towards Zhao Hai, sending a sword qi flying along the way.

The sword was swung really fast, and its sword qi was similarly as quick. In almost a blink of an eye, the sword had already reached Zhao Hai.

At this moment, a formation appeared in front of Zhao Hai. Before the sword qi hit him, a shield was already there to block. Zheng Yu’s aggressive sword qi was actually blocked by Zhao Hai’s magic formation.

Although Zheng Yu was very arrogant when facing Zhao Hai, he still knew that he needed to be careful. He knew Iron Tower’s strength, so he knew that Iron Tower wouldn’t just fall down in one blow. The sword qi he sent out was just a probe to have a fair assessment of Zhao Hai strength. And at this time, Zheng Yu knew that Zhao Hai was strong.

Zheng Yu knew that he couldn’t stop. He waved his sword again and again, sending sword qi flying like machine gunfire towards Zhao Hai.

This caused the spectators to be excited. The reason these people came to watch this battle was because they saw Zhao Hai as a dark horse. He was a mysterious character whose techniques were never seen before. During his past battles, Zhao Hai would always use his dark mist, making the audience unable to see what was going on inside. When the dark mist dissipates, only then would they know that Zhao Hai had won. Only a few people were able to see Zhao Hai’s attacks. Because of this, everyone was very curious about him.

Unexpectedly, Zhao Hai didn’t cover the arena with dark mist this time. Because of this, people could now see how he fights. This caused them to feel excitement towards the show.

When Zhao Hai saw Zheng Yu’s speed in releasing sword qi, his eyes couldn’t help but shrink. While his right hand was still holding the defensive formation, Zhao Hai made some gestures with his left hand, releasing a 10-layer formation in front of him.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s action, everyone watching couldn’t help but gasp. Not only those watching, even experts from the Machine Field were surprised.

Using both hands to use two magic formations at the same time wasn’t an easy task. One needed to split their attention in order to accomplish this. Moreover, the ratio of this division needed to be seriously considered. After all, this relates to one’s control over their spiritual force. Diverting one’s concentration might cause the collapse of a formation and lead to a backlash. Because of this, most Mages would never use two formations at the same time. Using one formation for each hand like Zhao Hai was something that only a few Mages could achieve.

After Zhao Hai’s second formation was finished, large quantities of fiery arrows appeared. This formation had already become Zhao Hai’s signature, ten thousand fiery arrows. These arrows weren’t meant to attack Zheng Yu, instead it was to block the sword qi that were being sent over.

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom! Each collision caused a spectacular light show for everyone watching. This caused the audience to applaud in glee. However, there were those who stayed calm and quiet among these displays. This was because they just discovered how strong Zheng Yu and Zhao Hai were.

The arena was soon filled with smoke and sparks. Then suddenly Zhao Hai exclaimed, “Behead!” Upon saying this, he released a huge sword towards Zheng Yu’s direction.

And at the same time, Zhao Hai released hundreds of giant shields in front of him. The shields shuddered as a metallic collision was heard.

At this time, the smoke on the arena had dissipated and the audience could finally see the state of the battle. Zhao Hai’s giant shield had blocked Zheng Yu’s attack. Meanwhile, there was a giant sword that had already been cleared out by Zheng Yu.

As it turns out, not only his sword, but Zheng Yu himself was fast as well. He kept moving around to send attacks towards Zhao Hai while at the same time dodging Zhao Hai’s counterattacks.

Zhao Hai’s shield was still resisting any attacks coming his way. Zhao Hai waved his hand once more in order to prepare for another formation.

Zheng Yu was finally feeling threatened by Zhao Hai. He depended on his quick sword to disrupt Mages and triumph against them. However, Zhao Hai’s ability was completely out of his expectations. Zhao Hai could cast formations with each hand. This was equal to fighting two Mages at the same time. One Mage defends while the other attacks. There was no way for Zheng Yu to gain any high ground.

Now, after seeing Zhao Hai prepare another Magic spell, Zheng Yu couldn’t help but feel anxious. He paid careful attention to Zhao Hai and at the same time he was closing their distance.

Zhao Hai finally wielded his hand, releasing a 50-layer formation. This formation turned red before it became a one meter tall fireball. Then this fireball flew towards Zheng Yu with a speed that couldn’t be described as fast.

Zheng Yu couldn’t help but smile with scorn. He quickly moved past Zhao Hai’s fireball and then swung his sword towards Zhao Hai’s shield. In his opinion, a fireball as slow as that was no threat to him at all.

But as Zheng Yu moved, he discovered that Zhao Hai’s magic was tracking him. And after that fireball, ten more came after. Even then, Zheng Yu was still able to dodge these fireballs. The spectators couldn’t help but be confused. They didn’t understand why Zhao Hai would use slow fireballs to attack an agile opponent like Zheng Yu.

Chapter 1187: Brothers Against Each Other

Although Zheng Yu was also confused, he was in the middle of a fight and had not found anything strange. He continued to dodge Zhao Hai’s fireballs while also sending his attacks. He discovered that Zhao Hai’s giant shield was beginning to become less steady, which was good news.

With this thought in mind, Zheng Yu hastened his attacks. However, he failed to see that something had managed to surprise the spectators.

What Zheng Yu didn’t see was Zhao Hai’s fireballs still existing after he dodged them. Moreover, these fireballs slowly turned into fiery figures. These fiery figures were made entirely out of the fire element. It was one of the summoned fire element creatures.

Any magic department had their own summoning magic. The lifeform that each element summoned were also different. These fiery creatures that Zhao Hai summoned were called Flame Demons.

Actually, Fire Mages in the lower realms could also use summoning magic to summon flame demons. However, flame demons summoned in the lower realms were of the lowest level, their strength was simply bad. But in the Machine Field, with Magic Theory as well as the rich amount of spiritual qi, the flame demons that were summoned had very formidable combat strength.

Zhao Hai shot more than ten fireballs. And now, these fireballs all turned into flame demons. It was only now did the spectators understand why Zhao Hai sent out so many fireballs. His spell was actually a summoning spell, not just an ordinary fireball.

After launching about 15 fireballs, Zhao Hai’s formation finally vanished. But Zhao Hai didn’t stop here, he waved his hand once more to prepare casting another magic.

Zheng Yu’s full attention was on Zhao Hai. He was focusing on what spells Zhao Hai would use. But at this moment, he suddenly felt a burning hot sensation behind him. Zheng Yu was startled, then he immediately moved to the side, evading a claw of fire directed at his back.

Just as Zheng Yu evaded the flame demon, another flame demon came attacking. These flame demons weren’t as slow as the fireballs they originated from. Their attack speed was very fast. More than ten attacking flame demons caused Zheng Yu to be flustered.

As Zheng Yu was dodging the flame demons, Zhao Hai was finally able to cast his magic spell. A formation appeared in front of him as ten giant black arrows appeared.

These were dark killer arrows, also one of the spells Zhao Hai used before. These arrows were made from both the wind and darkness element. Their speed was very fast but they were as silent as smoke. This was the best magic to use for assassination.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent the ten arrows towards Zheng Yu. Although the speed of the arrows was fast, they didn’t make any sound, causing the target to be fairly oblivious to their approach.

Fortunately for Zheng Yu, he was still paying attention to Zhao Hai even as he was fending off the flame demons. Upon seeing Zhao Hai release fast arrows, Zheng Yu couldn’t help but get startled. Then he waved his sword faster, causing his attack towards the flame demons to be inconsistent since he was also defending against the killer arrows.

But at this moment, the ten arrows curved and shot towards Zheng Yu in all directions. Zheng Yu was shaken. However, he didn’t slow down as he waved his sword faster, causing a ball of sword qi to surround him, forming an almost impenetrable shield.

At this point, the ten dark killer arrows circled Zheng Yu’s position. They circled for a few rounds before all of them shot towards Zheng Yu once more. Zheng Yu quickly consumed his battle qi in order to deal with these arrows.

Just as he was able to fend off the arrows, arrow after arrow from Zhao Hai’s ten thousand fiery arrows spell fell from the sky. But this time, Zhao Hai deliberately made the arrows hit Zheng Yu’s surrounding area but not Zheng Yu’s position.

Seeing this outcome, Zheng Yu couldn’t help but feel helpless. He knew that he had already lost. Moreover, his defeat wasn’t due to cheating or some elaborate plot. It can be said that the fight was under Zhao Hai’s total control. Magic after magic, Zhao Hai was able to lead Zheng Yu by the nose from the very beginning. Zheng Yu simply couldn’t find his own rhythm. In this case, there was nothing left but for him to declare his loss.

Zheng Yu dejectedly stored his wind sword as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I lost. Zhao Hai, you’re strong. I was defeated fair and square.” Then after giving Zhao Hai a salute, he turned around and left the arena.

At this moment, the referee also made a declaration of Zhao Hai’s win. At this point, the referees wouldn’t dare act unreasonably. They wouldn’t dare turn any matter into something sensitive. Once they do so, they would certainly suffer extreme bad luck.

Zhao Hai went down from the arena and returned to where Xiong Li and the others were. Xiong Li heavily patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Little Hai, you were really great out there. Very good. Very very good.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “He’s just a bit neglectful.”

Dongfang Yu shook his head and said, “Come on, Little Hai, do you treat us as fools? He didn’t underestimate you, he just isn’t your enemy. I asked Little Fei for his opinion and he told me that even he wouldn’t have good odds winning against Zheng Yu.”

Sun Fei smiled bitterly and said, “It’s just too hard. Zheng Yu is truly fit to be called the Wind Sword. His sword is very fast. If Big Brother Hai isn’t able to cast two formations at once, then I’m afraid you would have lost.”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “Yes, Zheng Yu’s sword technique is very fast. He’s truly formidable. Right, let’s stop talking about him. How about I teach you how to cast two magics at once when we’re free?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. One must know that being able to cast two formations at once was a huge help when it came to real battles. Although this meant that one’s energy consumption would double, releasing two spells instead of one was an enormous advantage during fights. There were crucial times where another magic spell was needed in order to finish the battle. Also, having such an ability was a very good trump card to use against the enemy.

Sun Fei immediately agreed. At this time, the second batch of participants had been selected. This time, Dongfang Yu was called. However, his opponent wasn’t one of the seeded participants but instead it was one from the top 100. Dongfang Yu said his farewell to the group before heading to his arena.

Because of Zhao Hai, Xiong Li, Sun Fei, and Dongfang Yu’s close relationship, the people from the Machine Field had already called them the Four Brothers. In addition to their good relationship, they were also very strong.

And since their relationship was good, the Ashley Family, Wu Family, Yan Family, and the Fire Temple had already formed an alliance. This was completely out of the Ashley Family’s expectations. However, they really liked this outcome.

Dongfang Yu’s opponent was a Mage. Moreover, the Mage was quite strong so Dongfang Yu proceeded with caution. But with Dongfang Yu’s mastery of his fire dragon technique, the battle was over before long.

At this point, of the four brothers, only Sun Fei had yet to fight. But Sun Fei’s luck was very good. On the second to the last round, he was able to have his turn to fight.

Sun Fei’s opponent was also a Mage. But since the Mage wasn’t among the seeded participants, Sun Fei was able to easily win.

After two days of fighting, the top 50 was finally decided. The next few days would be Zhao Hai and the others’s rest days. These days would be used to rank the number 51 to 100 positions.

Although it was just the ranking battles for the 51st to 100th place, massive amounts of people still came over to watch. After all, these people were the most outstanding newcomers in the past 5 years. The quality of their fights would truly be worth looking at.

After four days of battles, the ranking from 51st to 100th had finally been decided. Wind Sword Zheng Yu was able to easily take up the number 51st slot. This also made it clear to everyone how strong seeded participants were. And it also highlighted Zhao Hai’s strength.

Now that the ranking for the lower half has been decided it was time to see who would get the 1st to 50th place. It was time for Zhao Hai and the others to return to the arena.

After one day, the top 25 had been chosen. Zhao Hai and the others had another chance to rest. These days would be used to decide the 26th to 50th positions.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai and his brothers had yet to meet. The four advanced smoothly up to the top 25. During this time, Zhao Hai was once again faced with another seeded participant. But this person wasn’t from the Machine Field Army. Instead, it was a seeded participant from the Radiant Temple. But in the end, he was still defeated by Zhao Hai.

After the 26th to 50th positions were dealt with, it was time for the top 25 to fight once more. But since there would only be 12 battles, one lucky person would be chosen to have a free passage to the next round. There was no other way of doing things, after all, one person couldn’t fight two battles on the same day.

And this good luck actually fell into Sun Fei’s head. Since Sun Fei was able to progress with no effort, naturally, Zhao Hai and the others had him treat them to a meal.

The remaining 24 people would be divided into 12 pairs. But this time, Zhao Hai and the others weren’t in luck. Zhao Hai finally bumped into one of his brothers, Dongfang Yu. This battle naturally attracted a very large amount of spectators. Those viewing online had also skyrocketed. The reason for this was because the two were now very famous experts in the Machine Field. Another reason was because the two were very close friends. Because of this, the audience wanted to see the result of their battle.

Zhao Hai and Dongfang Yu stood on the arena. Dongfang Yu looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled bitterly as he said, “I didn’t expect to be this unfortunate this soon. Alright Kid, don’t you dare show mercy. I don’t want our fight to look lame.”

Upon hearing Dongfang Yu, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he replied, “I have always looked forward to receiving brother’s fire dragon technique. Come, Second Brother, let’s have a proper fight!”

Dongfang Yu also laughed and said, “Alright, let me have a look at your strength!” Then he waved his fiery red dragon sword before pointing it towards Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1188: Xiong Li vs Zhang Qinghe

At this time, the ring to start the battle was heard. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he waved his hand and a 5-layer formation appeared in front of him. Then the formation turned red before a red dragon flew out of it and then headed straight towards Dongfang Yu.

When Dongfang Yu saw Zhao Hai’s attack, he couldn’t help but laugh. Then he waved his fire dragon sword and then sent a fiery red sword qi towards Zhao Hai’s fire dragon.

However, much to Dongfang Yu’s surprise, just as his sword qi was about to cut the Fire Dragon, the dragon opened its mouth and then swallowed the sword qi. After the sound of an explosion, Dongfang Yu’s sword qi vanished. On the other hand, the dragon’s head was the only thing left of its body. Nevertheless, the head kept flying towards Dongfang Yu.

Dongfang Yu shouted, “Ha!” Then he moved and retreated. At the same time, he continually waved his sword and sent sword qi after sword qi towards Zhao Hai’s fire dragon.

Dongfang Yu didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s control over magic to be this delicate. Moreover, his magic actually had this much power to it.

What Dongfang Yu didn’t know was that this was the most ordinary kind of attack Zhao Hai could do. If Zhao Hai mixed in astral qi to his attack, then his attacking strength would increase even more.

The emotion below the arena was mixed. There were those who saw the magnificent display of the two fighters and felt excited. They shouted and waved their hands with each blow.

But as for the other participants left in the competition, they couldn’t help but turn silent as they looked at the two. Xiong Li and Sun Fei were sitting beside each other. While looking at the arena, Xiong Li turned to Sun Fei and said, “Little Fei, what magic did Little Hai use? How could it be that strong? Dongfang actually used three sword qi strikes in order to get rid of it.”

Sun Fei smiled bitterly and said, “On the surface, it looks just like an ordinary 10-layer fire dragon spell. However, I am sure that 10-layer fire dragons cannot be that strong. From what I can see, Brother Hai uses formations that I had never seen before. I don’t know what formations he used to make his sets. This is the reason why his spells are much stronger than average.”

Although Xiong Li wasn’t a Mage, he was still clear about matters regarding magic formations. So upon hearing Sun Fei, his brows couldn’t help but tighten up as he said, “You mean Little Hai has been creating his own formations?”

Sun Fei shook his head and said, “That’s impossible. I might believe it if he created his own formation sets. But formations? That is absolutely impossible. Creating your own magic formations is much more difficult than creating formation sets. It’s possible that those formations are the secret formations of the Ashley Family. After all, secret formations of a family aren’t allowed to be distributed outside.”

Xiong Li nodded, then he sighed and said, “I heard that I am a genius. But comparing to Little Hai, I’m just too far off. This kid just ascended roughly a year ago and he’s now this strong. It’s really unbelievable.”

Sun Fei nodded, he sighed as he said, “I don’t want to think about that right now. Because whenever I do, I feel like killing myself.”

Upon hearing Sun Fei, Xiong LI couldn’t help but laugh. He patted Sun Fei’s shoulder and said, “Don’t think about it too much. That kid is a demon that can’t be compared to normal standards.”

As the two were talking, Dongfang Yu and Zhao Hai continued to exchange blows for several rounds. Although the attacks the two dished out looked impressive, those who were knowledgeable knew that the two were holding back. They were just comparing their qualitative abilities. It was basically an exhibition match.

This caused those who were watching to feel confused. They knew that the two had a great relationship with each other. However, this competition had something to do with their rankings as well as the benefits of their families. In this case, they shouldn’t be playing around. However, the two were doing just that, they were playing around.

The two continued to clash for half an hour. The formations Zhao Hai used were mostly from the fire element. Meanwhile, Dongfang Yu proved his skill with his fire dragon sword as he swung it in all kinds of directions. Their fight looked very lively, it was very entertaining for the spectators. Meanwhile, the referee couldn’t help but bitterly smile from time to time. The two actually used the ranking tournament as a place to spar.

However, he couldn’t stop the fight. After all, the two were still fighting and didn’t stop for a moment to chat. This made the referee helpless once more.

After ten more minutes of fighting, Zhao Hai and Dongfang Yu finally got bored. They now had a fair idea of the other party’s strength. Dongfang Yu was truly strong, but he was still inferior when compared to Zhao Hai.

Once they reached this understanding, Dongfang Yu withdrew his fire dragon sword as he laughed and said, “Alright, that’s enough. Then I’ll have to depend on you when we face the other realms.” Then he turned to the referee and then said, “I admit defeat!”

Upon seeing the conclusion, the referee didn’t say anything and immediately declared Zhao Hai as the winner. In any case, nobody would oppose to Dongfang Yu losing.

 Zhao Hai looked at Dongfang Yu and then he laughed and said, “Don’t worry, leave those fellows from the other realms to me. Let’s go, we still need to make Little Fei bleed. After Boss Xiong’s battle, we’ll go drink.” After this, the two proceeded to walk off the arena.

Looking at the two laughing and being friendly with each other, those under the arena were surprisingly not angry. Instead, they gave the two a heavy applause. For the people on the stands, this was a testament to the two brothers’s friendship.

However, those who were knowledgeable saw something else. Although the match between the two was merely a spar, they saw that Dongfang Yu was in fact exerting some effort in the last couple of clashes. However, Zhao Hai just easily received these attacks. Even if the two engaged in real combat, Zhao Hai would still be the winner.

Also, those watching below recalled that Zhao Hai had yet to use any items to defeat his opponents. He did so ever since the start of the qualifiers. In this case, how strong was Zhao Hai really? A lot of people couldn’t help but submit when they thought of this.

One must know that Zhao Hai’s previous opponents weren’t pushoevers. Also, there was Zheng Yu and Iron Tower, people from the Machine Field Army who had a grudge against Zhao Hai. In this case, it was impossible for these two to be lenient towards him. But even so, Zhao Hai still managed to easily defeat them. This just shows how strong Zhao Hai really was.

After Zhao Hai and Dongfang Yu returned to where Xiong Li and Sun Fei were, Xiong Li looked at Dongfang Yu and said, “Dongfang, how is Little Hai’s strength? Is he a little bit strong? After all, I still need to beat him.”

Dongfang Yu gave Xiong Li a look as he said, “Brother Xiong, don’t blame me for reminding you. Even if you are a little stronger than me, you’re still a long way off from Little Hai. If I were you, I’d surrender immediately.”

Xiong Li snorted and said, “Get lost. If I have to admit defeat, then it will be after a huge fight. Otherwise, people will think that I’m weaker than you.”

Upon hearing Xiong Li, Sun Fei and Dongfang Yu couldn’t help but laugh. At this time, the next round of participants were called over. This time, it was Meteor Zhu Chen versus Iron Lancer. It was a heavy matchup. There was no need to talk about Zhu Chen. Just like Sun Fei’s situation, he was absorbed by the Divine Earth Palace. His defensive strength was astonishing while his offensive strength wasn’t that bad. Moreover, he was vicious and merciless.

Iron Lancer, on the other hand, was a rare cavalry warrior. He had a powerful offense while his mount adds to his mobility. A man and his mount managed to reach the top 25. Only a small number of people were able to fight him for more than 20 mins. It was obvious that his strength wasn’t low.

These two against each other would surely be a good show. Xiong Li became excited to see the match. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai looked at Zhu Chen’s appearance. Zhu Chen wasn’t tall, he was fat and looked a little like Buddha. But his eyes were very cold, enough to make one’s hair stand up.

Even with his cold eyes, Zhu Chen had a smiling face. He had the smile of a person who had just been on vacation for a very long time. It was hard to say what he was thinking about.

At this time, Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “This Zhu Chen looks more annoying than Iron Lancer. He’s still smiling as though he hadn’t killed a lot of people. I hate these kinds of people the most.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Xiong Li as he smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, in any case, murder is no longer allowed in the arena. Let’s wait until the Six Realm Beginner Competition, let’s destroy him then.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others turned to him. Xiong Li looked around them as he whispered, “Little Hai, don’t speak like that. If the others know that we’re planning to kill people during the Six Realm Beginner Competition, they’ll never let us off.”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “As long as we get a good position and gain benefits for the Machine Field, they wouldn’t dare touch us. When the time comes, they wouldn’t even have enough time to give us praises.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the three brothers looked at each other and saw a trace of excitement in their eyes. They weren’t afraid of fighting other people. However, this was offending the Machine Field. They were still aware of their own strengths. But if they could deal with reprehensible people, that would be good as well.

Zhao Hai looked at the three and smiled. Then he turned his attention to the arena. It seems like Zhu Chen and Iron Lancer were talking to each other. It’s just a pity that the arena’s shield blocked any noise from coming out. However, before long, the two began to make a move.

Zhu Chen’s defensive abilities were truly strong. 5, 10-layer formations were conveniently thrown out. As for Iron Lancer, even if he had formidable offensive strength, he still couldn’t break through Zhu Chen’s defenses in a short time. Meanwhile, Zhu Chen was counterattacking using his Earth Magic. He used Quicksand as well as Earth Spikes. These two spells were fatal towards cavalry units. Although it can be said that Iron Lancer’s mount wasn’t bad, it still couldn’t do anything against those it was weak against.

Moreover, Zhu Chen’s attacks weren’t actually weak. But one could say that it wasn’t something on par with the others in his rank. And even if Iron Lancer’s attacks were being dulled, this didn’t mean that he couldn’t deal with Zhu Chen’s counters. This caused Zhu Chen to be unable to do anything to Iron Lancer.

Zhao Hai and the others were already prepared for such an outcome. Zhu Chen was someone who was strong in defense but weak in attack. Generally, he would defeat his enemies by grinding them down until they could no longer go on. This meant that among the top 100, the longest battles would certainly involve him.

This time wasn’t an exception. Iron Lancer would attack but he couldn’t deal with Zhu Chen’s defense. Then there was Zhu Chen’s weak counterattack. To be honest, his means of attack couldn’t compare to his defense. His offensive means were too limited.

Zhao Hai looked at the battle and couldn’t help but feel sleepy. From the perspective of others, this might look like a beautiful battle. But in Zhao Hai’s eyes, it was practically meaningless. This battle involved too many matters that both sides were unable to fight at a very solid level.

And just like Zhao Hai thought, the battle went on for more than one hour. In the end, Zhu Chen was able to grind Iron Lancer down and then win. However, the audience was very discontented with the battle. This was because it was too boring. They preferred Zhao Hai and Dongfang Yu’s spar than this.

After this fight, it was Xiong Li’s turn. Xiong Li had a very good opponent this time. His opponent was one of the Ten Great Experts, tenth place Golden Egg Zhang Qinghe.

Zhang Qinghe was a Metal element Mage. His confrontation with Xiong Li would certainly be full of action. Therefore, when Zhao Hai saw that he was Xiong Li’s opponent, he turned to Xiong Li and said, “Boss Xiong, you need to be careful. This isn’t like your previous fights. You might be eliminated.”

Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “I’ll be fine. Don’t forget, I still need to spar with you.” Then he stood up and walked to the arena. However, his mood wasn’t as relaxed as his words. It was clear that he was attaching great importance towards Zhang Qinghe.

Zhang Qinghe being a metal element Mage meant that his offensive strength wasn’t something to joke about. And with his background of being a metal element ability user in the lower realms, this meant that he was flexible in his attacks. Moreover, it was rumored that his control over metal was formidable. He was certainly a very difficult opponent to face. To be honest, if talking about offensive strength, then Zhang Qinghe would be up there with Sun Fei.

Xiong Li and Zhang Qinghe stood at the arena and then looked at each other. Both knew that the other party wasn’t someone easy to deal with. Although the Ten Great Experts were one group, they haven’t really met each other before. Also, they haven’t experienced each other’s strength. With this in mind, they would certainly be cautious when faced with each other.

Once the bell rang, Xiong Li immediately roared and then took his hammers before charging forward.

Zhang Qinghe waved his hand and released a huge iron ball. Then this iron ball divided itself into five smaller balls. After that, he cast a layered magic formation, causing an explosion in the sky that rained arrows towards Xiong Li.

Chapter 1189: Streep Enters the Stage

Zhang Qinghe’s rain of arrows was different than Zhao Hai’s ten thousand fiery arrows. The latter was a mix between the metal and the fire element. Meanwhile, Zhang Qinghe’s rain of arrows only involved the metal element. However, it was quicker, sharper, and had more penetrative power.

Xiong Li coldly snorted, then he waved his sledgehammer, causing a round sword qi to appear. This sword qi was something unique to Xiong LI’s hammers. It was a type of sword qi transformation. Swords would send out slashes or arrow-type sword qi. Meanwhile, Xiong Li’s sword qi was round due to his hammers.

Zhang Qinghe’s arrow rain was quickly dispersed. Xiong Li proceeded to wave his other sledgehammer, sending a round sword qi towards Zhang Qinghe. Xiong Li didn’t see Zhang Qinghe set up a defensive formation. So he wanted to send a long-range attack to see how defensively strong Zhang Qinghe was.

Zhang Qinghe didn’t dodge. Instead, one of the five iron balls stopped in front of him and transformed into a shield. Xiong Li’s sword qi that was supposed to hit Zhang Qinghe was instead blocked by this iron shield.

The iron shield in front of Zhang Qinghe shuddered and made a large ringing sound. It managed to block Xiong Li’s attack.

When he saw this, Xiong Li’s eyes shrank. He knew that even if his attacks looked normal, they actually contained 70% of his strength. And since his fighting technique was mainly based in strength, his attacks couldn’t be blocked by any simple 5-layer formation. But now, Zhang Qinghe managed to block it by using an iron ball. It seems like his defensive ability was quite strong.

Although he just found out that Zhang Qinghe was strong, Xiong Li wasn’t demoralized. On the contrary, he was even more excited. He had always wished for an even match. It’s just a pity that his previous opponents couldn’t satisfy his craving.

With this thought in mind, Xiong Li couldn’t help but laugh loudly. His battle intent flared up as he said, “Good, Zhang Qinghe, you didn’t disappoint me. Hahaha, come. Let’s fight.” Then he roared and then threw himself towards Zhang QInghe.

When Zhang Qinghe saw Xiong Li’s approach, he couldn’t help but feel bitter deep inside. Although it seemed that he easily blocked Xiong Li’s blows, he was actually exerting great effort on it. Xiong Li’s attack was too strong. It would be uncomfortable if Xiong Li continued his assault.

Zhang Qinghe immediately changed his tactic. He went as far from Xiong Li as possible. Then he used magic to attack. Also, he made it a priority to block Xiong Li’s round hammer qi.

Naturally, Xiong Li discovered this change of Zhang Qinghe. He wasn’t annoyed by it. After all, this was a common tactic in a fight between Mages and Warriors. Although Warriors in the Machine Field could send out their sword qi to attack Mages at a distance, it would still take time for their attack to reach the target. Mages can use this time to either defend or dodge. It was the same thing as Warriors strafing in order to avoid the spells Mages send their way.

Xiong Li had experienced such tactics many times before, so he had ways to deal with it. Even so in an arena with a limited surface area. Xiong Li wasn’t afraid of this tactic.

Xiong Li moved his body and turned sharply. The sledgehammers in his hand danced causing shadows to fly towards Zhang Qinghe. Zhao Hai paid attention to this and saw that Xiong Li’s hammer technique was quite special. Not only was it a technique for close combat, it was a technique that combines both the hammer as well as the sword qi that was released during the process.

Close combat techniques can only attack the enemy within the range of the Warrior. Meanwhile, sword qi could attack the enemy from a distance. Xiong Li’s technique was a combination between close combat as well as sword qi. Together, his hammer technique would launch sword qi towards Zhang Qinghe, proceeding to restrict Zhang Qinghe like wall. This caused Zhang Qinghe’s area of action to get smaller and smaller. At this point, keeping distance against Xiong Li was becoming impossible for Zhang Qinghe.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and discovered that Xiong Li’s hammers were specially made. Not only can they launch hammer qi, they were also connected with each other by a chain. This chain was very long, allowing Xiong Li to make the range of his hammers dozens of meters. This range couldn’t be underestimated.

Zhang Qinghe also knew Xiong Li’s plan. To be honest, Xiong Li’s tactic wasn’t intelligent. However, it was a very effective brute force method.

Xiong Li was tall and sturdy. He was super strong and also had an astonishing defensive strength. At the same time, his talent for fighting was very good. His methods were very effective, causing Zhang Qinghe to not know what to do.

As the space got closer and closer, the distance between the two got smaller and smaller. Zhang Qinghe knew that this couldn’t go on. He clenched his teeth and exerted some energy as he waved his hand. His five iron balls slammed together and formed an enormous shield in front of him. At the same time, he released a spell. It seems like he wanted to block Xiong Li using his shield while also using the opportunity to use powerful magic to make Xiong Li retreat. This way, he could gain some space for himself to move.

However, if he did this, the amount of spiritual force that he’d use would be huge and he’d risk losing to Xiong Li. But if he didn’t do this now, he can only be pushed back by Xiong Li until he surrenders.

But just as the enormous shield was set up, Xiong Li pulled on the chains of his hammers and then received them. Then his body flew towards the shield. He held his sledgehammers up before smashing straight down towards the shield!

Bang! A loud sound of collision was heard. Zhang Qinghe who was casting his spell was shaken. He knew that the matter he was most worried about had happened. Xiong Li didn’t wait for him to form his spell and instead just immediately attacked.

Zhang Qinghe let out a long breath. He knew that he had lost since Xiong Li managed to reach him. While he was disappointed at his loss, he looked at Xiong Li and said, “I lost.”

Xiong Li was just about to smash his hammer down once more when he saw that the shield had suddenly vanished. Then Zhang Qinghe admitted his defeat. Xiong Li couldn’t help but stare, then he clicked is cheek and said, “Boring” Then he took his hammer down. After the referee announced that he has won, he unhappily went down from the arena.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li’s expression. Then he smiled and said, “Big Brother, don’t get too disappointed. Let’s go have a drink. There’s no longer anything worthy of watching anyway.”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “Alright, alright, let’s drink.” But just as the group was about to leave, Dongfang Yu paused and then stopped Xiong Li and the others. This caused Xiong Li and the others to stare. Then Dongfang Yu pointed towards the arena. And when they saw who was on, they decided to stay.

After Xiong Li’s fight, the next group of fighters were selected. The person chosen for this battle made Zhao Hai’s group stop. This was because the person that appeared on the arena was too famous. If fame was discussed, then he was much much more famous than Xiong Li. It was Streep.

Saint of Ice Streep. He was the Water Temple’s most talented genius in recent years. He was both powerful and handsome. He was the prince on a white horse that countless young girls in the Machine Field idolize. Moreover, he was polite to others and does good things. He was the incarnation of perfect.

However, Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t true. Zhao Hai doesn’t believe that a perfect person exists. If such a person existed, then he would have long since died. Moreover, Streep wouldn’t have been able to ascend if he was that good. He surely had killed countless people in the lower realms.

But in the Machine Field, Streep actually managed to gain fame by being a saint. This caused Zhao Hai to be confused. Who knew what kind of potion this guy managed to get.

The Machine Field wasn’t the same as ancient China. This wasn’t the place where you could act like a saint and people would treat you like a saint. The Machine Field placed strength first. If you were weak, then even if you were good, nobody would save you. But if you were strong, even if you were a wicked person, some group would still protect you. It was because of this that Zhao Hai was confused. He didn’t know what Streep was planning to do with his reputation.

Since he had this thought, Zhao Hai wanted to see Streep. So when he discovered that Streep was going to fight, he couldn’t help but stop as well.

There was no need to talk about Xiong Li and the others. Streep was ranked first among the Ten Great Experts. Xiong Li wasn’t convinced by the ranking. So after seeing that Streep was about to fight, he decided to stay back and spectate.

In the past, whenever Streep was about to fight someone, his opponent would immediately admit defeat. And after reaching the top 100, Streep wasn’t able to meet a good match. He managed to end his battles in 2-3 moves. Therefore, up until now, Zhao Hai and the others hadn’t managed to take a good look at Streep’s strength.

The reason why they thought that Streep would have to fight properly today was because of his opponent. Streep’s opponent was also one of the Ten Great Experts, Army Breaker Lu Dingtian!

Army Breaker Lu Dingtian was the most secretive among the Ten Great Experts. People might expect Lone Wolf Yan Zhengshan to be the most secretive. However, ever since Yan Zhengshan ascended four years ago, he was already able to kill a thousand enemies. Although these things were done in a low-key manner, the matter themselves weren’t a secret.

Lu Dingtian was different. He was very secretive in both his matters and his actions. However, nobody doubted his strength. Being able to defeat an army only by using his dagger-axe was enough for him to join the Ten Great Experts.

Chapter 1190: Streep’s Peculiarity

Streep was an idol to a lot of young women. His appearance was very handsome and he also had hair that could make even the most beautiful women jealous.

Compared to him, Lu Dingtian looked very ordinary. Lu Dingtian looked about 30 years old. He was dark and thin. He wasn’t that tall. His facial features were on the cold side. He had a full body armor on as he held his dagger axe in his hand. He looked like a warrior from ancient times, but not the strong one.[1]

After the two stood on the arena, Streep bowed towards Lu Dingtian. Lu Dingtian returned the gesture with a salute. However, this salute was quite unusual. He just knocked his dagger axe on the ground, and that’s it.

The bell for the start of the battle was heard. Lu Dingtian held his dagger-axe with his two hands and then looked attentively at Streep. Meanwhile, Streep had a faint smile on his face, looking very confident.

Zhao Hai was about to concentrate on the battle when he suddenly heard shouting behind him. This startled him. He turned around and saw women behind him turning crazy as they shouted Streep’s name.

Zhao Hai stared, he couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He didn’t expect to see starstruck fans in the Machine Field as well. And it seems like they were manic fans too.

Naturally, Xiong Li and the others were able to notice these women. Just like Zhao Hai, they also couldn’t help but bitterly smile. Xiong Li sighed and said, “This guy is really taking advantage of women.” Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “I always hated guys like him. I’d like to face him once later on.” At this time, Streep and Lu Dingtian have already begun to move. Just before Lu Dingtian moved, Streep sent out a 10-layer formation. Moreover, this was sent out instantaneously. However, Lu Dingtian wasn’t a pushover. This caused their exchange to be very lively.

Zhao Hai saw Streep’s actions and couldn’t help but feel strange. Streep used very ordinary magic formations. It can be said that these formations couldn’t have huge power behind them. However, in Streep’s hands, these formations had actually become powerful. It was very strange.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai talked to Laura inside his head, “Laura, look into Streep’s situation. I want to know how he’s able to improve the power of these magic formations.” Laura and the others complied and immediately analyzed Streep’s footage using the scanner. Before long, a result came out.

Laura quickly reported, “Brother Hai, we found it. The reason of Streep’s strength might be because of his cultivation technique. It’s possible that he has something that is mixed with his spiritual force that made his formations more powerful. It’s the same as your astral qi.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his expression changed as he said, “Like astral qi? But his formations doesn’t have traces of astral qi. Maybe it’s another energy, like evil qi?” Laura replied, “We don’t know yet, we haven’t seen evil qi.”

Zhao Hai didn’t ask anymore. He already knew that Lu Dingtian would lose. Streep has something similar to Zhao Hai’s astral qi. This meant that his strength was a stage or two higher than Lu Dingtian. There was no way for Lu Dingtian to win.

However, Lu Dingitan wasn’t someone to be trifled with. Although Streep was using an unknown energy to attack Lu Dingtian, Lu Dingitan was still able to defend. None of the two were able to gain an advantage for quite a while.

After fighting for an hour, Lu Dingtian was finally caught with a freezing attack. Streep had won.

Seeing this result, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but have a heavy expression. Xiong Li could gauge that he and Lu Dingtian had the same strength. It might be possible for the two of them to injure one another when they fight. But now, Lu Dingtian was actually defeated. This meant that he wasn’t a match against Streep. This caused Xiong Li’s mood to get heavy.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li’s expression, then he smiled and said, “What’s the matter Big Brother Xiong? You feel afraid? Rest assured, I’ll deal with him if ever we meet.”

When Xiong Li heard Zhao Hai, he glared at him and said, “Get lost. Who says I’m afraid of him? But to be honest, Streep really has true skill.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly. He knew why Streep was strong, even if he didn’t know what exact energy it was. But Streep was indeed strong. It seems like he really deserved to be in the first place of the Ten Great Experts.

 The group found a place to eat and then proceeded to take a rest. The next day, they returned to the stadium in order to attend the competition for the final 13 competitors. They would be divided into 6 groups with one person being the bye. It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai and the others knew who the lucky person was. The person selected to be the bye was one of the Ten Great Experts, Swift Wind and Rain Lei Xiaotian. He was a Mage of two elements and a person from the Wind God Palace’s Lei Family.

Now that Lei Xiaotian has been selected as the bue, the remaining participants had to be selected to fight. This time Sun Fei wasn’t lucky. He was arranged to fight against Meteor Zhu Chen. They proceeded to fight each other in the arena and in the end, Sun Fei wasn’t able to penetrate Zhu Chen’s defenses and was finally defeated.

Xiong Li’s opponent was also one of the Ten Great Experts. It was Lone Wolf Yan Zhenshan. Yan Zhenshan was fast and very agile, but he was eventually defeated by Xiong Li. However, Xiong Li also exerted some effort in order to win.

As time went by, Zhao Hai was finally picked. This time his opponent was also one of the Ten Great Experts, it was the person Zhao Hai saw in the past, Strongwind Li Kuangren.

To be honest, Zhao Hai had taken a liking to Li Kuangren. Although this person was impulsive and hot-headed, he was straightforward. He wasn’t someone who would let injustice happen in front of him.

When Zhao Hai got on the arena and stood opposite Li Kuangren, he smiled faintly as he bowed and said, “I have long heard about the name Strongwind Li Kuangren. I’ve admired you especially the last time when you confronted Zhang Family’s Zhang Mingyue. It’s just a pity that the Five Element Swordsmen made things difficult. I’ve missed a great opportunity to get to know you. It’s truly regrettable.”

When Li Kuangren heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but have a favorable impression of him. So upon hearing Zhao Hai, Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. I’ll be honest with you, I didn’t agree to you being seeded in the beginning. But after seeing you fight in the last few days,  this Li Kuangren has been convinced. Meeting you today is my misfortune. This Li Kuangren knows that I’m not your match, but I still like to try.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Hahaha, then how about we drink together after our fight? I’ll introduce you to my brothers Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, and Sun Fei.”

Li Kuangren was amused, he nodded and said, “That would be great. But mister, we need to begin.” At this time, the bell rang to start the fight. Li Kuangren held his two axes in his hands.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he immediately sent out a 5-layer formation to begin his fight with Li Kuangren. Although Li Kuangren knew that he wasn’t Zhao Hai’s match, he was still a Warrior and he wanted to at least give it a try. At the same time, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back. He knew that he couldn’t hold back against people like Li Kuangren. If he did, then Li Kuangren would think that Zhao Hai was looking down on him. Therefore, Zhao Hai let loose on casting his spells, making the arena very lively.

After exchanging blows for half an hour, Zhao Hai was finally able to see an opportunity to capture and defeat Li Kuangren. Once the two got down from the arena, Zhao Hai introduced Li Kuangren to Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, and Sun Fei. The group proceeded to get some drinks, no longer caring about the rest of the fights.

The next day was the competition to get the top 4. Naturally, since there were 7 participants left, another bye would be selected. Although it looks unfair, this was the fairest way to go forward. But when the result came about, people were doubting whether the results were being manipulated or not. This was because Lei Xiaotian was chosen once again.

Not to say Zhao Hai, even XIong Li and the others were surprised. Nevertheless, the competition must continue. Zhao Hai was in the first match. This match was actually against an old acquaintance, Zhu Chen.

Upon seeing Zhu Chen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He had always wanted to test out Zhu Chen’s defensive capabilities. The two didn’t talk and just waited for the bell to start. Once the bell rang, Zhu Chen immediately set up shields to protect himself.

Zhao Hai would naturally be impolite. He immediately unleashed his spells. Ten 50-layer formations were quickly thrown out towards Zhu Chen. This was something that has never been seen before.

Zhu Chen didn’t attack and just went full-on defense. On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t bother to make any defensive measures as he went completely offensive. This caused the spectators to focus on the battle. This was a battle between offense and defense that has never been seen in this competition before.

Zhao Hai had yet to use his astral qi in this competition. There simply was no need to do so. He also refrained from using astral qi in his battle with Zhu Chen. Although he was now in the offensive side and was consuming more energy. Zhu Chen’s energy consumption was surely not small. He could grind Zhu Chen down this way.

People already had an idea about Zhao Hai’s strength. But after seeing Zhao Hai send out 50-layer formations in an instant, they couldn’t help but reevaluate him. There was no longer ang trace of doubt towards Zhao Hai.

Their fight went on for an hour. And throughout this span of time, Zhao Hai’s offense never got weaker. Zhu Chen actually couldn’t bear the pressure and was forced to drink a restoration potion. However, the restoration was slow and with the rate of his consumption, Zhu Chen was quickly pushed into a corner. He didn’t have any opportunity to counterattack.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t drink any potions until now. One could see from this point that he was stronger than Zhu Chen. Zhu Chen also knew that he could no longer go on with this fight. Because of this, he immediately announced his surrender.

* * *

Dagger-axe(戈)

Chapter 1191: Final Four!

The final four were finally revealed. They were Zhao Hai, Streep, Xiong Li, and Lei Xiaotian. This time, drawing a bye wasn’t needed. But after they were selected, the four were given a few days of rest. What happened next was the battle between the 5th to the 25th place. This would make the battle between the four the highlight of the qualifier.

Zhao Hai paid attention to the battle for the 5th to the 25th place. After all, Sun Fei and the others were among the participants. And the result was satisfactory. Sun Fei, Dongfang Yu, and Li Kuangren placed in the top ten. Li Kuangren was sixth, Dongfang Yu was eighth, and Sun Fei was tenth.

Although the battle for the 5th to 25th place was very heated, the climax of the qualifiers, the battle between the top four, had yet to happen.

The ranking competition for the 5th to 25th place used up three days. Zhao Hai used these days to watch the competition. And after each event, the brothers would go and have a drink. The time was spent merrily.

The past several days also allowed Xiong Li and the others to understand Li Kuangren more. It was quite obvious that Li Kuangren had quite a fiery temperament. Moreover, not only was he hot-headed, he was the type of person who would give a person a beating right then and there.

But generally speaking, this kind of character made Li Kuangren straightforward and likeable. There was no right or wrong in his eyes, only something he accepted and didn’t accept. Even if it was he was an emperor, as long as he agrees to something, then anything could work. Even if you took his axe in exchange for wine, he wouldn’t say anything and would just laugh about it.

If such a person fell under bad hands, then he would become a tool to do their bidding. But after Zhao Hai and the others came in contact with Li Kuangren, they knew that Li Kuangren’s family weren’t bad people.

…

Finally, the day tens of thousands of people were waiting for had arrived. It was the start of the battle between the top 4. The first battle immediately began, it was Streep vs Xiong Li.

Upon seeing this matchup, everyone in the stands became excited. Streep was the first among the Ten Great Experts. He was the person most people expected to gain first place in the competition. He was also handsome and polite, making him very famous in the Machine Field.

On the other hand, Xiong Li was second among the Ten Great Experts. His fighting strength was formidable. And with his tall and strong appearance, he was also a dream man for quite a few women. Moreover, he was the sole Warrior among the top four. This made him very famous among the Warriors.

This was a collision between the first and second Great Experts. Sparks were flying in all directions. This caused everyone to be excited.

The competition between the top four couldn’t compare to any other ranking tournament. Because of this, the fight needed to be more formal. After the fighters were selected, both sides were given half an hour to prepare before they would fight.

At this time, Xiong Li was sitting down as he looked at the far away Streep. Streep also saw Xiong Li, but he just smiled and nodded. His demeanor was very polite.

Although Xiong Li was repulsed by Streep, he also knew that there were a lot of people looking at them at this time. So he didn’t lose his temper and just smiled and returned Streep’s nod.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li’s action and couldn’t help but smile. Then he whispered to Xiong Li’s ear, “Boss Xiong, you need to be careful. I’ve received some information in the past few days. Streep is strange.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li became curious, so he asked, “Strange? What’s strange about him?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I suspect that Streep has experienced a lucky encounter. I’ve been looking into his battles in the past few days. His magic formations are just ordinary ones, but their attacking power is very powerful. I think he has something that could make his spells stronger than normal. So you need to be extra careful when you fight him.”

When Xiong Li heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he nodded and said, “Alright, I got it. Don’t worry, I’ll be careful.” Zhao Hai nodded.

Half an hour quickly passed by. Xiong Li and Streep proceeded towards the arena. When the two stepped into the arena, their expressions couldn’t help but turn serious.

The bell rang, marking the beginning of the fight. However, neither participant made a move. They knew that the other party couldn’t be taken lightly, so they were very careful.

Both of Xiong Li’s hammers were already in his hands. Streep had also setup a defensive formation for himself. But at the moment, none of the two made a move. This caused a deafening silence to descend on the entire stadium.

After five minutes, Xiong Li finally roared and then waved his sledgehammer and sent sword qi towards Streep. Streep was also able to respond quickly. He used a 10-layer formation to meet this attack. The battle had started.

Xiong Li’s attack had been disrupted, but this time he didn’t try to corner Streep like he did with Zhang QInghe. Instead, he sent sword qi at a distance while also minding his defenses.

Streep was also being very careful. He sent 5 and 10-layer formations forward while at the same time he uses formations to protect himself.

The fight between the two was very strange. Nothing happened in the first five minutes, but after Xiong Li moved, everything exploded like dynamite. Both attacked with all of their strength, hoping to end the fight sooner.

Xiong Li’s thunderous attacks were fully unleashed. Each hammer qi was sent over with all of his power. But at this point, Xiong Li began to realize what Zhao Hai said. Streep’s attacks were indeed strange.

He had fought Ice Mages before. Although the spells fired by these Ice Mages were strong, these spells could still be blocked by battle qi. These spells were never a threat.

However, Streep’s magic was different. Even if these spells were blocked by battle qi, there was a slight pinch of cold strands going straight to the opponent’s body. This would cause one to spend some effort to resolve this strands, cutting one’s focus towards attacking.

In the beginning, Xiong Li didn’t care much about these cold strands. He thought that the small amounts wouldn’t do anything to him. But as more of these cold strands enter his body, Xiong Li discovered that they were beginning to wreak havoc inside his body. This caused Xiong Li to waste Battle Qi in order to eradicate these strands.

Xiong Li became more cautious. However, he was slowly falling behind. Streep wasn’t Zhu Chen whose attacks were weak. Whether it be offense or defense, Streep was equally strong in each aspect.

As the fight reached the one hour mark, Zhao Hai began to wrinkle his brow. Dongfang Yu and the others’ faces were also quite ugly. Xiong Li was now clearly at a disadvantage. There was no hope for him to win.

If this was a real-life situation, then Xiong Li might use other methods. However, they were forbidden to hurt their enemy in the arena. Because of this, Xiong Li’s hands and feet were essentially tied.

After another hour of battle, Xiong Li discovered that there was no longer any point to this fight. So after thinking about this, he finally stopped and admitted defeat.

Once Xiong Li got down from the arena, Zhao Hai looked at him as he smiled and said, “Boss Xiong, are my suspicions correct?”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “He’s indeed strange, very strange. His attacks has something other than spiritual qi. Other Mages don’t have it. It should be something that doesn’t exist, but it did.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “This Streep certainly experienced a luck encounter. But Boss Xiong, rest assured, I’ll teach him a lesson when we meet later on.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “If it was a real fight, then I might not be afraid of that fellow. But since we’re at the arena, I’m limited by what I can do. This caused him to have an advantage.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. At this time, he was preparing for the next battle. This time, there was no need to draw on who the two participants were. There were only two remaining people, Zhao Hai and Lei Xiaotian.

Half an hour passed in a blink of an eye, and Zhao Hai began walking to the arena. But when Zhao Hai arrived, he discovered that Lei Xiaotian wasn’t there. Zhao Hai waited for several minutes before seeing Lei Xiaotian slowly walking over.

Zhao Hai just calmly waited for Lei Xiatian. Even after he entered the arena and the shields got up, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. He knew that if he got angry now, Lei Xiaotian’s plan would succeed.

When Lei Xiaotian saw that Zhao Hai kept silent and hasn’t made any noise, he couldn’t help but be surprised. However, he still smiled and said, “Zhao Hai, it’s been hard for you to reach this place. How about you admit defeat so that you can avoid losing too badly.”

Zhao Hai looked at Lei Xiatian, unsure if Lei Xiaotian was extremely arrogant or was just overly good-natured. After reaching this point, even if Zhao Hai wasn’t strong, there was no way for him to surrender. Otherwise, it would be hard for him to enter social circles in the Machine Field.

Also, Lei Xiaotian was talking as though he was giving Zhao Hai the privilege to surrender. This caused Zhao Hai to be speechless. Seeing that Zhao Hai remained silent, Lei Xiaotian’s expression turned unhappy. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What? You don’t want to surrender? Don’t give me that expression. I think highly of you so I gave you the opportunity to surrender. If you don’t surrender, I’ll have to be impolite.”

Zhao Hai looked at Lei Xiaotian and said, “Are we close?”

Lei Xiaotian shook his head and said, “We aren’t close.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then he said, “Then did we know each other before? Or do you know Boss Xiong and the others? Do we have any connection with each other?”

Lei Xiaotian didn’t know what Zhao Hai was going for, but he still replied, “What? You want us to be friends? I already told you, we’re not close. I don’t know anybody you know.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, since we’re not close, we’re not friends either. So why do you need to give me face? Is it because you’re not strong enough and just won because others gave you face? So in turn, you want to give face to others? Am I right?”

When Lei Xiaotian heard Zhao Hai, his face couldn’t help but turn red. Then he said, “Dogfart! This Lei Xiaotian ascended when he is 20 years old. And I reached level 4 in just three years. My talent has been widely recognized in the Machine Field. I don’t need to give others face. Alright, since you don’t accept my goodwill, then excuse me for being impolite. You don’t know how fierce this Lei Xiaotian could get.”

After he said that, Lei Xiaotian waved his hand and released a 10-layer formation that shot ice arrows towards Zhao Hai. These arrows were very fast, evidently passing through a wind element formation.

Zhao Hai didn’t really care about it as he smiled and then waved his hand, releasing a 5-layer formation. This formation turned into a shield that protected his body, keeping the ice arrows off.

After the shield appeared, Zhao Hai waved his hand once more, releasing a 10-layer formation that produced a fire dragon that went straight towards Lei Xiaotian.

Lei Xiaotian coldly snoted, then he released another 10-layer formation that produced a contrasting ice dragon. When the fire and ice dragons met, it looked like a real fight between two dragons as they bit and clawed each other.

After Zhao Hai launched his fire dragon, he immediately sent his ten thousand fiery arrows towards Lei Xiaotian. Lei Xiaotian was somewhat startled. Now that the fire and ice dragon were in a dogfight, they demanded strict control over them. Lei Xiaotian’s ice dragon also needed all of his spiritual force to control it. There simply was not enough spare spiritual force to release another spell. And now, Zhao Hai actually sent another spell. This only meant that Zhao Hai was stronger than Lei Xiaotian.

With this thought in mind, Lei Xiaotian’s expression couldn’t help but turn ugly. He had been called a genius ever since he was very little. This caused an arrogant and conceited attitude to bloom inside him. Now that he saw someone more talented than him, how could he easily accept it?

Lei Xiaotian immediately let go of his control over the ice dragon. Then he quickly released a 10-layer formation that exploded and transformed into five huge ice shields, guarding Lei Xiaotian in all directions. And right after this, Lei Xiatian was heard muttering an incantation as well as making hand gestures. He was planning to unleash advance level magic.

Zhao Hai looked at this and just smiled. Then he waved his hand, releasing another 10-layer formation. A huge ice cone flew out of the formation. Then soon after the ice cone materialized, winds surrounded it causing it to spin like a giant drill bit. Zhao Hai waved his hand again, causing the ice drill to head straight towards Lei Xiaotian.

Lei Xiaotian’s ice shields soon met with the drill. However, the drill just paused for a moment before it punched a hole through Lei Xiaotian’s shield and then shot towards its target.

Lei Xiaotian, who was still making hand gestures, was taken aback. He immediately stopped casting his spell as he retreated. But at this moment, he suddenly felt heat coming from behind him.

Chapter 1192: Defeating the Genius

When Lei Xiaotian felt the heat on his back, he couldn’t help but get startled. Then he turned his head to see the fire dragon that had fought against his ice dragon. He didn’t notice it going behind him and was now opening its mouth to wait for him to come over.

As soon as Lei Xiaotian stopped, the ice cone immediately appeared in front of him. Lei Xiaotian could already feel the coldness on his face. Ice and fire on both directions, he was in a dilemma.

Lei Xiaotian knew that he had already lost. He didn’t think Zhao Hai could still control his fire dragon in this scenario. Although Lei Xiaotian didn’t see how the fire dragon went behind him, he was sure that the fire dragon moved right after he extinguished his ice dragon. This only meant that Zhao Hai could control three spells at the same time!

Lei Xiaotian’s thought was correct, Zhao Hai could in fact maintain three spells at the same time. In fact, Zhao Hai can maintain more than three. It was just that using three spells was enough for Lei Xiaotian.

When Lei Xiaotian gave up control over his ice dragon, Zhao Hai continued controlling his fire dragon and had it go behind Lei Xiaotian. This was done while Lei Xiaotian was casting his spells, so he wasn’t paying attention to the fire dragon. Because of this, Lei Xiaotian was successfully trapped by Zhao Hai.

Even if Lei Xiaotian didn’t admit his defeat, it was already clear that Zhao Hai had won. Therefore, Zhao Hai withdrew his ice cone as well as fire dragon. The referee also declared that it was Zhao Hai’s win.

Lei Xiaotian had a difficult expression as he was looking at Zhao Hai. He didn’t expect to lose this match. To be honest, he didn’t look down on Zhao Hai nor did he despise him. The reality was because he was jealous of Zhao Hai.

Lei Xiaotian had always been called a genius, some even tell him that he was a genius among geniuses. But compared to Zhao Hai, Lei Xiaotian was nothing. Ascending less than one year ago but already managed to reach level 4. Lei Xiaotian took three years to attain this achievement.

His jealousy towards Zhao Hai caused Lei Xiaotian to wear an arrogant appearance before the battle. The reason for this has something to do with his character as well as his intent to make Zhao Hai lose to him in front of many people. This way, he could prove that he was the most talented among the beginners.

Although he had seen Zhao Hai’s previous battles, he still believed that Zhao Hai couldn’t match him. But now, not only did Zhao Hai defeat him, Zhao Hai managed to do so without much difficulty and in less than 20 minutes!

Even compared to the battles for the top 25, a fight lasting less than 20 minutes was still considered short. Let alone in the semifinals, 20 minutes was too short. Lei Xiaotian could almost feel the sky falling down on him.

Zhao Hai noticed Lei Xiaotian’s reaction, but he didn’t have the mood to comfort him at this time. He wasn’t related to Lei Xiaotian and both of them didn’t have any connections to speak of. There was no need for Zhao Hai to be charitable. So after the result was announced, Zhao Hai just walked off the arena.

Upon returning to where Xiong Li and the others were, Xiong Li gave Zhao Hai a large hug as he laughed and said, “Good job kid. That was beautiful. This is the shortest semifinals I have seen. Hahaha.”

Dongfang Yu also laughed and said, “I also didn’t expect the fight to be this short. That was beautiful Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s nothing. Maybe it’s just because Lei Xiaotian didn’t take me seriously. But Boss Xiong, you’re going to fight Lei Xiaotian next. I haven’t fully tested his abilities so you need to be careful.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “Rest assured, I’ll win.”

Dongfang Yu and the others smiled. They didn’t leave the stadium yet since the battle for the 3rd and 4th position would happen soon. Lei Xiaotian and Xiong Li would fight after half an hour of recovery. As for the finals, it would be held the next day.

Half an hour quickly went past. Xiong Li already arrived on the arena but Lei Xiaotian seems to be taking his time. But it was obvious that Lei Xiaotian wasn’t being intentionally late this time. Instead, he had yet to recover from his loss. His thoughts were still mixed up.

The bell rang and Xiong Li and Lei Xiaotian’s battle began. However, Lei Xiaotian’s actions seem to be limited by something, making him use only sixty percent of his true power. This allowed Xiong Li to win the battle.

To be honest, Lei Xiaotian’s level wasn’t just this. His confidence had been seriously damaged when he was defeated by Zhao Hai. This caused him to behave abnormally. Otherwise, Xiong Li wouldn’t have won this easily. After all, Lei Xiaotian was a Mage of two elements.

Now that Xiong Li and Lei Xiaotian’s battle was done, the qualifiers was nearing its end. The next day, the last battle of the competition would happen, Zhao Hai versus Streep. This was a battle between the Machine Field’s most powerful beginner and the qualifier’s dark horse. Everyone had their own guess as to who would end up winning in the end.

In the eyes of the Machine Field’s people, even if Zhao Hai had been performing well, it would still take some time for him to surpass Streep. Zhao Hai finished his battles in a relaxed manner and he didn’t use any items. However, Streep was the same, he had yet to use any items. Moreover, Streep managed to easily defeat his opponents, the only exception was his fight with Xiong Li where he exerted a bit of effort. But nevertheless, Streep managed to breeze through the qualifiers.

Now that the two were going to meet, it would be a battle between a dragon and a tiger. Although Zhao Hai had gained a lot of supporters, there were a lot more people who were rooting for Streep.

Since Zhao Hai could see that Streep’s attacks weren’t ordinary, other people could naturally see it as well. One shouldn’t underestimate the people from the Machine Field, they weren’t fools. All who had some knowledge could see that Streep’s attacks were different compared to others. And just like Zhao Hai, all of them were thinking that Streep managed to have a lucky encounter.

The next day quickly arrived. Since it was the last and most important day of the qualifiers, there were even more people in the stadium. There were also some honored and distinguished people who came to watch the battle. Cadjo and Desbarres were naturally present. Besides the two, Luke and Margaret were in the stands. The group all had smiles on their faces, they didn’t have any trace of worry at all.

In fact, the progress that Zhao Hai made was satisfactory enough. Even if Zhao Hai was defeated, they wouldn’t be disappointed. After all, the progress that Zhao Hai made was Ashley Family’s best record.

Zhao Hai’s placement would give the Ashley Family a huge benefit. They could use Zhao Hai’s progress to develop the family as well as gain new allies. Being able to draw the Fire Temple, Wu Family, and the Yan Family was already enough to offset being enemies with the Zhang Family.

Because of this, Cadjo and the others were in a very happy mood, causing them to have wide smile whenever they meet people they were acquainted with. These acquaintances were also smiling whenever they meet the Ashley Family. Even if they weren’t that close, they would still say a few good words.

The Machine Field’s people were practical. The Ashley Family would receive great benefits and could share it with other people. With the Ashley Family’s foundation, they would use these benefits to develop the family as well as their relationships. It was a good time to establish a good relationship with the Ashley Family.

Time quickly went past and it was already nine o’clock. The bell of the stadium rang, making everyone settle themselves down. Zhao Hai didn’t move and just stayed in his seat. The match was scheduled for ten o’clock so there was still an hour left. This hour would be used to prepare for his battle with Streep. But since they couldn’t just make people wait in the stadium, there would be performances to pad out the time.

This would be Zhao Hai’s first time seeing live artistic performances in the Machine Field. There were a lot of performances set up. There were dances, songs, and even theatrical shows. All of these performers learned martial arts. Their moves were very delicately arranged and there were even Mages at the side to assist in making gorgeous and beautiful magical visuals in the background.

Since Zhao Hai didn’t need to prepare anything, he just used this one hour to enjoy the performances. He was quite relaxed. Terry was also very relaxed. The two weren’t tensed, making everyone else feel awkward.

Before long, the bell rang once more. The performances stopped. Zhao Hai looked at the time and it was ten minutes before the battle. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Streep. Streep was calmly sitting in place while talking to another person. There was no anxiety seen on his face at all.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he could understand why Streep was so confident. Streep’s attacks contain a special energy, this would no doubt give anyone confidence in winning. Streep must have thought that nobody would be able to defeat him at this level. So even if Zhao Hai was strong, Streep still believed that he would win.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh deep inside. He was afraid that he might kill Streep if he used his astral qi. Zhao Hai believed that his astral qi was stronger than Streep’s unknown energy.

The reason for Zhao Hai’s confidence was the results of his analysis. He asked Xiong Li in detail regarding his battle with Streep. And after running the information through the Space’s Scanner, Zhao Hai reached this conclusion.

From the Space’s analysis, Streep’s unknown energy should be a variant similar to evil qi. However, his energy wasn’t as strong as evil qi. He could increase the energy he could send by increasing the frequency of his attacks. However, this increment couldn’t be large, which made it worse than evil qi or astral qi.

Because of this conclusion, Zhao Hai could rest assured. He didn’t want to exert too much strength in dealing with Streep. Zhao Hai wanted to hide his trump cards as much as possible.

Chapter 1193: A Huge Move

Clang!

After a melodious ring, Zhao Hai and Streep proceeded towards the arena.

Once the two were on the arena, the shields went up. The two stood opposite of each other 100 meters away.

Terry, with his everpresent confident smile, looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, I have known about you all this time. Being able to compare notes with you at this moment is truly an honor.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then returned the greeting as he said, “Mister Streep is too polite. I’ve long admired the person in the first place among the Ten Great Experts. I’m very lucky to be able to exchange one or two spells with you.”

If one just looks at them, they wouldn’t look like two people who were going to fight. Instead, they looked like two friends who liked each other and were having a nice discussion.

Naturally, none of the two believed what the other said. Those who took the other party’s words seriously were certainly fools. At this time, the bell rang, signifying the start of the realm qualifier’s finals.

As soon as he heard the bell, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Mister Streep, the battle has begun. Excuse me for being impolite. I’ll be making my move first.”

Although Zhao Hai was talking to Streep, his defense didn’t relax at all. He had an uncomfortable feeling towards Streep.

Despite Streep’s nice and polite way of talking, Zhao Hai never had the inclination to be friends with him. This was due to the uncomfortable feeling that he had been experiencing all this time. It always told him to stay far away from Streep.

Streep was also quite stunned by Zhao Hai. Actually, he was paying attention to Zhao Hai in the past few days. Zhao Hai had formidable strength even with him having ascended less than a year ago. In that short time, he was able to become a level 4 Mage. Moreover, he managed to succeed in pursuing the Ashley Family’s young miss, making it possible for him to become a core member of the family. Most importantly, in just a very short time, he was able to become friends with Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, Sun Fei, and even Li Kuangren. It was clear that Zhao Hai was an extremely skilled person.

And such a person was talking polite towards him, which made Streep’s heart even more cautious.

So upon hearing Zhao Hai, Streep stared. Then his expression turned serious as he said, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. We’ll have to exchange blows eventually. Please proceed.”

Zhao Hai looked at Streep’s eyes, then he smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then allow me to be impolite.” Then Zhao Hai made his move and released a 5-layer formation that sent out a fire dragon towards Streep.

Streep looked at Zhao Hai’s attack and then moved his hand to release a 10-layer formation. This formation appeared to be a huge machine gun. It sent out a barrage of ice cones towards the approaching fire dragon.

Naturally, Streep knew about Zhao Hai’s multicasting abilities. He knew that if he used an ice dragon to combat the fire dragon, then he would only be the one losing the exchange. Therefore he changed his battle plan and decided to just shoot ice cones towards the fire dragon. It was much easier to cast and operate. He would just adjust the direction in order to deal with Zhao Hai’s fire dragon. This was the best way to deal with this situation.

When Zhao Hai saw Streep’s response, his eyes couldn’t help but light up. Then he waved his hand and released his ten thousand fiery arrows. At this point, his fire dragon had already been shot down by Streep’s ice cones.

When Streep saw Zhao Hai’s ten thousand fiery arrows, he immediately erected a giant 10-layer formation ice shield in front of him. This managed to keep Zhao Hai’s arrows at bay.

But this time, Zhao Hai’s attack turned more violent. He used two offensive spells at the same time to attack Streep. However, Streep wasn’t just any other Mage. After he blocked Zhao Hai’s ten thousand fiery arrows, he immediately countered.

It must be said that Streep’s spiritual force was very formidable. And since the ice shield was just there, he spend little to no effort to maintain it. This allowed Streep to use another magic with ease.

Streep had naturally realized that Zhao Hai was a severe threat. He wanted to deal with Zhao Hai as soon as possible. Because of this, while he supported his ice shield, he muttered an incantation while performing hand seals. His seals were very quick and before long he had completed his incantation. Streep pointed towards Zhao Hai and said, “Extreme Cold, Permafrost, Bind!”

Right after Streep said that, the entire arena was suddenly shrouded with white fog. This white fog was quite overbearing. Everything that was touched by this fog was immediately turned into ice. The arena was no exception.

One must know that Streep’s Extreme Cold, Permafrost spell was a 100-layer formation. It was certainly very formidable.

 Zhao Hai saw this and knew that the spell was powerful. His waved both of his hands and then released 10-layer formation fire dragons from both of them. Lifelike dragons emerged from the formations. But this time, they didn’t attack Streep. Instead, they circled Zhao Hai and revolved around him.

Streep saw this and couldn’t help but smile. He believed that his spell wasn’t that easy to break. This spell wasn’t only a level 4 formation with hundreds of layers, it also had a lot of yin energy added to it.

This yin energy was Streep’s biggest trump card. He depended on this energy to become the first of the Ten Great Experts. If not for this yin energy, then he wouldn’t even be able to become one of the Ten Great Experts.

Just like what Zhao Hai saw, even if Streep was a genius, his talent still fell short compared to Lei Xiaotian and Xiong Li. His formations were very common even if he was able to obtain secret formation sets. But after yin energy was added to these formations, their attacking power greatly increased. This allowed Streep to be very powerful among the beginners.

Ever since he discovered the uses of yin energy, Streep continued to collect it all these years. And as he collected more and more yin energy, his magic formations became stronger and stronger. And in the past two years, no Mage nor Warrior of his generation were able to match him. Because of this, he became very confident in his spells. Be believed that Zhao Hai’s fire dragons would never be able to hold the Permafrost spell back.

But much to Streep’s surprise, after the white mist got in contact with the fire dragons, it began to dissipate. Although the fire dragons got smaller in the process, they still managed to hold off against the permafrost spell.

Upon seeing this outcome, Streep’s eyes became round. This was the first time he saw someone block his permafrost spell using a ten-layer formation. One must know that whenever fire magic was used to fight against permafrost in the past, both the fire spell as well as its user would be frozen. This was the first time where the permafrost was blocked by a fire element spell.

After releasing more than ten fire dragons, Zhao Hai stopped. Then he began whispering incantations and then making had seals.

Actually, Zhao Hai’s actions were just for show. He didn’t need to mutter any incantations nor do any had seals. This was because the formations had already been recorded by the Space, he could use them whenever he wants.

However, he needed people to see that he was still casting spells and doing hand gestures. Otherwise, people would probably turn crazy knowing that he could cast hundred or thousand layered formation sets instantaneously. How long has it been since Zhao Hai ascended? Being able to reach level 4 for in less than a year was already monstrous enough. If he shows that he could release a 1000-layer formation instantaneously, he would no longer be seen as a monstrous talent, he would be seen as a monster.

After whispering and making hand gestures for some time, Zhao Hai proceeded to release his magic, “Wind breathes fire, fire rides the wind, Raging Inferno, Burn!”

Along with Zhao Hai’s declaration, fire began to shoot up into the sky. Then with him as the center, a fiery tornado appeared. The winds helped the fire to turn intense almost instantly. The tornado swallowed the fire dragons in before heading towards Streep’s location.

The permafrost spell launched by Streep was broken the instant the fire tornado came into being. When Streep saw this, his expression couldn’t help but change. He quickly waved his hand and muttered some words. Before long, a more than 100-layer formation appeared in front of him as he said, “Ice as the body and water as blood, Ice Dragon, roar!’

When Streep’s voice fell, the formation consisting of hundreds of layers in front of him suddenly shook as a dragon roar was heard. Then a huge blue being came out of the formation. It was a giant dragon with a height of 100 zhang(333m). When the dragon appeared, it immediately clashed with Zhao Hai’s fire tornado.

Boom!

The entire arena shook. Meanwhile, the shields surrounding it began to develop cracks. It looks like it would split at any moment.

When the referee saw this, he was greatly surprised. Then he immediately called over several Mages in order to repair the shield. This allowed the shield to stabilize and not break.

But due to the large explosion, the inside of the arena became hazy. Nobody could see what was going on inside. However, there weren’t any sounds of fighting heard, which made people feel relieved.

Although the sound of the explosion was very loud, the spells used by the two participants were very dazzling. This caused the spectators to cheer.

Even after seeing the arena’s shield crack, none of them left the area. Instead, their eyes were locked into the battle. Although, nothing could be seen at this time.

Chapter 1194: The Peak

The fog on the arena quickly dissipated and two shadows could be seen. One figure was on the left while the other was on the right. Both were about 100 meters away from each other. It looked like none of them moved from their initial positions.

In fact, this was exactly what happened. Ever since the battle started, the two just sent their magic without moving. This also showed how “evenly matched” the two were.

After the fog completely dispersed, people could finally see the two combatants. What they saw caused an uproar. This was because the participants on the stage were in completely different states.

Zhao Hai was still calmly standing in place. His robes were in perfect condition. He looked like he didn’t undergo a fight.

On the other hand, Streep looked somewhat in distress. His robes were burnt in a few spots. Moreover, his hair had been burnt. There were black marks on his face. He looked very pitiful in his current appearance.

This was also the reason why the people were in an uproar. This was because most of them thought that Streep was stronger than Zhao Hai. But now, it seems like Zhao Hai was the more powerful one.

Streep was aware of his own situation, and he stared at Zhao Hai with a burning gaze. He had always cared about his image and he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to place him in such a situation. What annoyed him more was the fact that Zhao Hai looked basically untouched.

Streep began to form a hatred towards Zhao Hai. He hated Zhao Hai for embarrassing him. He also hated Zhao Hai for being stronger than him. And lastly, he hated Zhao Hai for defeating him.

However, Streep was also a cunning man. He knew that he could no longer do anything to Zhao Hai in this arena. Therefore, he took a deep breath to calm his mood. Then he bowed and said, “Mister Zhao Hai’s strength is really extraordinary. You have my sincere admiration. I admit defeat.” Then he turned his head to the referee to announce his surrender.

When the referee saw Streep’s signal, he immediately opened the arena’s shield while at the same time announcing the winner, “The Machine Field’s realm qualifier champion is Zhao Hai! Holding second place is Streep!” When the referee announced the result, the stadium was in an uproar. There were a lot of people who were cursing Streep for admitting his defeat. This was because Streep just made them lose a lot of money.

Seeing Streep surrender, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get surprised. Then an intrigued smile bloomed on his face. Naturally, he could see the killing intent in Streep’s eyes. Zhao Hai just didn’t expect Streep to give up this early.

Of course, Zhao Hai wasn’t so naive to believe that Streep would let him off just like that. Streep just decided to endure, so that his retaliation would be bigger. Streep’s revenge would certainly be fierce, he might even be planning on killing Zhao Hai.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of Streep. If Streep really decided to kill him, then that would give him a reason to kill Streep.

When the referee announced that Zhao Hai had officially become the realm qualifier’s champion, the whole stadium immediately resounded with cheerful music. All kinds of magical fireworks flew up into the sky.

Zhao Hai remained standing in the arena as he bowed in all directions. Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t need to do that. But his actions gained him the admiration of the audience. Soon enough, people were standing up to give Zhao Hai applause.

On the reserved seats, Cadjo was wiping away his tears. The Ashley Family will gain a lot from Zhao Hai becoming the champion. And these gains didn’t only come from the tournament’s prize. Since Zhao Hai was the largest dark horse of the qualifiers, Cadjo made use of it to bet on him. After each victory, the Ashley Family’s winnings became bigger and bigger.

Cadjo knew that the Ashley Family’s opportunity to rise up has arrived. The current Ashley Family was too vulnerable. They didn’t have that much territory, manpower, resources, and allies. If they didn’t aim to increase their status at this time, then it would truly be a huge waste.

The awards ceremony came immediately after. There was nothing special about it. The prize they sent Zhao Hai wasn’t to his liking, so they negotiated the entire afternoon before the event formally finished.

Once everything was done, Zhao Hai wanted have a drink with Xiong Li and the others. However, he was stopped by Cadjo and was asked to prepare to attend a party that evening.

Zhao Hai knew that this was something he couldn’t avoid, so he agreed. However, he told Xiong Li and the others that they would be drinking the next day. Then after that, Margaret and Zhao Hai returned to the Ashley Family’s building

When they returned, they immediately went to their room and then entered the Space. Laura and the others welcomed them with happy faces. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Congratulations Brother Hai!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What’s there to congratulate about, it’s just the realm qualifiers. Right, did you monitor Streep’s situation?”

Laura nodded and said, “Rest assured, he’s under surveillance. But this man is really shameless. The moment he returned to his room, he immediately went and looked for a woman.” While Laura said this, her face turned red. It seems like Streep did something that shouldn’t be looked into.

When Zhao Hai heard Laura, he couldn’t help but knit his brows as he said, “He’s looking for a woman? It seems like Streep’s strange energy had something to do with the female gender. Continue paying attention to him. Of course, don’t look at him when he’s with a woman. Otherwise, I’ll be jealous.” Laura and the others twisted Zhao Hai’s sides immediately after he said that. However, Zhao Hai just laughed it out before leading everyone in. After taking a bath, he returned to the living room to see that Laura and the others were doing something.

Zhao Hai went behind them to see what they were doing on the computer. From what he could see, they were designing clothes that would look good for him to wear.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. It must be said that Zhao Hai didn’t care much about what he was wearing. Normally, he would just use his transforming garment that turned into mage robes. This mage robe looked ancient and ordinary. It was just black and not anything special.

However, this didn’t sit well with Laura and the others. In their eyes, Zhao Hai’s fashion sense was very bad. And this time, clothing was very important. He would meet distinguished people in the party so he needed to look special when facing them.

Zhao Hai just smiled and went along with what they were doing. He didn’t want to be the one to take care of this. He usually prioritized comfort when it came to his clothing. But if he were to attend a formal occasion, he needs to wear formal clothes. Otherwise he would lose face.

Zhao Hai sat on one side drinking tea while Laura and the others were discussing about what he should wear. His heart couldn’t help but enter tranquility. This was what he yearns most in life, a life with no disputes.

It can be said that once women discussed clothing, their spirits would reach an astonishing degree. Time passed, two hours, three hours, and they were still discussing. They had already selected one outfit, but they seem to think that there was still something better, so they kept discussing.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. Now that Cadjo was preparing for the party, nobody went to look for him all this time, and they also didn’t want to disturb him. Zhao Hai comfortably changed the Space’s monitor to look at Streep.

At this time Streep was currently practicing. The woman that Laura and the others talked about was no longer there. Actually, Streep wasn’t injured at all, he was just ruffled up. Zhao Hai didn’t dare hurt Streep, or else he would have to give up being first place.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to do such a thing. There were other opportunities to deal with Streep outside of the arena. But while Zhao Ha fought against Streep, he released a very thin silver needle and inserted it into Streep’s scalp. At that time, Streep was so focused on fighting that he didn’t notice pain that was only a bit stronger than a mosquito bite.

Moreover, Zhao Hai’s silver needle can turn soft. So when it pricked Streep’s scalp, it immediately turned soft, disguising itself as white hair.

Streep’s hair was blue, so it was able to hide the silver hair much better. Because of this, Zhao Hai believed that his silver needle wouldn’t be discovered.

After watching Streep, Zhao Hai changed the monitor’s display to the Machine Field’s channels. There were movies, tv series, and news. There were a lot of content to watch.

Upon seeing the content of the news, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This was because it was currently showing the awarding ceremony. He was there bowing to the audience.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he looked at himself turning to face the audience. But this time, Laura suddenly shouted, “Brother Hai, turn the volume up. We want to hear what they are saying.”

Zhao Hai turned his head and saw that Laura and the others were also watching the news. Their eyes turned bright upon seeing him in the monitor.

Zhao Hai smiled and then waved his hand to increase the volume of the television. “Zhao Hai ascended less than a year ago but he has already become a level 4 Mage. He’s a genius in cultivation and through his indisputable strength, he managed to get the first place in the Machine Field’s qualifiers. He is the Machine Field’s pride, the might of the realm……”

Hearing these praises, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He didn’t expect the Machine Field’s television program to be so polite while talking about him.

Laura and the others were looking at the monitor with great interest. But after hearing the discussion for some time, they finally got bored. Zhao Hai looked at them and then said, “Are you done picking what I should wear?”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and the others immediately took out a laptop and then faced it towards Zhao Hai. Of the thousands of clothes present, they were finally able to settle on one.

Zhao Hai inspected the clothing. It was a black robe with silver embroidery. It was gorgeous but not flamboyant. Moreover, its style was different than normal mage robes. Inside was a long gown that was like a robe but was divided into a top and a bottom. It was covered by a buttonless robe that had a sort of windbreaker. It looked very charming.

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “That looks very good. Margaret, how about you? It’s a party to celebrate my win, so it’s natural that you’re going to be my female companion.”

Margaret smiled and said, “I’ll be wearing this.” Then she showed her dress. It was also a black mage robe with silver embroidery on the upper part. Its style was very novel and attractive.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. It’s a pity that you can’t go out in public yet. Otherwise, I’ll be taking all of you outside. People will surely envy me to death.” Zhao Hai looked at the other clothes on the computer as he smiled towards Laura and the others.

When she heard this, Laura smiled and said, “It’s fine. There will be time later on. Brother Hai, you should prepare. The party is happening soon.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he changed the image on the monitor to Cadjo and the others. The party would be held in the large hall of the Ashley Family’s building. This place was big enough to host a party. The preparations were already complete, only some finishing touches were being done.

Zhao Hai looked at the time and said, “Alright, I think I need to leave. Boss Xiong and the others will be arriving soon. It’s possible that they’ll look for me first.” Then at this time, Zhao Hai saw Xiong Li and the others walking over. Zhao Hai and Margaret left the Space. Zhao Hai’s robe already changed to the design they decided on. As for Margaret, her robe was still being made by the Processing Machine. Laura and the others would send it to her in her room.

As for other things like jewelry and makeup, everything had already been taken care of. Margaret’s hair didn’t need to much work since her natural hair already matched her robes. And after all, Zhao Hai was the star of the party.

After coming out of the Space, Zhao Hai immediately opened the door to his room. Xiong Li and the others were already waiting outside. Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, and Li Kuangren all changed into new Warrior clothing. Xiong Li also made an exception and put away his huge hammers. Sun Fei was also wearing new mage robes which made him look quite handsome.

When the group saw Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but stare. Zhao Hai’s robes were very well-designed. It gave him a noble and charming aura. And at the same time, it gave people a bright feeling towards him.

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Little Hai, good, good. I didn’t expect you to know how to dress well. You look like another person. You look very good. How could a kid like you look so charming?”

Upon hearing this, Dongfang Yu and the others laughed!

Chapter 1195: Viper Ba Dong

The night silently came. However, Machine Field Planet was a planet that never sleeps. The planet’s night life was very rich. This was even more so today since the qualifiers just ended. Families held parties to commemorate their achievements. And the most eye-catching party of them all was of course hosted by the Ashley Family.

The Ashley Family wasn’t considered to be that big of a family in the Machine Field. Before this, it can be said that their name was unknown in the vast territory of the realm.

Although the Ashley Family was in good terms with other families before, these families were just medium to small-sized families. They weren’t that influential in the Machine Field.

In the past, whenever the Ashley Family held parties and sent written invitations to powerful families, they didn’t even expect them to respond. Those who participated in their parties were those from medium-small sized families who they had good terms with. Moreover, besides those who they have a really good relationship, the other families would just send in representatives to attend, they didn’t place great importance to the party.

However, this time, it was different. Now that Zhao Hai had gained first place in the realm qualifiers and brought the Ashley Family great benefits, the great families of the Machine Field had to give them face. This was because everyone knew that the Ashley Family was on the path to becoming powerful. Having the Ashley Family as a friend was much better than being their enemy.

Because of this, a lot of people expressed their desire to attend the Ashley Family’s party. In the parking lot of the Ashley Family’s building were a lot of cars passing in and out. There were men and women dressed in their best attire holding crystal glasses and drinking wine inside the building’s lobby. Once in a while, women’s laughter could be heard in the halls.

The melodious music as well as the light breeze that sent coldness to everyone, and also the absence of the sweltering heat of the day, made those present very comfortable.

Cadjo shuttled back and forth in the crowd to meet and talk with people he was both familiar and unfamiliar with. Desbarres and Luke were the same. At this time, the three of them were the faces of the Ashley Family.

Xiong Li’s group of four were standing in the lawn. Xiong Li looked around him and then snorted as he said, “I hate these kinds of parties the most. These are just people wearing masks and talking nonsense. It’s very boring.”

Li Kuangren nodded and said, “Right, you can see that their laughs and smiles are all fake. It’s better if we take Brother Zhao Hai out and then have some drinks and meat ourselves.”

Donfang Yu looked at them and then he smiled and said, “Alright, stop complaining. It’s already very good that we managed to attend this kind of party. Look at everyone here, some are from powerful influences, there are also honored and famous people here. It’s only because of our relationship with Little Hai that the Ashley Family gave us invitations to this party. Do you really think these kinds of parties would invite people from External Halls like us?”

Sun Fei nodded and said, “Boss Xiong, don’t be too sad. Also, we can use this as an excuse to take Brother Hai out drinking later.”

Upon hearing Sun Fei, Xiong Li stared for a moment, then he said, “Right, we can do that. I like that plan. Then it’s decided!”

The group laughed, causing them to attract attention. However, the looks directed at them had despise mixed in. It was clear that the natives of the Machine Field were still looking down on ascenders.

Xiong Li and the others didn’t care about it. They were people who could summon wind and rain back in the lower realms, they had seen everything. Even if their status in the Machine Field wasn’t as good as back in the lower realms, they were still geniuses that were highly valued in their respective External Halls. They wouldn’t care about minor matters like these.

At this time, the clock struck eight. Those who were going to come had already arrived. It was also at this time that Zhao Hai and Margaret showed themselves to the guests.

When the two appeared, they immediately attracted the attention of everyone present. Zhao Hai and Margaret were both wearing black robes that weren’t too showy. However, one could see that these robes were specially made. There were places that were unique compared to other robes. Most importantly, the designs of the two robes were specially made so that when they stood together, their clothes would blend in with each other. At this point, even blind people could see that they were a couple.

Seeing Zhao Hai come out, everyone came to give him their greetings. Zhao Hai also received each person with great politeness. And to everyone’s surprise, Zhao Hai was able to say their names casually as if they had met before.

Achieving this feat wasn’t easy. This was because everyone present here could affirm that this was their first meeting with Zhao Hai. And when the Ashley Family handed over their invitations, their families didn’t even say who would be coming. In other words, Zhao Hai being able to know who they were was very remarkable.

Zhao Hai had participated in a lot of parties back in the lower realms. Although the environment has changed, the courtesy needed for such events didn’t change much. Therefore, Zhao Hai was able to comfortably conduct himself well in this situation.

Although this party was held to celebrate his victory, Zhao Hai knew that he was just an expert of the Ashley Family at this time. If it wasn’t for giving the Ashley Family some face, then these people wouldn’t have been enthusiastic in meeting him.

This party’s star was Zhao Hai, but the truth was actually different. He was only the face of the party. This party was a ground for powerful and influential people to mingle with themselves in both an open and covert way. Zhao Hai’s purpose in this party was no different than a vase being used as decoration.

After greeting everyone that needed greeting, Zhao Hai led Margaret towards where Xiong Li and the others were. Seeing the two arrive, Xiong Li smiled and said, “Little Hai, I didn’t expect you to be this experienced in dealing with people. Did you attend a lot of parties before?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I had time to attend these parties before. In fact, the parties are the same each time. As long as you participate in one, you’ll know what to do the next time.” Xiong Li couldn’t help but laugh. Like Zhao Hai, he had attended parties before, so he knew what Zhao Hai was talking about.

The group proceeded to talk amongst each other. On the other hand, more and more people went to talk to Cadjo. After all, those who came here knew that Cadjo was someone that held the trust of the Ashley Family’s Patriarch. Moreover, he was a very powerful character. The true star of the party was actually him.

Zhao Hai knew about this, so after giving his greetings, he took Margaret with him and then went to where Xiong Li and the others were. He didn’t try to approach any guest and try to build a relationship with them.

Time passed in a moderate manner in this event. Unknowingly, it was already 9 o’clock. At this point, Cadjo had established cooperative relationships with some families. It can be said that he had received a bountiful harvest.

At this time, a blue light was seen from a distant place and before long it arrived at the Ashley Family’s parking lot. When Cadjo saw this blue light, his expression couldn’t help but change. This was because he recognized this blue light. In the Machine Field, only one group had this specific blue light in their vehicles, it was the Water Temple..

The Water Temple was one of the top powers of the Mage Alliance. The power that they held was much more than the Ashley Family.

Originally, the Water Temple had no enmity with the Ashley Family. Sending someone to this party was equal to the Temple’s support of the Ashley Family. Cadjo should be happy about this.

However, one shouldn’t forget that Streep was someone from the Water Temple. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then Streep might have gained first place. But now, Streep has been defeated by Zhao Hai. This was akin to the Ashley Family having developed enmity with the Water Temple.

Naturally, not wanting to offend the Temple, Cadjo was polite and sent an invitation. However, the Temple didn’t send a response. This caused Cadjo to think that nobody from the Temple was coming. But now, an hour into the party, the Water Temple suddenly arrived. This caused Cadjo to think about the possible reasons why.

When the car stopped, the door opened and two people came out. Upon seeing who came, the eyes of those present couldn’t help but shrink. This was because they didn’t know who the other person was. Moreover, this unknown person wasn’t wearing clothes normally worn in the Machine Field. Instead, the man was dressed as though he was from the Cultivation Realm.

Cadjo believed his own judgement. He knew that those from the Cultivation Realm didn’t just dress differently than those in the Machine Field. They also carried themselves differently. Even if someone from the Machine Field wore clothes from the Cultivation Realm, they still wouldn’t be able to gain the Cultivation Realm’s special temperament.

As for the other person, Cadjo know him very well. This was the reason why Cadjo’s heart jumped. This person was a Bishop from the Water Temple. He was named Ba Dong. However, this Ba Dong had a nickname, Viper!

Viper Ba Dong. Upon hearing this nickname, one would have an idea as to what kind of person he was. Just like his nickname, Ba Dong was as venomous as a snake. As long as someone enters his sights, they wouldn’t have any lucky day. When this person decides to be vicious, nothing would stop him from chasing after his enemy. He was a very hard to deal with character.

It can be said that Cadjo wouldn’t be nervous if any other person from the Water Temple came. But after seeing Ba Dong, Dadjo’s heart couldn’t help but tighten up. However, he still took a step forward. When he was a couple of meters away from Ba Dong, Cajo laughed and said, “I didn’t expect Bishop Ba Dong to actually come. My Ashley Family is incredibly honored. This Cadjo expresses his gratitude.”

Ba Dong was tall, dark, and thin. He had no redeeming qualities. But once you look at his eyes, your body would no doubt turn uncomfortable. You could see a hint of coldness in his eyes, it was as though you were staring right into the eyes of a snake!

Chapter 1196: Skyfrost Sword Li Chuchen

Ba Dong looked at Cadjo and slightly nodded as he said, “Cadjo, congratulations on your achievement. Right, let me introduce you to this talented gentleman. This is Li Chuchen from Extreme Cold City of the Cultivation Realm. He’s also going to participate in the 6 Realm Beginner Competition. In the Cultivation Realm’s qualifiers, he managed to get the tenth place.”

Ba Dong saying that Li Chuchen was just 10th place wasn’t an insult, but actually a compliment. Becoming tenth place in the Cultivation Realm was much more significant than being first in the Machine Field. It must be said that it was extremely rare for a tenth placer in one realm to be equal to a tenth place to other realms.

Cadjo immediately felt angry due to Ba Dong talking to him like he was talking to a junior, but after hearing Ba Dong’s introduction, Cadjo couldn’t help but dissipate his anger.

Although the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm occasionally had friction, the two realms weren’t without communication. And even if these exchanges were far and few in between, the Cultivation Realm always had the upper position during these events. They always took the lead.

And since the Six Realm Beginner Competition was about to begin, everyone began getting information about the talented newcomers from the Cultivation Realm. And Li Chuchen’s name was one of the names being passed around.

A genius named Li Chuchen, nicknamed Skyfrost sword, ascended into Extreme Cold City four years ago. Although it has only been four years since he ascended, he was now a Foundation Establishment cultivator. Moreover, he was granted an advanced-grade magic treasure by the Extreme Cold City’s City Lord, an item named the Skyfrost sword. Li Chuchen relied on this sword to slowly increase his reputation.

Extreme Cold City wasn’t an unknown force in the Cultivation Realm, it was one of the more influential sects. Its disciples reached 10 million in number. Their Inner Disciples numbered 1 million and their Core Disciples were about 10 thousand. Including their Elders and other resident experts, they were no doubt one of the more powerful sects in the Cultivation Realm.

One shouldn’t look down on Extreme Cold City’s 10 thousand Core Disciples. Although they were few, they were very strong. The Cultivation Realm’s Core Disciples were in a completely different level compared to the Machine Field’s Core Members.

Most Core Members in the Machine Field were people from the families themselves. It didn’t matter if they were strong or talented, as long as they were from the family’s direct lineage or members from extended families, they were allowed to become core members. Because of this system of not attaching great importance to a person’s talent, the core faction of some families were very weak.

But the Cultivation Realm was different. In the Cultivation Realm, everyone spoke with their strength. Before becoming Foundation Establishment, cultivators would be in the Outer Sect. Only once they reach Foundation Establishment would someone become part of the Inner Sect. If one could become Gold Core Experts, then they would become Core Disciples. They would then have enough strength to face one Machine Field fleet.

As for Li Chuchen, he was able to reach Foundation Establishment and enter the Inner Sect only four years after ascending. This in itself was a great accomplishment. He was a rare genius.

Because of this, even if Li Chuchen was only in tenth place in the qualifiers, Cadjo didn’t dare underestimate him. He immediately gave Li Chuchen a bow as he said, “So it is Young Hero Li. This Cadjo has been disrespectful. I didn’t expect Young Hero Li to visit our Ashley Family. It’s truly an honor to have you visit.”

Li Chuchen didn’t give Cadjo even a little bit of face. He just snorted and said, “I heard that a genius has popped up from your family and became the champion of your qualifiers. Hahaha. The Machine Field has been getting more and more absurd. Hahahaha. Someone who ascended less than a year ago actually became the realm champion. You still have the face to host a party? Don’t you think it’s ridiculous?”

Upon hearing Li Chuchen, Cadjo’s face immediately turned ugly. Then he turned to Ba Dong and saw him just smiling and staying silent.

Cadjo wasn’t actually angry because of Li Chuchen’s arrogance. The Cultivators had always been like this. The reason Cadjo was angry was because Li Chuchen seemed discontented with Zhao Hai’s achievement. If this was really the case, then he might challenge Zhao Hai. This would put Zhao Hai in danger.

When he thought of this, Cadjo couldn’t help but get angry at the Water Temple even more. He didn’t expect the Water Temple to be this malicious. Zhao Hai could use his strength to fight for the Machine Field in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. However, the Water Temple actually wanted to cut Zhao Hai’s path prematurely. This was absolutely a shortsighted plot that didn’t think about the bigger picture.

Although he was seething, Cadjo didn’t dare show his anger. He remained polite as he answered Li Chuchen, “Of course, the strength of the Ashley Family can’t enter the eyes of Young Hero Li. However, the Ashley Family hasn’t achieved any decent accomplishments recently, so we couldn’t help but celebrate this one. I apologize for making Young Hero Li laugh.”

This wasn’t because Cadjo was submissive. If this was any other event, he would be impolite towards Li Chuchen. After all, even if Li Chuchen was a disciple of Extreme Cold City, he was still an ascender. Moreover, he’s from the CUltivation Realm. Even if Li Chuchen was offended, he still couldn’t do anything. In the end, this was the Machine Field and he was an outsider.

The reason Cadjo was polite was because he wanted to shift Li Chuchen’s attention so that he wouldn’t challenge Zhao Hai.

Cadjo was an old fox who had been swimming in rivers and lakes for a long time. What he heard from Li Chuchen wasn’t good. Although Li Chuchen was from the Cultivation Realm and that the Cultivators wouldn’t dare to easily wage war with the Machine Field, if Li Chuchen used the excuse of challenge to kill Zhao Hai, then the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to do anything. After all, the Ashley Family couldn’t declare war against Extreme Cold City.

Lu Chuchen wasn’t the fearful one. What was scary was the influence behind him. Extreme Cold City was very powerful. When the time comes, not a lot of people would support the Ashley Family in going against the city. After all, nobody was willing to offend a huge power like Extreme Cold City.

It can be said that the Water Temple’s move was quite ruthless. Since they couldn’t act against Zhao Hai, they used Li Chuchen. If Li Chuchen challenges Zhao Hai, then Zhao Hai would have no choice but to accept. This was the custom in the Machine Field.

The Machine Field had been pressed down by the Cultivation Realm. However, the Machine Field’s people had their own dignity. If a Cultivator killed Zhao Hai, then the Machine Field would certainly make a move. This was because they could claim that the Cultivators were bullying the weak. However, if Zhao Hai was challenged, then Zhao Hai had to agree. If Zhao Hai refuses the challenge, then he would be bringing shame to the Machine Field. Because of this, Zhao Hai had to agree to Li Chuchen’s challenge. The Machine Field would rather have Zhao Hai be killed in a challenge than to have Zhao Hai bring shame to the realm. This was the pride of the Machine Field.

The Water Temple had already settled the event. They wanted Li Chuchen to step forward and challenge Zhao Hai in order to seek revenge. It seems like the Water Temple really wanted to snatch the first place position away from Zhao Hai. The Water Temple didn’t get what they want, so they had to resort to these means.

It was pure coincidence that Li Chuchen, a disciple from the Extreme Cold City and a participant of the Six Realm beginner competition, happened to visit the Water Temple. This was because there was something he needed there, and this thing was called Heavenly Divine Water.

Heavenly Divine Water was also a treasure in the Cultivation Realm. However, the quantity of this item wasn’t a lot. This divine water was very useful for Li Chuchen’s cultivation. Additionally, Li Chuchen was currently in a bottleneck. So he decided to go out for experience and personally get the divine water from the Water Temple.

Heavenly Divine Water was also very important for the Water Temple. However, they wouldn’t deny Li Chuchen’s request. This would make Li Chuchen owe them a favor. And if Li Chuchen gets stronger and achieves great results in the Six Realm Beginner Competition, Extreme Cold City would owe the Water Temple. There was no reason for the temple to refuse Li Chuchen’s request.

Li Chuchen had a similar situation to Lei Xiaotian. He grew up receiving constant praise from others. Therefore, he was very proud. Ba Dong could see this so he brought Li Chuchen to the Ashley Family’s party so that Li Chuchen would challenge Zhao Hai.

Ba Dong also knew that he would bring trouble to the temple by doing this. After all, this was colluding with an outsider to deal with someone from the Machine Field. However, he couldn’t help but do it. He really wanted to kill Zhao Hai.

The reason Ba Dong was like this was because Streep became strong under his tutelage. He paid a great price so that Streep could become strong as soon as possible. Ba Dong did this so that Streep could gain first place in the qualifiers. In turn, Ba Dong’s position in the Temple would increase and maybe he might become an Archbishop of the Water Temple one day.

However, all of his efforts were destroyed by Zhao Hai. Therefore, Ba Dong hated Zhao Hai so much that when he saw Li Chuchen he immediately thought of it as an opportunity. As long as Zhao Hai was removed, then everything else would be worth it.

It was said that a dead genius wasn’t a genius at all. As long as Zhao Hai was dead, the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to do anything in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. It would then be impossible for the Ashley Family to rise up. Meanwhile, Streep would still be alive. And as long as Streep could get a good score in the competition, then the Ashley Family’s allies would turn their heads towards the Water Temple. And Ba Dong wouldn’t be in any trouble!

Chapter 1197: The Covenant of Three Swords

Since he had thought of all of these consequences, Ba Dong decided to have Li Chuchen take action. This explains why he was here.

Although Cadjo wasn’t aware of the thoughts going on inside Ba Dong’s mind, he knew clearly why Ba Dong was here. He was here for Zhao Hai. Because of this, Cadjo had to lower his head in order to shift Li Chuchen’s focus away from Zhao Hai.

At this time, the guests of the party also noticed the conversation between Cadjo and the guests from the Water Temple. All of them looked at Ba Dong with despise. However, it seems Ba Dong didn’t even notice their gazes.

To Ba Dong, this was a path to no return. He didn’t ask Li Chuchen to deal with Zhao Hai. Instead, he took a shot against Zhao Hai’s achievement. Now, even if he stopped Li Chuchen from challenging Zhao Hai, Li Chuchen wouldn’t listen to him.

Cadjo’s plan was good. However, Li Chuchen wasn’t easily deceived. Although Cadjo adopted a low position, this didn’t remove Li Chuchen’s intention to challenge Zhao Hai.

Lu Chuchen snorted and said, “I heard that this Zhao Hai is quite arrogant. I even heard that he’s looking down on Cultivators. I always wanted to compete with the experts of the Machine Field. Since I’m here, I might as well teach him that the world is much more profound than he thinks.”

Upon hearing Li Chuchen, everyone’s vision changed from Ba Dong to Zhao Hai.

Those who came here weren’t fools. All of them knew that Li Chuchen’s presence here was certainly incited by someone. And there was no need to ask as to who this person was, since it was clearly Ba Dong. Ba Dong was from the Water Temple and Zhao Hai just snatched the qualifer’s first place from Streep who was also from the temple.

Everyone felt that Ba Dong’s behaviour was shameless. It was clear that he wanted to kill Zhao Hai. Ba Dong was shameless enough to collude with people outside of Machine Field in order to kill someone from the same realm. However, they had to admit that this plot was quite venomous.

Nobody would reject a challenge in the Machine Field. If you declined, then you would be losing face for the Machine Field and showing weakness to the other realms. Nobody in the Machine Field would want to associate with you anymore. Moreover, all of your benefits would be cancelled and your qualifications for the Six Realm Beginner Competition would be withdrawn.

Because of this, despite everyone looking at Cadjo with despise, people were looking at Zhao Hai in pity. However, there were even more people who looked at Zhao Hai with looks of schadenfreude. It was as if they were looking at someone who was already dead.

As soon as Cadjo heard Li Chuchen, his body slightly shook then his face paled. He knew that he could no longer change the situation.

Not only Cadjo, besides Zhao Hai and Margaret, the faces of Desbarres, Luke, as well as Xiong Li and the others paled in an instant. They all had the same idea as Cadjo, that Zhao Hai was finished.

Zhao Hai naturally knew what was going on, so he took Margaret and went to Cadjo. Then he looked at Li Chuchen as he smiled and said, “Is it Young Hero Li? Hehe. This Zhao Hai is very honored to be able to meet you.”

Li Chuchen looked at Zhao Hai, then he coldly snorted and said, “You’re that arrogant one?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I haven’t said anything like that. It seems like Young Hero Li has misunderstood. I had always been impressed by the power of the Cultivation Realm. And how can I be so stupid to say such a thing? Young Hero Li is smart, you should be able to differentiate between right and wrong. And since this is the case, Young Hero Li should already be careful against villains who use you as a tool for their malicious plans.”

As soon as Li Chuchen heard Zhao Hai, he immediately understood what he meant. He turned to look at Ba Dong and coldly snorted. However, he turned back to Zhao Hai and said, “You’re not worthy of lecturing me. If you don’t want to fight, then just tell it to me straight. This Li Chuchen wouldn’t want to dirty his sword with the blood of a coward.”

When he heard Zhao Hai’s appropriate response, Cadjo couldn’t help but feel hope. However, Li Chuchen’s response quickly extinguished this hope. Cadjo’s face suddenly sank. He didn’t expect Li Chuchen to be this overbearing. Even in such circumstances, he still insisted on going after Zhao Hai.

At the same time, Zhao Hai didn’t expect Li Chuchen to be this unreasonable. His eyes narrowed slightly, then he smiled and said, “Since Young Hero Li wants to do it, then there’s no reason for this Zhao Hai to disagree. Young Hero Li, please decide on a time and a place.”

Lu Chuchen coldly snorted and said, “There’s no need to decide on a time and place if it’s a lesson. We’ll do it now. As long as you can take three of my swords and survive, then I will let you go and wait for you in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. But if you die to my swords, then you’re just getting what you deserve.”

Zhao Hai looked at Li Chuchen’s face, then he smiled and said, “Since that is the case, then allow me to receive the power of the skyfrost sword.”

Li Chuchen coldly snorted, then he waved his hand. A shortsword appeared. It wasn’t very long at only about one meter in length. Both the blade and the handle were white. At the hilt of the sword was a sword knot. It was a sword knot that was similarly white.

The moment this sword appeared, the temperature of the surrounding area immediately dropped. And after some time, the air became icy cold. Li Chuchen confidently smiled as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you ready?”

Zhao Hai looked at the people around them and then he said, “Young Hero Li, there are too many people here. If you and I fight in this place, then innocent people would be affected. How about we find another place?”

Li Chuchen was also aware that the people in the party were distinguished and famous people of the Machine Field. It wouldn’t be good if he injured one of them. So he coldly snorted and said, “Alright, let’s go.” Then he flew up and headed towards a forest nearby.

Machine Field Planet had always been a large planet that was scarcely populated. Therefore, it’s ecological situation was very good. Despite its huge cities, each building was actually at a distance from each other. Some were even separated by several li. Therefore, there were quite a few forests nearby.

This forest wasn’t far away from the Ashley Family’s building. Actually, this forest was purposefully planted by the Ashley Family. It was composed of Incense Trees. The seeds of these trees were known to emit bursts of pleasant scent. This scent wasn’t strong but it can calm someone’s mind. It also had an effect of repelling insects.

The construction cost of this forest wasn’t cheap. However, nobody cared about it right now as Li Chuchen and Zhao Hai flew inside it. Those among the visitors who had the ability to fly took to the skies. As for those who were unable to fly, they got into their vehicles and then hovered at a distance away from the forest.

Xiong Li and the others had ugly faces as they approached the forest. Margaret also went with them. Xiong Li and the others looked at Margaret and discovered that she didn’t seem to be worried at all. This caused them to feel strange. Isn’t Margaret too confident in Zhao Hai?

Li Kuangren couldn’t help but ask Margaret, “Sister-in-law, aren’t you worried about Little Hai? His opponent is a Cultivator from the Cultivation Realm.”

Margaret looked at Li Kuangren, then she smiled and said, “Third Brother, rest assured, Brother Hai will be fine. Have confidence in his abilities. Even if he faced a native from the Cultivation Realm, he still wouldn’t fall.”

Right after Margaret said that a cold snort was suddenly heard at the side. Margaret turned her head to see Ba Dong. Margaret’s eyes couldn’t help but narrow as she quickly ignored him and proceeded forward.

This narrowing of the eyes was Zhao Hai’s habit. He does this whenever he was dissatisfied with something. Margaret seems to have obtained it from him.

Li Kuangren and the others also heard Ba Dong’s cold snort. They all glared at the Water Temple Bishop, but Ba Dong seems to be unable to notice them.

Xiong Li and the others didn’t do anything in retaliation. Even the impulsive Li Kuangren didn’t berate Ba Dong. This was because despite his plots, Ba Dong was still a Bishop of the Water Temple. However, they already took an oath that no matter what the outcome of Zhao Hai’s battle was, they would definitely take revenge against the Water Temple.

Xiong Li and the others haven’t known Zhao Hai for a long time, but most of them were temperamental people. It can be said that it was fate for these brothers to meet. Fate was truly wonderful at times. Although they hadn’t been friends for long, it was like they had been brothers for their entire lives.

For Xiong Li and the others, Zhao Hai was their brother. And now, their brother has been placed in a bad situation. They couldn’t get angry because their strength was still not enough. Because of this, they can only endure.

At this time, Zhao Hai and Li Chuchen had arrived at a spot inside the Incense Tree Forest. They didn’t step on the ground but instead hovered above. The two were separated by a hundred meters.

Li Chuchen looked at the spectators before he tauntingly smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “It looks like your achievements hasn’t been well regarded.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “I only think about what I can deal with. Young Hero Li, please begin.”

Li Chuchen looked at Zhao Hai’s expression before he coldly snorted. He held his skyfrost sword in front of him before he waved it and announced, “Severing the Mountains and Rivers, First Sword!” Along with his declaration, the skyfrost sword increased in size. The originally 1 meter sword became meters long. The sword also got thicker as it extended and cut towards Zhao Hai.

This sword seems like an ordinary chop. However, Zhao Hai knew that this attack wasn’t so simple.

The skyfrost sword chopped down from the sky, its body gently trembling. However, one shouldn’t look down on this gentle shaking. This wasn’t because of Li Chuchen’s lack of control of his sword. On the contrary, Li Chuchen’s mastery of the skyfrost sword was very good. The reason the body trembled was because it was blocking Zhao Hai’s routes of escape. No matter which direction Zhao Hai dodges, the sword would still be able to hit him at the shortest amount of time. It can be said that Zhao Hai would have no other way to deal with this attack other than going at it head on.

When Zhao Hai saw this, his expression changed. Then he waved his hand, taking out a silvery white mage staff. When the spectators saw this staff, they couldn’t help but stare. This was because Zhao Hai never took anything out during the qualifiers. Everyone thought that this was because Zhao Hai had yet to find a staff that was compatible with him. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to actually reveal his staff at this time. This was to say that Zhao Hai hadn’t used his true strength during the competition.

Naturally, the staff that Zhao Hai took out was Liquid Silver. Zhao Hai saw the might of the skyfrost sword and knew that it was impossible for it to be a threat to him. However, if Zhao Hai used his body tempering fist to counter the attack, then he would be showing an important aspect of his strength. Because of this, he chose to take Liquid Silver out instead.

After taking Liquid Silver out, Zhao Hai immediately waved it as a layered formation appeared in front of him. This magic formation set quickly turned into a shield.

At this time, Li Chuchen’s sword chopped down. The huge skyfrost sword carried with it a might that could shake the heavens and the earth. It didn’t take long before it hit Zhao Hai’s hundred-layer formation shield.

Boom! A loud explosion entered everyone’s ears. When the skyfrost sword came down, everyone’s heart rate increased. This was because the sword kept falling towards Zhao Hai.

However, just as the sword managed to break the shield, another smaller shield took its place. The sword broke the shield again but was blocked by another smaller shield.

It was at this time that people discovered that the skyfrost sword hadn’t actually broken through the first shield. Although it looked large, it was actually a formation set that produced layers upon layers of shields stacked one after another. As the sword chopped through each layer of Zhao Hai’s shield, its momentum began to slow down.

Some quick minded people counted and saw the skyfrost sword breaking through more than sixty shields. This feat was actually very amazing. It was a large shield composed of 100-layer shields stacked one after another. It wasn’t easy to break even one of them yet the skyfrost sword managed to go through sixty.

After going through approximately 90 shields, the skyfrost sword finally stopped. Everyone let out a long breath, some couldn’t help but cheer. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s formation set to block Li Chuchen’s formidable sword.

Li Chuchen’s expression slightly dropped. He looked at Zhao Hai as he coldly snorted and said, “Good job. I didn’t expect you to block my sword. However, you still have two more to deal with.”

After he said that, Li Chuchen held his sword once more and chanted, “Pierce the skies, Second Sword!” Along with his voice, the skyfrost sword transformed into its normal form. Then Li Chuchen stabbed towards Zhao Hai’s direction. The sword quickly shot out as though it was going to stab the entire world at its tip!

Chapter 1198: The Third Sword That Never Misses

Zhao Hai stood still as he watched the sword. It wasn’t that he doesn’t want to move, it was that he couldn’t. Li Chuchen’s second sword was very formidable. It completely locked into Zhao Hai. If he moved,  then the sword would follow behind him. The sword doesn’t only fly in a straight line, it could also turn. Therefore, dodging would only be a waste of time.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as a hundred-layer formation appeared in front of him. When the formation appeared, a large sword began to materialize out of it. The sword wasn’t any smaller than the first sword. The sword’s body was entirely golden, glistening as it appeared. This golden sword faced the skyfrost sword, tip to tip.

Boom!

The large sword and the skyfrost sword collided. Two different swords clashing caused an unbelievable amount of energy to burst out. The explosion caused a wave that started at the center of the collision and spread outward. Whenever a tree was hit by this wave, they would immediately be uprooted.

The spectators outside the forest immediately erected their shields. But since they knew that the energy that would remain when it reached them had decreased by a lot, ordinary shields were enough for protection.

When the large sword collided with the skyfrost sword, it froze over before turning into fragments. But in turn, it managed to stop the skyfrost sword from going forward. Now that its momentum was quenched, the skyfrost sword lost all of its imposing power. At this point, even if Li Chuchen himself was to fly forward to attack Zhao Hai, the force he would add would still be insufficient.

Knowing that his second attack has been rendered useless, Li Chuchen’s expression sank even more. Although he was used to having his attacks being blocked, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be able to do so. He knew that the Machine Field’s hundred-layer formations were strong, however, he still didn’t pay any attention towards Zhao Hai. In his mind, he only needed one sword to kill Zhao Hai on the spot. But unfortunately for Li Chuchen, Zhao Hai was able to survive two swords in a row. This caused Li Chuchen’s face to turn ugly.

Cultivators from the Cultivation Realm were rarely defeated by the Machine Field’s Mages and Warriors. Even if the opponent wasn’t a level 4 but instead a level 5, Foundation Establishment experts would still be able to survive, even killing the enemy. This had something to do with how both sides cultivate.

When Cultivators practice, they would take in energy into their own body and then digest it in their dantian to be absorbed by their sea of energy. This would give them a supply of energy during fights.

And once this energy reaches a certain level, they would liquefy. Upon successful liquification of energy, one would then become a Foundation Establishment Expert. And once one’s energy becomes a solid core, they would then reach Core Formation.

As for the Machine Field, they practice differently than the cultivators. Warriors in the Machine Field mostly practice Battle Qi. Battle Qi gave importance to tempering one’s body. They would frantically exercise their body then produce Battle Qi. Once Battle Qi was produced, they would store it in their bodies to slowly transform their physique. However, this battle qi wouldn’t form a dantian. Therefore, Battle Qi was much more difficult to utilize compared to the qi used by the Cultivators.

Meanwhile, Mages practice spiritual force. However, practicing spiritual force wasn’t easy. And in addition, items suitable for Mages were too few. Cultivators, on the other hand, had a lot of tools they could use.

Mages in the Machine Field would generally have only a Mage Staff and also their own formation sets. Their families might provide them with additional protection but that was it. Warriors were in the same state. Besides their weapons and defensive equipment, they weren’t able to use any other thing.

Cultivators were able to forge all kinds of artifacts. From portable flying swords to peculiar items that had unique effects. It can be said that they had tools for everything. Because of this, Cultivators would win most of the time when up against Mages and Warriors from the Machine Field.

And today, Li Chuchen declared that as long as Zhao Hai survived three of his swords, then he would let Zhao Hai go. Therefore, the only weapon he could use now was the skyfrost sword. He was too arrogant in making his declaration.

Li Chuchen had become arrogant, not only because he was a genius, but also because he was a Cultivator from the Cultivation Realm.

Of the entire World of Cultivation, there was without a doubt that the strongest group hailed from the Cultivation Realm. Because of this, no matter where they went, Cultivators would always think that they were a cut above others. Naturally, Li Chuchen wasn’t an exception, let alone here in the Machine Field.

Because of this arrogance, Li Chuchen wanted to kill Zhao Hai in a flawless manner in order to show his power and prestige. However, he didn’t expect Zhao Hai to block two of his swords. This caused Li Chuchen to be caught in a tight situation.

A Foundation Establishment Cultivator unexpectedly couldn’t deal with a level 4 Mage. If this went out, then people would certainly laugh to death. Li Chuchen’s face would be dragged into the mud. Not only his face, he would also pull down the face of Extreme Cold City as well as the entire Cultivation Realm. Therefore, Li Chuchen needed to make his last sword succeed.

Li Chuchen looked at Zhao Hai with a cold expression on his face. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this hard to deal with. Although he hadn’t fought against Mages before, he still knew something about them.

Mages in the Machine Field rank their strength based on how many layers of formations they could support. The more layers, the stronger the Mage. However, this didn’t mean that a level 6 Mage could send out 1000-layer formations all the time, this was impossible. It was like how a Cultivator couldn’t use his unique skill all the time. If such a skill was that easy to use, then it wouldn’t be called unique.

Because of this, Cultivators held an advantage when going up against a Mage. Cultivators could use all kinds of artifacts in order to fight at 100 percent of their strength. Meanwhile, Mages would need to reduce their strength. This was because if they sent out a strong formation, then they would need a long time to prepare it. The enemy would never give them this much time. In actual combat, using instant-cast formations were the norm.

The fact that Zhao Hai could cast 100-layer formations instantaneously and repeatedly actually surpassed Li Chuchen’s estimates. Li Chuchen might understand if Zhao Hai could send a 100-layer formation shield the first time since it could just be stored inside his staff. However, where did the large sword come from?

Li Chuchen’s attacks weren’t just randomly sent out. His Severing the Mountains and Rivers sword was actually meant to test Zhao Hai’s strength. That move would generally have no problems dealing with Level 4 Mages since that move blocked all of the opponent’s escape routes. Even if Zhao Hai was able to block it, Li Chuchen could also use his second sword to exploit Zhao Hai’s weakness.

Sure enough, when Zhao Hai used a layered formation to form a shield, Li Chuchen immediately saw Zhao Hai’s weak point.

Because of this, Li Chuchen’s second move was his Pierce the Skies sword. His first sword was a cutting move, so its power was somewhat scattered. Since it needed to take into account a lot of things, it was impossible for it to concentrate all of its power into a single point. It wasn’t surprising for it to be blocked by a thick shield.

As for the second sword, pierce the sky was a very overbearing attack. It locked on to the enemy as it stabbed towards them. There was no need to doubt its penetrating power. Li Chuchen intended to use this attack to puncture through Zhao Hai’s shields. However, Li Chuchen didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would use another formation and had a huge sword block the skyfrost sword’s attack.

Li Chuchen looked at Zhao Hai for a moment before he smiled and said, “Good, good. It seems like the Machine Field’s newcomers this time have some skills. I didn’t expect you to be able to block two of my swords. However, my third sword will certainly cut you.”

Zhao Hai gripped liquid silver before he returned the smile and said, “Young Hero Li, please proceed. If I die by you hand, then that only meant that I haven’t practiced enough. Nobody will complain on my behalf.”

Li Chuchen coldly snorted and said, “So what if there’s a complaint? Nobody will listen to a dead person’s grievances. Take my move, Flowing Clouds, third sword!”

Just as his voice fell, Li Chuchen’s skyfrost sword flew up and made unnatural movements. It didn’t fly in a straight line and instead hovered slowly. Moreover, as the sword flew up, mists began to appear on the surroundings. This mist travelled faster than the sword and before long Zhao Hai was covered by it.

Zhao Hai felt that this sword wasn’t as overbearing as the last two. However, it was very flexible. It was like water that silently crept on. Naturally, murder in this way would happen silently.

Zhao Hai discovered that the white mist that the skyfrost sword produced wasn’t simple. Not only was the mist producing very cold air, it was also suppressing spiritual force in a large scale. This limited the distance his spiritual force could travel..

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai decided to take the bull by the horns. He quickly released fire dragons. As fire dragons appeared, they immediately surrounded Zhao Hai’s body. This scattered the white mist. However, the mist couldn’t be underestimated, it also consumed the fire dragons at a very fast rate.

Zhao Hai didn’t care as he casted another formation. This formation set produced winds and ice blades that eventually formed into a tornado. This formation set was initially used for offensive means but Zhao Hai used it this time to defend. He stood in the center of the tornado as it expanded bit by bit.

The two magic formation sets extended the range of Zhao Hai’s spiritual force. But at this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly felt that something had entered the area covered by his tornado. If it weren’t for the Zhao Hai’s formidable spiritual force, then he wouldn’t have sensed it!

Chapter 1199: Mutual Probing

When he detected this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. But he immediately concentrated his spiritual force and explored the surrounding area. Soon, he was able to discover something abnormal in the tornado.

Zhao Hai knew that in this tornado filled with ice blades, there were 360 ice blades altogether. These ice blades were coordinated with each other, forming a large net inside the tornado. All those who enter would be shredded.

But when Zhao Hai’s spiritual force searched inside the tornado, he actually felt that there were 361 ice blades inside. What made it 361 was precisely Li Chuchen’s skyfrost sword. The attacking method of the skyfrost sword was actually very strange. It could even enter Zhao Hai’s magic and become part of it.

With the skyfrost sword becoming one with the ice blades, it was akin to a fish returning to its school. It advanced alongside the tornado and didn’t resist. This wouldn’t only make it undetectable to Zhao Hai, it could also hide its aura using the tornado as a cover.

Li Chuchen’s previous two attacks were very overbearing. But the attack this time was actually as supple as running water. However, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to underestimate this attack. If Li Chuchen’s last two attacks were sword and spear meant for clashing, then this third attacking was simply meant to kill.

The skyfrost sword was now akin to a silent assassin. Only when it was the opportune time would it reveal itself and make a sudden attack. This was very dangerous.

If Zhao Hai’s spiritual force wasn’t formidable, then it would be impossible for him to discover the hidden sword. And even if he knew about it, it was still very difficult to deal with this attack.

Zhao Hai was well aware that having the skyfrost sword this close to him was too dangerous. Even if the skyfrost sword had integrated itself into the tornado, there was still a trace of Li Chuchen’s soul inside it. If Zhao Hai used any means other than magic, then Li Chuchen would certainly find out.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but flash a cold light. Then he waved his hands and cast a 50-layer formation from each one. Once these formations materialized, they immediately became ice dragons. These ice dragons shook their bodies before charging towards the wind blade filled tornado.

When the skyfrost sword detected the approaching ice dragons, Li Chuchen knew that his plan was most likely discovered by Zhao Hai. In an instant, the skyfrost sword exploded with incomparably powerful might. One ice blade sprang out from the tornado as it headed towards Zhao Hai.

However, this action didn’t seem like an attack. It was like a stream of water that arced towards its target. This time, the attack was more complex and unpredictable. Moreover, its speed was anything but slow.

Zhao Hai’s expression turned heavy. He lifted his mage staff as he whispered some incantations. A 100-layer formation appeared in front of him and soon formed a huge hammer. Once this metallic hammer appeared, it immediately locked into the skyfrost sword. With the might that could destroy the heavens and the earth, the hammer pounded towards the incoming attack.

As the trajectory of the skyfrost sword changed, the hammer did as well. Since the sword was locked into him, there was no need for Zhao Hai to purposefully command his hammer.

It didn’t take long before the hammer and the sword came in contact. Boom! A loud sound was heard as Zhao Hai’s large hammer vanished. However, the skyfrost sword didn’t slow down, instead it became faster as it stabbed towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai felt his heartbeat going quicker, he didn’t expect the skyfrost sword to use the strength of the explosion to propel itself forward. It truly was very difficult to deal with.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai waved his hand as huge magic formation appeared in front of him. Once this formation appeared, the ice and wind tornado vanished as it gathered around the magic formation. Even the white mist was being sucked by the formation. This allowed the spectators outside to have a clearer view of things.

The formation set rotated, and in the process of rotating, all magic formations slowly fused together forming a huge formation plate. This formation plate revolved around Zhao Hai before stopping in front of him, restricting the approaching skyfrost sword.

The skyfrost sword wanted to avoid the formation plate but was unsuccessful. If the skyfrost sword was a car, then the formation plate was a roadblock. However, the plate just rotated in place and didn’t attack the skyfrost sword, it just guarded Zhao Hai.

The sword was at a deadlock. The spectators couldn’t help but have their hearts stuck in their throats. But at this time, Li Chuchen’s expression changed. This was because he knew that it wouldn’t be good to drag on. He knew that there was no way for his attack to break Zhao Hai’s magic formation.

Zhao Hai’s magic formation was strange. Although it was just a 100-layer formation set, it could actually absorb the surrounding energy to strengthen itself. This caused the formation to be more and more solid and increasingly hard. At this point, it was impossible to break through this formation using the skyfrost sword.

This isn’t to say that Li Chuchen couldn’t break this formation, but it was impossible for his third attack to do so. His third sword was akin to flowing water that changes its direction silently as it approached the enemy before making a sudden attack.

Although this attack was very hard to defend against and was the best for killing, there was no denying that the power of this attack was much worse than the last two attacks.

This was an attack that sacrificed offensive strength in exchange for unpredictability. And if the skyfrost sword was met by another attack, then it could use that to strengthen itself.

Zhao Hai discovered this characteristic back when he sent his hammer out. Because of this, he changed his tactic and instead used the rotating formation disc. Moreover, he controlled it in a way where it wasn’t attacking. Instead, the magic was used to protect. This way, the skyfrost sword wouldn’t be able to make use of it.

Zhao Hai was dragging on since he knew he could. However, Li Chuchen wasn’t in the same situation. His identity didn’t allow him to make a compromise. Either he withdraws his sword or continues on with his attack.

Receiving his sword meant that Zhao Hai blocked his three attacks. And with his arrogance, Li Chuchen would no longer attack Zhao Hai, which meant that Zhao Hai had passed his test.

Also, Zhao Hai had the confidence to block Li Chuchen’s attack. This meant that Zhao Hai had won since he could block Li Chuchen’s third sword if even Li Chuchen decided to continue on with his attack.

Naturally, Li Chuchen taking his sword back held a different meaning compared to him continuing with his attack. These choices would show Li Chuchen’s character. If Li Chuchen receives his sword, then this meant that he knew that he had failed, and has decided to give up. This would show that he was a very dangerous person. Those who had the patience to retreat were dangerous enemies.

If Li Chuchen carried on with his attack, then this meant that he was a person who couldn’t accept losing. He would insist on doing what was impossible just to save face. Such person was equally dangerous since he might become a villain that would take any opportunity for revenge.

It wasn’t late for a gentleman to take revenge after ten years, while a villain would be a threat from morning to night. This didn’t mean that a gentleman wouldn’t retaliate. On the contrary, a gentleman’s revenge would be calmer. He waited for ten years for an opportunity. So when this opportunity arrives, he would make sure that the enemy would never recover.

A villain’s revenge lacked the patience to endure patiently and calmly. He would retaliate from dawn to dusk and would use all means to achieve his goal. This would make him very annoying. But in the end, it was still difficult to know which of the two had a more effective method.

Zhao Hai was now waiting for what Li Chuchen would do next. He wanted to see what kind of person Li Chuchen was.

Li Chuchen looked at the stalemate with a cold expression. He knew that continuing would be futile. Although he was reluctant, he needed to make a decision.

Li Chuchen turned his head to Zhao Hai who was controlling his formation disc and couldn’t help but give a cold snort. His three attacks were meant to test Zhao Hai’s strength. The first sword tested his ability to respond. That sword wasn’t easy to deal with, yet Zhao Hai was able to block it.

The second sword was to test Zhao Hai’s offensive capability. Not only was the sword so simple. It also represented Li Chuchen’s confidence. And once again, Zhao Hai passed the test.

As for the third sword, it was meant to test Zhao Hai ability for magic. Magic control wasn’t an easy matter. The move ‘flowing clouds’ wasn’t a simple move. This sword required an intense amount of concentration. In order to block this strike, Zhao Hai would need a similar level of control over his spells. Although it seems like he made a bit of an effort, Zhao Hai still blocked it regardless.

Li Chuchen knew that he didn’t have the means to kill Zhao Hai in three swords. Therefore, he coldly snorted and then took his skyfrost sword back. He knew that he was in the Machine Field, and that it wouldn’t be good to continue fighting with Zhao Hai. If he wanted to deal with Zhao Hai, then he needed to do it in the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Upon taking his skyfrost sword back, Li Chuchen looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Very good. Zhao Hai, you’re quite strong. I’ll be seeing you in the Six Realm Beginner Competition.” Then he turned his head towards Ba Dong for a moment before flying away. He didn’t even spare a word towards the Water Temple Bishop.

Seeing Lu Chuchen fly away, the environment became alive once more as applause began to break out. Almost every single person present were smiling. The Machine Field has been suppressed by the Cultivation Realm all these years. In one-on-one battles, there was almost no way for the Machine Field to win. But now that Zhao Hai managed to block three swords from Li Chuchen, they couldn’t help but feel that it was a victory for the Machine Field.

There was only one person present who had a very ugly expression, and it was Ba Dong! Ba Dong didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be able to block Li Chuchen’s three swords. Now, he was someone who tried to steal a chicken only to lose the rice used to lure it. Everyone knew that he brought Li Chuchen to deal with Zhao Hai. This meant that he would no longer be received well in the Machine Field.

At this time, Cadjo’s voice sounded out from beside Ba Dong, “Bishop Ba Dong, I apologize for the Ashley Family’s poor treatment of your companion. Please accept a glass of wine from me as an apology.” Cadjo’s words didn’t have any shred of sincerity in it and it even held a bit of chill.

Chapter 1200: Instant Fame

Cadjo’s expression showed his current mood very well. He was both cheerful and murderous. He was happy because Zhao Hai was alright, but he felt like he wanted to kill Ba Dong on the spot.

When Ba Dong heard Cadjo’s words, he couldn’t help but look at Cadjo. The Ashley Family Manager was looking at him with a cold stare. Ba Dong’s heart turned cold, then he said, “I’m afraid I can’t. I’ve already disturbed you for long enough. I’ll be taking my leave.” Then after he said that, he turned around and went to his car before it sped away.

Seeing Ba Dong vanishing in the distance, Cadjo couldn’t help but coldly snort. He will remember this and make sure that Ba Dong wouldn’t have any good days to come. Being called the Smiling Demon wasn’t’ a joke.

At this time, Zhao Hai flew back from the forest. Then he received his magic staff before looking at Cadjo and said, “I’ve been unfair to General Manager. I caused the family to lose money by destroying the Incense Tree forest.”

When Cadjo said this, he couldn’t help but laugh. Then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Alright, alright. I’ll ask the higher authorities to excuse you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. At this time, people from the party went to talk to Zhao Hai and Cadjo. The two stayed there and handled the courtesies.

However, this time, people’s attention weren’t on Cadjo. Instead, they were more interested in talking with Zhao Hai. He just managed to block three swords from Li Chuchen, this was enough evidence that he had true strength.

Looking at these people, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel a bit of sorrow. The Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm was supposed to be on equal grounds. He was the first place in the realm qualifier while Li Chuchen was tenth. Yet these people see it as a miracle that he was able to block Li Chuchen’s three swords. This showed how pitiful Ascenders were in the Machine Field.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t show his emotion at this time. He just smiled as he talked with the people who approached him. Zhao Hai not being arrogant made everyone feel very good about him.

Xiong Li and the others weren’t able to squeeze in, but they didn’t seem to care. They just stood aside and looked at the smiling people surrounding Zhao Hai. Xiong Li even said, “How famous do you reckon Little Hai would be? I think the entire realm will know about this by tomorrow.”

Sun Fei’s face showed his excitement as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Too strong, Brother Hai is too strong. He’s my idol.”

Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Very good, very good. But this way, he’ll have to treat us for drinking tomorrow. Hahaha, that Cultivator fellow had an ugly face when he left.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “I think Ba Dong had the ugliest expression. When he left, he almost seemed like he was running away. He plotted against Little Hai but failed. Now, Little Hai will be seen by the Machine Field as a hero while he would be seen as a traitor. I wonder how he’ll fix his reputation now.”

Margaret, who didn’t join the crowd, smiled and added, “He’ll have a very hard time doing that. Don’t forget that Uncle Cadjo is also known as the Smiling Demon by the Machine Field. He would only plot against another person if provoked. And now that Ba Dong offended him, he wouldn’t be able to leave it at that. Ba Dong will surely have a hard time.”

Upon hearing Margaret, everyone present unconsciously nodded. It has been a few years since Xiong Li and the others ascended, so they were familiar with Cadjo’s title of Smiling Demon. They also knew what this name entailed. Therefore, they agreed to Margaret’s words.

Dongfang Yu looked at Margaret and asked, “Sister-in-law, why are you here instead of being beside Little Hai?”

Margaret smiled faintly and said, “I don’t like dealing with such crowds. Actually, Brother Hai dislikes it as well. However, he has no choice but to face them now. If he wasn’t thinking about the Ashley Family, then he would’ve already went drinking with you. He said that it’s very exhausting dealing with such people.”

Dongfang Yu and the others laughed. They had some understanding of Zhao Hai, and he did indeed dislike such crowds.

If any other Ascender were placed in Zhao Hai’s position, then they would have already been shining with joy. Being able to gain connections with such famous and influential people was something that was very important for Ascenders. Therefore, most ascenders would definitely flatter these people if they were in Zhao Hai’s shoes.

Dongfang Yu and the others couldn’t help but think about what would happen if they were in Zhao Hai’s position. They wondered if they were still able to be as calm as Zhao Hai. But after inspecting themselves, they knew that they couldn’t be sure.

Cadjo’s party was held not so late. So when people found out about what happened, they immediately drove over to the party in order to inquire about the situation. In the end, the party had to extend beyond its schedule.

The party finally ended very late into the night. When everyone had gone back to take a rest, Margaret and Zhao Hai returned to the Space. Zhao Hai didn’t feel anything when he was fighting against Li Chuchen. However, he found himself to be very exhausted when dealing with the crowd. After going to the hot spring with Margaret, he returned to his room and slept.

What Zhao Hai didn’t know was that when he was asleep, the entire Machine Field erupted. Video of his fight with Li Chuchen had spread. Nobody knew who spread it around but it didn’t take long before it reached all corners of the realm. This caused a stir  in the Machine Field.

The Machine Field had always been at a disadvantage when it comes to one-on-one. Not to say about the same levels, even those who were a level or two above their Cultivation realm counterparts wouldn’t dare challenge cultivators.

Yet now, Zhao Hai who was a level 4 Mage managed to block three swords from a tenth place beginner Cultivator. He didn’t even look frazzled after receiving the three swords. Zhao Hai was already famous for being a dark horse, and this event made him even more well-known.

Countless people faced their computers that night, watching a recording of Zhao Hai and Li Chuchen’s battle on repeat. They were unable to restrain themselves from feeling excited, they were unable to sleep.

The fight was too beautiful. The attacks were splendid and even more so Zhao Hai’s defence. From the video, Zhao Hai’s defense was flawless. He didn’t even press wind one time, no distress was seen on his face.

Beautiful, it was too beautiful. This was the most beautiful battle between a Mage from the Machine Field and a Cultivator. Zhao Hai’s popularity sharply increased.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of any of these since he was sleeping inside the Space. He had a very good sleep. He was aware that Li Chuchen was a Cultivator at Foundation Establishment stage. His fight with Li Chuchen made him realize how strong he was in relation to his peers. Being able to fight with Li Chuchen like that without exerting much effort gave Zhao Hai a boost of confidence. Zhao Hai knew that Li Chuchen didn’t use all of his strength. However, this was natural. Li Chuchen had a lot of magical artifacts that he didn’t use, but Zhao Hai was in the same position. He still had his astral qi but he didn’t use it. This was because he was afraid that Li Chuchen would find out about it.

The Cultivation Realm’s people were very sensitive when it came to special qi. Astral qi was one with very overbearing strength. If Li Chuchen felt even a hint of astral qi in Zhao Hai, then Zhao Hai would certainly have bad days ahead.

After resting the entire night, Zhao Hai ate his breakfast the next morning before leaving the Space along with Margaret. Then the two returned to their room in the Ashley Family building.

Just as they returned, Cadjo sent for someone to call them over. Upon entering Cadjo’s office, the two couldn’t help but stare. There were only three other people inside, Cadjo, Luke, and Desbarres. However, their eyes were very red. They looked like they hadn’t slept since last night.

Zhao Hai looked at the appearance of the three as he confusedly asked, “General Manager, Camp Lord, what happened? You didn’t sleep last night?”

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai, then he suddenly laughed as he said, “Little Hai, sit, sit. Hahaha. You really did great this time. Hahaha. You’re famous now. There’s nobody in the Machine Field who doesn’t know your name.”

Zhao Hai looked puzzled at what Cadjo said, he couldn’t understand what was going on. From the time he slept last night up until now, he didn’t access the internet, the same was true for Laura and the others. Because of this, he didn’t know anything that happened online.

After Cadjo had Zhao Hai sit down, he said, “Last night, someone uploaded a video of your battle with Li Chuchen to the internet. This caused a sensation online. Everyone is talking about you saying that you are a hero of the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “They’re exaggerating. I just blocked three swords from Li Chuchen. Cultivators have far more means than we can imagine. If we really fought each other, then I can’t guarantee if I can win against him.”

Cadjo waved his hand and said, “It’s useless. The moment you blocked Li Chuchen’s three swords and won the duel, you’ve already become a hero. Besides you, nobody can do something like that at the same  level. Not to say all three swords, they wouldn’t even be able to block one.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I know, but I can’t get anything out of this fame. Being famous isn’t that big of a deal.”

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai as he shook his head and said, “You idiot. This doesn’t benefit you directly. But this is a huge advantage for the Ashley Family. You’re now like a living billboard of the family.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, then he waved his hand and said, “Alright. But I don’t want to participate in those parties anymore. If anyone wants to invite me to a party, please tell them that I’m busy. I’ll leave everything else to the family.”

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but shake his head and smile bitterly. He didn’t know what else to say. However, Desbarres smiled and said, “Alright, you also need to show yourself less. People would surely come over to challenge you so that they could elevate their own fame. So before the Six Realm Beginner Competition begins, you need to be in seclusion.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and said, “Camp Lord, didn’t  you say that other participants aren’t allowed to challenge anyone before the Six Realm Beginner Competition? Then why would I need to close up?”

Desbarres smiled faintly and said, “Of course, no other participant would want to challenge you. However, this news wouldn’t only spread in the Machine Field. What if some Cultivators come here and challenge you? What do you do now? It’s better for you to close up immediately.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll close up. But I already promised Brother Xiong Li and the others to drink. If they come to see me, just have them go to my room.” Desbarres nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll take care of it. Don’t worry.” Zhao Hai nodded before leading Margaret back to his room.

When the two returned to their room, Margaret immediately opened up her computer and went to a video website. And just as she opened the site, she saw the huge headline, “Newly crowned Machine Field Champion Zhao Hai fighting against the Cultivation Realm’s Top Ten!” The headline linked to the video. Margaret went to the link and then saw a video viewed billions of times, and that number was still going up.

Margaret couldn’t help but giggle as she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it seems like you’re very famous now.”

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly as he watched the video. The footage was clearly taken by someone who attended the party. The quality of the video wasn’t good, but it was because of this that it was more authentic.

And even if the quality wasn’t good, it had shown everything that happened. It even managed to record every word they spoke.

Zhao Hai looked further down on the page and saw that there were comments below.

First comment: Beautiful, fantastic! Our Machine Field finally managed to face a Cultivator and win. Support! Supporting Zhao Hai! The pride of the Machine Field!

Second comment: I support the first comment! Support Zhao Hai! The pride of the Machine Field!

Third comment: I didn’t expect our Mages to face a Cultivator. Powerful, too powerful. Why didn’t anybody do this before? It’s too strange!

Fourth comment: The commenter above isn’t a Mage, so he doesn’t know that Zhao Hai is far more powerful than most level 4 Mages. In the machine field, as long as one could use 100-layer formations, then they would be level 4. Casting 100-layer formations instantaneously is something that cannot be done by any other Mage. Zhao Hai is just too powerful!

Fifth comment: Don’t get your hopes up. Zhao Hai only managed to block against the enemy’s three attacks. Moreover, Cultivators have a lot of magic treasures. Those three swords isn’t their only means to attack. Moreover, Zhao Hai is going full defense. It isn’t unusual for him to block three swords.

Sixth comment: The fifth comment is talking fart. Even a plant could see everything clearly. Although Zhao Hai is on the defensive, it’s clear that he wasn’t in distress. His clothes aren’t even ruffled nor did he take a step back. This shows that Zhao Hai still has more strength than this. His strength should be on par with Li Chuchen. Fifth comment, if you don’t know anything, then keep your mouth shut!

Chapter 1201: Stir Between Two Realms

Zhao Hai was famous! Very famous! Everyone in the Machine Field was discussing Zhao Hai. And it wasn’t only the average people who were talking about him. Even the huge powers of the Machine Field had him as a topic of conversation.

Zhao Hai underestimated the hatred that the people of the Machine Field had against the Cultivators. This wasn’t just because of the Cultivation Realm’s various invasions towards the Machine Field. This hatred started at a spiritual level.

People from the Cultivation Realm always looked at the people of the Machine Field with an arrogant attitude. They conducted themselves as though they were emperors looking at beggars. It was this attitude that made people from the Machine Field hate the Cultivators to the core.

This hatred only got stronger and stronger to the point where the people from the Machine Field prayed that someone would get strong enough that it made them equal to the Cultivators.

However, no Mage, Warrior, or Mech Soldier managed to achieve this goal. None of them were able to defeat a Cultivator of the same level. This caused people to hope more and more.

Although Zhao Hai only blocked three swords from Li Chuchen, the significance of this result was actually more than expected. It was a breakthrough for the Machine Field. Because of this, everyone was happily talking about it.

Nobody in the Machine Field believed that Li Chuchen was holding back. This was because the Cultivators were always impolite towards people from the Machine Field. If they ever duelled someone from the Machine Field, they would certainly go brutal. It was simply impossible for a Cultivator to hold back. With this in mind, people believed that Zhao Hai was strong enough to block Li Chuchen’s three swords!

These reasons made Zhao Hai a very famous individual in the Machine Field. He was now seen as a hero of the realm.

While everyone was talking about Zhao Hai, the subject in question suddenly announced that he was closing up for practice. It was still unknown as to when he would show up again.

Upon hearing this information, everyone in the Machine Field were startled. Then rumors began surfacing everywhere. Some people said that Zhao Hai was seriously injured after fighting Li Chuchen. He just restrained his injury and was now feeling the backlash. They say that Zhao Hai was dying.

There were also some people who said that Zhao Hai was closing up in order to practice a secret technique. This way, he could defeat more Cultivators in the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

All kinds of rumors appeared and the Machine Field fell into confusion. At this time everyone wanted to see Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai was already out of sight.

After things slowly went out of control, the Ashley Family decided to have a press conference. They announced to everyone that Zhao Hai wasn’t injured. The reason he was closing up was because he needed to prepare for the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Originally, people were dissatisfied with the Ashley Family’s response. However, what happened afterwards made them understand why the Ashley Family did it.

Just like what Desbarres said, the battle between Zhao Hai and Li Chuchen didn’t only cause a huge reaction in the Machine Field. The Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm were connected in a way. Because of this, any important matter in the Machine Field would quickly be made known in the Cultivation Realm. With Zhao Hai and Li Chuchen’s battle being the biggest matter in the Machine Field, it was natural for the Cultivation Realm to be aware of it.

Upon hearing about this information, the people in the Cultivation Realm were in an uproar. One must know that in the entire World of Cultivation, the Machine Field was the weakest of the 6 realms. This was also one of the reasons why others look down on the Machine Field.

And now, the Cultivation Realm’s tenth place qualifier wasn’t able to kill the Machine Field’s first placer in three swords. This was absurd for those in the Cultivation Realm.

It didn’t take long before the people from the Cultivation Realm found a recording of the battle and watched it. Although the quality of the recording wasn’t good, those who knew something were still able to make sense of it. They knew that the result wasn’t because Li Chuchen was holding back, it was because his opponent wasn’t weak.

Because of this recording, the Cultivation Realm’s people didn’t blame Li Chuchen for losing. Instead, they were startled by Zhao Hai’s strength.

Naturally, those who didn’t blame Li Chuchen weren’t those of the general public. The high-level beings in the Cultivation Realm didn’t blame Li Chuchen since they knew that he was strong. On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t weak either. Li Chuchen didn’t hold back and yet his three swords were still blocked by Zhao Hai. There was no reason for Li Chuchen to be blamed for this outcome.

Those in higher positions didn’t say anything about it, but things were different for the others. After all, competition exists everywhere, especially in the Cultivation Realm.

Although the Cultivation Realm was very rich in resources, this advantage was being negated by its huge population. In this case, those who gets to use these resources were limited. Therefore, competition was brutal.

Every Cultivator had a dream, and that was to achieve immortality and live alongside the heavens and the earth. However, becoming immortal needed a lot of resources such as cultivation methods, weapons, pills, and other things. The more important something was, the more scarce they were. So in order for a Cultivator to get closer to this dream of immortality, they would have to fight for it.

And the top ten newcomers were the top existence among the lower levels of the Cultivation Realm. They were above others and enjoyed resources much better than most people. They also practice the best cultivation methods and were generally envied by a lot of people.

In the past, these experts were very famous because of their strength. Even if other people say anything to them, these words were often said in secret. In the Cultivation Realm, the right to speak depended on one’s strength. If that expert heard it, then it would be a problem if they kill the one who talked. Nobody would go to the trouble of talking bad about these top ten experts to just be killed in the end.

However, this matter gave those at the bottom level an opportunity. Li Chuchen was one of the Cultivation Realm’s ten great experts and was enjoying the best of treatments. But despite these benefits, Li Chuchen was still not able to take care of a kid from the Machine Field!

There were quite a few talks like these in the Machine Field. Naturally, most experts wouldn’t care about this since they saw Zhao Hai’s strength. However, those who had been suppressed by Li Chuchen didn’t care about how strong Zhao Hai was. They just clung on the fact that Zhao Hai was from the Machine Field, and that Li Chuchen was putting mud on the Cultivation Realm’s reputation.

There were also people who had strength worse than Li Chuchen that decided that it was a good idea to kill Zhao Hai. In their eyes, Li Chuchen wasn’t able to kill Zhao Hai because of the three sword covenant. If this three sword covenant wasn’t in place, then Li Chuchen would’ve easily killed Zhao Hai.

And since Li Chuchen failed to kill Zhao Hai, the others saw this as an opportunity to elevate themselves. If they could kill Zhao Hai, then they would be regaining a huge face for the Cultivation Realm.

There were quite a few Cultivators who had the same idea. They immediately went to the nearest transmission formation and went to the Machine Field. All of them were planning to challenge Zhao Hai.

Naturally, the movement of such numbers of people couldn’t be hidden from the people of the Machine Field. Seeing a sudden influx of Cultivators, the Machine Field couldn’t help but turn vigilant. They quickly investigated the reason why these people came.

Before long, they got their answer. All of these people were here to challenge Zhao Hai. Moreover, it seems like they had no intention of hiding their plans as all of them went to look for the Ashley Family.

However, the Ashley Family only gave a single answer, Zhao Hai was closing up and was unavailable! It can be said that this excuse was the most effective one. Closing up to practice wasn’t only done in the Machine Field. Every single cultivator did this at some point of their lives. When someone was closing up, it was taboo to disturb them. Therefore, since Zhao Hai was closing up, nobody was allowed to issue him a challenge.

When this information was sent to the Machine Field, people finally found out why Zhao Hai suddenly closed up. To be honest, people became relieved upon knowing about this.

Then almost at the same time, the top 100 beginners of the Machine Field decided to close up as well. After that, a large number of experts decided to close up. “Closing up” had become a trending topic in the Machine Field’s online world.

Due to the Machine Field’s rogue-like practice, those experts from the Cultivation Field had no way to challenge anyone at all. Some of them thought that since there was no way to challenge Zhao Hai, they would challenge others in order to give themselves a boost in fame. However, it seems like everyone was closing up. They couldn’t find anyone to challenge, this caused them to be annoyed.

These Cultivators also knew that they can only challenge famous experts. There was no significance in challenging small fry. Killing these weak Mages and Warriors was useless. Once they go back, they wouldn’t be able to gain any face.

Because of this, the foreign challengers found themselves in a very awkward situation. If they remained, then they would have nobody to challenge. Most of them were also unwilling to go home. They were in a dilemma.

Just like the challengers, the high-level figures of the Machine Field were also having headaches. Although they had protected their experts by having them close up, they ended up shouldering all of the stress and pressure.

No matter what the higher-levels say, the people of the Machine Field believed that everyone closing up was just a reason to evade the challenge. This was the action of a coward. Therefore, there were a lot of people cursing online. In their opinion, they would rather have Zhao Hai die in battle than seeing everyone acting like cowards. They had lost face!

Chapter 1202: Heading Out

Those in high positions in the Machine Field considered these public clamorings as though they didn’t exist. They knew clearly that they shouldn’t listen to this public outcry. If they caused the Machine Field to lose all 100 of their participants, then the Machine Field would no longer be able to fight for benefits in the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

And once the Machine Field couldn’t fight for benefits, they would get weaker and weaker. Then they would be bullied even more, and then lose more in the future. This wasn’t something that the higher-ups of the Machine Field wanted to see.

Actually, both the public and the higher-ups of the Machine Field don’t see ascenders as someone on their own side. To them, Ascenders were merely tools. But the difference between ordinary tools and Ascenders was that there were some Ascenders that were useful while there were some that were useless.

Naturally, Zhao Hai and the other participants were useful tools in the eyes of the Machine Field’s higher-ups. Therefore, they couldn’t just be sacrificed like that.

Zhao Hai was also aware of the troubles happening outside, but he didn’t care. For him, those Cultivators outside weren’t worth his time. If he went out now, he could easily kill all of those people.

Of course, Zhao Hai wouldn’t do that. There was no need to. For Zhao Hai, murder was something he would only do whenever it benefits him. There was no need for senseless slaughter.

Zhao Hai was currently practicing his spells inside the Space. After he practiced with Liquid SIlver, he proceeded to use his body tempering fist while inside the sandy region of the Space.

Zhao Hai knew that his own strength still wouldn’t allow him to run amuck in the Machine Field. Therefore, he needed to strengthen himself as soon as possible; and the body tempering technique was a good method to reach that goal.

Since the Machine Field were acting cowardly, most Cultivators left. Only a small number of people stayed in the Machine Field, they were still looking for that opportunity.

Peace began to return to the Machine Field as the Cultivators retreated. It was impossible for these people to focus on this matter for too long, especially if it didn’t matter much to their lives.

The winds in the Machine Field gradually calmed down, which was something that the higher-ups of the Machine Field wanted to see. They don’t want the participants of the competition to be disturbed. This was because they were looking forward to this particular Six Realm Beginner Competition.

This time, the Machine Field’s representatives included Zhao Hai, Streep, Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, Zhu Chen, even Lei Xiaotian. Compared to the past dozens of years, this was the Machine Field’s strongest lineup.

In the past Six Realm Beginner Competitions, there would be 600 participants overall. The Machine Field would have participants among the top 500 or 400. This was a complete loss of face for the Machine Field. They weren’t able to get any good benefits by these rankings alone.

But this time, Zhao Hai was able to block three swords from the Cultivation Realm’s tenth place. This was a good sign for the Machine Field. This was because, most of the time, the top ten experts of the Cultivation Realm would be the top ten experts of the entire World of Cultivation.

Although Zhao Hai only blocked against three swords from Li Chuchen, the higher-ups of the Machine Field still held hope for Zhao Hai. They wanted him to fight for benefits for the realm.

Days passed as the date for the Six Realm Beginner Competition approached. Cultivators that kept waiting for an opportunity were finally able to realize that the whole Machine Field was turtling up, so they just gave up and returned to the Cultivation Realm. After all, the Machine Field doesn’t have resources that they need, staying here for long wasn’t favorable for their cultivation.

Once all of the Cultivators left the Machine Field, the higher-ups were finally able to relax. The Machine Field returned to its former calm as everyone waited for the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Zhao Hai didn’t leave his seclusion just because the Cultivators had left. He still declared that he would continue with his closed door cultivation. This caused everyone who had their eyes on him to believe that he was truly injured. After all, Li Chuchen’s swords weren’t that weak.

This time, the Ashley Family didn’t bother to clarify the matter. In their opinion, there was no need to do so. Although there were people who kept monitoring Zhao Hai, their number wasn’t as great as before.

After one month, Zhao Hai finally decided to head out. It wasn’t that he could no longer endure closing up, it was that he had no choice but to head out. It was time for the Six Realm Beginner Competition.

Although the Six Realm Beginner Competition was still a month away, they still needed to prepare beforehand for their departure.

When Zhao Hai announced that he was going out, Xiong Li and the others quickly visited him. Xiong Li and the others were mainly there to see if Zhao Hai was indeed injured. After all, he wouldn’t have been in seclusion for that long. But after seeing how well Zhao Hai was doing, they felt relieved.

Once Xiong Li and the others left, Cadjo immediately called Zhao Hai over to his room. Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, how is your practice?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “General Manager, rest assured, there’s no problem whatsoever. This time, I’m sure that I can enter the top 100 of the competition.”

Cadjo smiled and said, “Don’t put yourself into too much pressure. If it’s disadvantageous, then don’t show your power. The Patriarch is already satisfied with your performance.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, General Manager, I know what to do. Right, how do we leave the Machine Field? Do we use a spaceship? When do we depart?”

Cadjo shook his head and said, “There’s no ship. This time, we’ll be using a transmission formation since you need to be in the Cultivation Realm for one month. This is also the way it is done.”

Upon hearing Cadjo, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but ask, “We need to stay in the Cultivation Realm for one month? What kind of rule is that? Isn’t that just sending us to the tiger’s mouth? What if those Cultivators challenge us?”

Cadjo shook his head and said, “You don’t need to worry about this. The Cultivators wouldn’t challenge you. You need to stay in the Cultivation Realm because the concentration of spiritual qi there is different from the Machine Field. You would need a month to adjust to their level. It has been decided to no challenges will be made in this period.”

Zhao Hai was still frowning. He doesn’t believe the words of the Cultivation Realm. The Machine Field was a very weak existence among the six realms, this meant that they don’t have much diplomatic influence. Although the Cultivation Realm said that nobody would make a challenge, there were innumerable means for people to accept a challenge. This was reality.

Cadjo looked at Zhao Hai and knew that he was thinking. He sighed and said, “I know what you are thinking about. Don’t think too much about it, this is the rule. But just be careful once you leave.”

Zhao Hai looked at Cadjo and said, “You aren’t going with us this time?”

Cadjo nodded and said, “Right, I won’t be going. Those who will be going to the Cultivation Realm would only number 150. There’s you 100 participants, and then 50 leaders. Leading the 50 team leaders is a very famous individual from the three powers, Skybreaker Blade Ma Rulong.”

When Zhao Hai heard Cadjo, he couldn’t help but gawk. He knew who Skybreaker Ma Rulong was. Ma Rulong wasn’t an Ascender and was a Machine Field native. Only a few Machine Field natives would want to practice martial arts. However, Ma Rulong loved martial arts ever since childhood. Moreover, the family he belonged to was an ancient Warrior Family of the Warrior Association. It was a tradition in his family to practice martial arts, but it wasn’t a priority for them to practice it. However, Ma Rulong put his entire heart into practicing martial arts. In the end, he was able to become a master of fighting.

Ma Rulong established his fame using his ghost head sword. At this time, he’s already become a level 7 Warrior. His strength was formidable. He wouldn’t have any problems facing a Core Formation Expert of the Cultivation Realm.[1]

But unlike his fellow natives, Ma Rulong doesn’t have any prejudice against Ascenders. It may be because of his love for martial arts. Because of this, he looked favorably towards Ascenders. He also wasn’t afraid of offending anyone from the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “I didn’t expect Senior Ma Rulong to be our escort. Then there’s no need to worry about the travel. General Manager, when will we depart?”

Cadjo answered, “You’ll leave the day after tomorrow. Although Ma Rulong will take the lead, you still need to be careful. There will be times where Ma Rulong wouldn’t be able to protect you. After all, the place you’ll be going is the Cultivation Realm. That is the territory of the Cultivators, we don’t have much influence there.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “General Manager, feel relieved. I know what to do. There’s no need to worry.”

Cadjo sighed, then he went to Zhao Hai’s side and then patted his shoulder as he said, “Remember that your own safety is most important. Think about Margaret. Even if you don’t get good results, the family will not blame you for it. After all, you already became the realm’s champion. You already surpassed our expectations.” Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I’ll make sure to be safe. Nothing bad will happen.”

Cadjo nodded, then he said, “Take time to go out for a walk. Let other people see you. We don’t want them to think that you’re really injured.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I happen to have a desire to explore. I’ve been cultivating all this time. I haven’t had much time to explore the entire planet.” Cadjo smiled and said, “Alright, go go. You’re currently the richest man in the entire family. You won’t have any money problems.”

Zhao Hai laughed and didn’t say anything else. He cannot tell Cadjo that he was heading out to sell things he had no need for. Everything that he needed was already in the Space. And even if the Space doesn’t have it, he could still have it made by the Processing Machine. Things made by the Space was always much better than items that can be bought outside!

* * *

Ghost head blade https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ftse4.mm.bing.net%2Fth%3Fid%3DOIP.ebQlJuXn-0GDQWdwUZDVDwHaNl%26pid%3DApi&f=1

Chapter 1203: Departure

Two days quickly went by. Over the two days, Zhao Hai and Margaret explored the entirety of the Machine Field Planet. This brought attention to a lot of people in the Machine Field.

However, nobody dared to cause trouble for Zhao Hai. With the Six Realm Beginner Competition on the horizon, nobody would disturb any participant, especially Zhao Hai.

But even so, whenever Zhao Hai was exploring with Margaret, a lot of people would stare at them. This made the two feel quite uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai was a high-profile individual, and his sudden appearance caused people to be taken aback. They always thought that Zhao Hai was injured. But judging by his current state, he looked very healthy. Was he really injured? Or was he just suppressing his injury?

Zhao Hai decided to ignore these people. Although there wasn’t much in the Machine Field Planet that caught his attention, he still made the effort to get gifts for Laura and the others. These things didn’t need to be expensive, it was the thought that counts.

What Zhao Hai brought for Laura and the others were trivial gadgets that weren’t worth their money but was instead beautiful. This was something girls liked.

Zhao Hai actually felt sorry for Laura and the others. They had been with him for a long time, but they could only stay inside the Space at this moment. They observe and understand the Machine Field only through the monitor. They can’t come out and play in the Machine Field. This caused Zhao Hai to feel very guilty.

After Zhao Hai played around with Margaret for two days, the time for departure finally came. Zhao Hai got up in the morning before going with Cadjo towards the place where they would depart.

The Machine Field Planet has two huge transmission formations. The first formation was something that can only be used by core members of the Machine Field. This formation could be adjusted to teleport towards more than 1000 planets in the Machine Field.

As for the other transmission formation, it was specifically guarded and shut off during normal times. This was done so that people from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t use it. A secret technique was used to shut it off.

The two formations were in two teleportation towers specifically constructed for their respective functions. They were heavily guarded structures. And now Zhao Hai and the others were heading there.

Margaret sat besides Zhao Hai as she snuggled to Zhao Hai’s bosom and whispered, “Brother Hai, you need to take care of yourself. Cultivators aren’t easy to deal with, especially that Li Chuchen. You made him lose face last time, he will surely retaliate.”

Actually, there was no need for Margaret to say those words. After all, she could just say them to Zhao Hai while inside the Space. However, if Margaret didn’t say anything, Cadjo and the others would get suspicious. Because of this, Margaret had to perform. This was also something that Laura and the others taught her.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, nothing bad will happen. I’ll come back safely.”

Margaret nodded gently, her eyes were somewhat red. The hand that she held Zhao Hai with couldn’t help but tighten. Although they could talk to each other inside the Space, being able to talk in person was different. Inside the Space, Zhao Hai doesn’t only belong to Margaret, he belonged to everyone. Only in the Machine Field would Zhao Hai belong to her alone.

Margaret was actually half worried and half acting. She loved Zhao Hai and she doesn’t want anything dangerous happen to him. Therefore, she acted thus.

Zhao Hai held Margaret near his ear and then whispered, “It’s fine. Don’t worry about not seeing me. I won’t be in any trouble.” Margaret buried herself deeper into Zhao Hai’s embrace. Zhao Hai could even feel his clothes getting wet with tears.

Zhao hai sighed. This was another debt that he couldn’t pay off in his lifetime. The only thing he could do right now was to treat his women well.

Cadjo saw Zhao Hai and Margaret’s state and didn’t say anything. Thunder already instructed the Ashley Family to allow Zhao Hai and Margaret’s relationship. In other words, he agreed to their union. Because of this, Cadjo didn’t react.

Actually, Cadjo was hoping that Zhao Hai would end up together with Margaret. Zhao Hai’s strength has already been proven. Moreover, Cadjo and the others were convinced with Zhao Hai’s character. They believed that Margaret would be happy if she ended up with Zhao Hai.

Marriage was a fuzzy concept in the Machine Field. If the feelings between two people were good, then they can be together without any need for a ceremony. Ordinary people would just live together without much fuss. Only unions between great families would require a wedding ceremony.

When he first found out about this, Zhao Hai was somewhat surprised. However, this made Zhao Hai a bit happy. This meant that there was no need for a flashy ceremony. In any case, Margaret loves him and he loves Margaret too.

It didn’t take long before the car arrived at the transmission tower. There were already a lot of cars parked beside the tower. When Zhao Hai and the others got out, they immediately entered the structure.

The first floor of the transmission tower was a hall. This hall was huge with thousands of square meters of floor area. There were a lot of people standing inside this hall.

When Zhao Hai entered the hall, he immediately captured the attention of everyone. The looks directed towards him were mixed with envy, provocation, and hostility. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, this was because he managed to spot Xiong Li and the others.

Zhao Hai quickly walked over to them. In the two days that he had been playing around with Margaret, he didn’t go and look for Xiong Li and the others. Therefore, when Xiong Li and the others saw Zhao Hai, they quickly welcomed him.

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I heard that you’ve been merry these past two days. But you’ve been too happy that you forgot about your brothers.”

Without waiting for Zhao Hai to speak, Margaret pouted as she said, “Big Brother Xiong, Brother Hai is accompanying me. Is there any problem?”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “There’s no problem, no problem. Hahahaha, Brother, Sister-in-law is angry. I’m just joking.” Xiong Li’s excuse caused everyone to burst into laughter.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Ever since ascending to the Machine Field, I have either been on missions or in seclusion. I haven’t gone out with Margaret that much. It just so happened that I have two days of free time. So of course, I took the chance to get to know Machine Field Planet. Once we arrive at the Cultivation Realm, it’ll be us brothers who will drink together.”

Li Kuangren laughed, then he patted shoulder and said, “Good, good. But Little Hai, the wines that you take out tastes so good. I can’t drink any other wine now.”

Everyone continued to talk with each other. This caused other people to look at them. The identities of the people present weren’t ordinary. These were the top 100 beginners in the Machine Field. Moreover, behind these 100 people were powerful groups. This caused everyone else to be pushed to the side.

At this time, the hall suddenly turned silent. Zhao Hai and the others paused as well. Then they turned to look at the person coming in from outside. This man had blue hair and appeared nonchalant.

When Zhao Hai saw Streep, his eyes couldn’t help but flash with despise. He wasn’t looking down on Streep’s strength but instead he was looking down on Streep’s conduct.

Zhao Hai didn’t give up on monitoring Streep in the past days. Almost every day, Streep would change for another woman. No woman stayed by his side for more than two days.

Zhao Hai was aware that this action was part of Streep’s cultivation. This was certainly the harvest he gained from that lucky encounter. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be this serious in changing from woman to woman. This also explains why his attacks were strong. His cultivation methods definitely had something to do with the yin aspect.

Streep also noticed Zhao Hai as he gave Zhao Hai a smile and a nod, as if he was very familiar with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai saw Streep’s gesture, he just gave a strong nod before turning around and ignoring him.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s actions, a flash of anger appeared in Streep’s eyes. Then he turned around and approached the other participants.

After Zhao Hai turned his head, he saw that Xiong Li and the others’ faces were somewhat ugly. Li Kuangren coldly snorted and said, “That fellow is really not pleasing to the eyes.”

Zhao Hai looked at Li Kuangren and the others. He knew that they were still angry about the injustice that happened back in the Ashley Family’s party. After all, Li Chuchen’s challenge only came about due to Ba Dong’s provocation. There were also a few people in the room whose face darkened, clearly directing hate towards Streep.

Zhao Hai looked at his brothers as he smiled and said, “Brothers, are you prepared? We’re about to leave soon.”

Xiong Li slightly smiled and said, “I’ve prepared everything. What I’m worried about is you, kid. You’ve been accompanying Miss Margaret for two days. Did you manage to prepare anything?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course I’ve prepared. I have high grade wine, seasonal dishes, and other delicious snacks.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but stare. They looked at each other before Dongfang Yu looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, didn’t you prepare anything else? Weapons? Defensive items?”

Zhao Hai just gave them a smile as he answered, “Rest assured, I prepared everything I need. I’m just used to bring food whenever I head out. This way, I’ll have something to eat and drink during downtimes. Hehe.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “I know about this. Back in the elimination round, while we were fighting, this fellow actually took out a recliner, an umbrella, and some drinks. He’s the only one who looks relaxed and free.”

Zhao Hai was about to reply, but footsteps were heard coming from the transmission tower. Zhao Hai looked up and saw a group of people going down.

Leading this group of people was a Warrior. This Warrior was tall and big, but he was actually very thin. His skin was a bit dark and he had a scar on his face. He had inch long hair while his eyes were ghastly cold. One could see that he wasn’t an affable person.

Zhao Hai knew that this was Skybreaker Blade Ma Rulong. This person was a true killer. From his debut to the present, he has entered battle thousands of times. There were times where he was injured but that was after he killed hundreds of characters. He was a true menace of the battlefield.

Following behind Ma Rulong were the respective team leaders. These leaders were Mages and Warriors, they were clearly from the three huge powers. These people were arranged to manage and protect Zhao Hai and the others.

After Ma Rulong got down, his eyes swept through Zhao Hai and the others before saying, “Is everybody here?” His voice was extremely low and seemed to carry his imposing aura.

Just as his voice fell,  a person wearing Mage robes went to his side before bowing and saying, “Answering to Sir Ma. Everyone is here.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he said, “All participants will follow him to the room over there. Everyone else should say their goodbyes.”

 After Ma Rulong said that, he no longer gave everyone his attention as he walked towards the room. This was the room where the transmission formation was. Zhao Hai and the others needed to head there.

Upon hearing Ma Rulong, Zhao Hai turned his head to Cadjo and said, “General Manager, we’re leaving. You take care. Camp Lord, you take care as well.” Then he gave the two a bow before turning to Margaret and giving her a gentle nod. After all the goodbyes were said, he turned and proceeded towards the room that Ma Rulong just entered.

At this time, Xiong Li and the others were also done saying goodbyes to their families. The group walked towards the transmission room shoulder to shoulder. Upon entering the room, they saw that the other participants were already inside. Ma Rulong was also inside. Because of Ma Rulong’s presence, everyone’s voices were in hushed tones.

When Zhao Hai entered the room, he couldn’t help but look at the floor. A magic formation was drawn into the floor. The formation was very complex, moreover it was very large. It spread out to all corners of the room. The formation was also filled with incomparably abstract symbols. It actually gave the room an aesthetic feel to it.

Everyone continued to speak in quiet tones. Before long, everyone was inside the room. The same Mage from before went to Ma Rulong’s side and reported, “Sir, everyone is present.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he looked at the participants and said, “I’ll be leading our trip to the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, you need to listen to my every word. The Cultivation Realm isn’t like the Machine Field. Nobody is allowed to wander about without by consent. Otherwise, I won’t be able to save you if an accident happens. Understood?”

Everyone gave a sound of understanding. Ma Rulong nodded, then he turned to a Mage and said, “Let’s begin.” The Mage nodded before he took out wrist computers from his storage item. These computers were as big as one’s palm. These computers floated towards Zhao Hai and the others. Upon receiving the gadget, the participants curiously inspected it.

As the participants were inspecting the computer, a voice was heard, “These devices are mainly used for communication and location. Contact information of the team leaders are already saved inside. If you come across something while strolling in the Cultivation Realm, you can use this device to contact a team leader. This device also has a positioning system, allowing us to find you in the shortest time. Because of this, you need to keep this device on yourselves at all times. Don’t store it in your spatial items.”

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t have any problems with it. They quickly placed the device on their hands. This gadget was made like a wristband. Although it appears like it was made out of bright silver, it wasn’t heavy at all. Instead, it was very soft and very comfortable to wear.

After seeing that everyone had equipped their computers, the Mage went to a corner of the room to start the formation. He went over and pushed a button on the wall. Before long, a flash appeared and everyone vanished from the room.

Chapter 1204: A Single Word Causing Public Execution

Zhao Hai only felt a flash of light in front of him before he was blinded. Once his vision returned, he looked around and found out that he was now in another place. This wasn’t the transmission tower.

The place where Zhao Hai and the others in was a broad platform. This platform was quite huge. Zhao Hai looked around and estimated the platform to be tens of thousands of square meters. There were dozens of Magic Formations that were constantly flashing. And every time it flashed, people would immediately appear. They seem to be very busy as they quickly went out of the formation and continued on.

Just like Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others were inspecting where they had ended up. Everyone had curious expressions on their faces. Although it has been some years since they had ascended, they haven’t actually been to the Cultivation Realm.

The Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm wasn’t that far from each other. However, it was very difficult for Xiong Li and the others to leave the Machine Field. Most of the time, they were either at missions or were practicing. The other times, they would head out and socialize with others. Due to this, it was understandable why they haven’t gone to the Cultivation Realm.

There were also only two ways to go from the Machine Field to the Cultivation Realm. The first method was to use a spaceship. However, most ships that were used for this method were freighters. These were ships used to transport goods between sects and families. It was almost impossible for normal people to get on board those ships.

The second method was to use a transmission formation, which was also not for everyone. And even if a transmission formation was available to go to the Cultivation Realm, the price to use it would be steep. If one wanted to use the transmission formation to go to the Cultivation Realm, then they needed to first explain who they were and then the reason for their travel to the Cultivation Realm. After that, a record would be kept before a background check would be done. Only after those troubles were finished was one allowed to visit the Cultivation Realm. It can be said that if it weren’t for the Six Realm Beginner Competition, then Xiong Li and the others wouldn’t have been able to go to the Cultivation Realm. It was just like back on Earth where some Chinese wouldn’t be able to go abroad for their entire lives.

Because of this, Xiong Li and the others were very curious about the Cultivation Realm. But at this time, a voice was heard, “Hey, you idiots. Don’t just stop there. You’re delaying other people.”

Zhao Hai and the others immediately looked around and saw a young man dressed in a black robe and a cap standing not far away, yelling at them. He had a look of contempt in his eyes and didn’t even bother to hide it.

Zhao Hai stared. They were wearing mage robes and warrior clothing, very different to what people in the Cultivation Realm wear. This young man should be able to recognize that they weren’t from here. So why was he being impolite? Doesn’t he know who they were?

At this time, a cold snort was heard nearby. Zhao Hai turned his head and saw that it came from Ma Rulong. Ma Rulong looked at the young man and said, “Who do you think you are? Why is a servant shouting here? Are you too impatient for your job?”

The young man actually craned his neck as he sneered and said, “I’m from the Seamount Faction of this city. What? It’s you who is impatient, isn’t it?”

Ma Rulong’s expression changed, he asked once more, “Seamount Faction? You’re from the Seamoung Faction?”

When the young man saw Ma Rulong’s response, he couldn’t help but proudly declare, “Correct, this one is from the Seamount Faction. Now, you better leave ten crystal stones to this grandfather. Otherwise, I’ll have to be impolite.”

At this time, Ma Rulong suddenly laughed and said, “Little Seamount Faction kid, daring to neglect the face of the Machine Field, you’re quite brave. Let’s see how the Seamount Faction responds after I kill you.” After he said that, Ma Rulong took out his one and a half meter long ghost head blade and then gave it a wave. A blade qi flew straight towards the young man. The young man screamed for a moment before he was bisected in half.

Ma Rulong didn’t even spare the young man’s corpse a glance as he said, “Let’s go.” Then he stored his blade and then proceeded towards the city.

Zhao Hai and the others were somewhat startled by what happened. Back in the Machine Field, although various families were very rampant, it didn’t reach to the point of public murder. There were some cases before, but it wasn’t prevalent. But now, Ma Rulong just took his weapon out and killed someone. This caused Zhao Hai and the others to be shocked.

But after seeing Ma Rulong proceeding forward, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t stay for long and just followed behind. However, there were some people who looked towards the corpse of the young man. Ma Rulong’s methods taught these newcomers a lesson about the Cultivation Realm.

Ma Rulong and the others quickly left the platform. As for the other people inside, almost nobody spared any effort to look at the young man’s corpse. In the Cultivation Realm, a dead person was as good as trash. This was especially true if the deceased was someone with no status.

After some time, another person wearing black clothing arrived. With a relaxed manner, he stored the young ‘s corpse before taking the young man’s job of maintaining order. It seems like nothing ever happened.

Ma Rulong proceeded to lead Zhao Hai and the others to the city. Upon entering the city, Zhao Hai was suddenly hit with a wave of nostalgia. This was because the city was constructed in a very familiar manner to him. The architecture of this city looked very much like ancient China, but much more exquisite. As they walked the cyan stone street, Zhao Hai thought that he had been sent back to the time of Ancient China. The clothes worn by people were also ancient robes, making Zhao Hai feel even more reminiscent of his home.

Before long, Ma Rulong arrived at a courtyard. Zhao Hai looked at the courtyard and saw a small plaque. Written on the plaque were three characters that read, Machine Field Headquarters.

As Zhao Hai was reading the plaque, Ma Rulong pushed the door and walked in. Upon entering the courtyard, Zhao Hai saw two Mages busying themselves. In front of them were two robots. It was clear that these two Mages were servicing these robots.

When the two Mages noticed someone coming in, they immediately turned their heads to see Ma Rulong. They couldn’t help but stare, then they placed their tools down as one of them greeted, “Sir Ma,  we didn’t expect you to be here personally. Excuse us for our lack of manners.”

Ma Rulong waved his hand, he glanced at the robots and said, “Forget it, you’re busy. Are the rooms prepared?”

The man quickly replied, “Sir Ma, rest assured, the rooms have been prepared. Please follow me.” Then after he said that, he led Ma Rulong and the others further in. Upon entering the courtyard, Zhao Hai and the others discovered that there were several buildings and even more courtyards inside. Moreover, there were a lot of rooms. It wouldn’t be a problem if more than 100 people stay here.

Ma Rulong walked past the second courtyard and then walked into the third courtyard. Then he looked at the participants and said, “This courtyard can house 30 people. The first 30 people according to ranking will stay here. As for the rest, you will be staying at the previous two courtyards.”

The Mage who repaired the robot said, “Mister Ma, rest assured, I’ll take care of the others.” Ma Rulong nodded before turning to the team leaders and said, “The first and second team will live with me in the second courtyard. The last team will live inside a courtyard of their own.”

The team leaders nodded before proceeding to take care of their things. Zhao Hai and the others remained in the third courtyard. Among them were the top ten great experts as well as those ranking up to 30th place.

A team leader assigned a room to Zhao Hai. The rooms weren’t divided according to ranking. Because of this, Zhao Hai, Xiong Li, and the others had rooms next to each other. The features of the rooms were more magnificent than those from the Machine Field, however it didn’t have any special appliance inside.

Zhao Hai and the others looked at their rooms from inside out. There were no notable things inside their rooms, it just had all required furnishings. It didn’t take long for them to get familiar with the room.

Each courtyard had its own small garden. There were trees as well as stone tables and benches there. When Zhao Hai and the others went out of their rooms, they went to the courtyard and took a table for themselves.

Xiong Li looked at the other people in the courtyard before turning his head towards Zhao Hai and the others, then he forced a smile and said, “So, the Cultivation Realm is really that brutal. Senior Ma actually killed someone in broad daylight.”

The group nodded, they didn’t expect Ma Rulong to kill someone that quickly. This surprised them. Dongfang Yu added, “It’s possible that Senior Ma did that in order to put out a warning. I also think that the actions of the young man are quite suspicions, it seems like someone had instructed him to do it. They want to demonstrate their authority. If Senior Ma wasn’t overbearing, I’m afraid we wouldn’t have any good days ahead.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said ,”I think so too. However, I think that this isn’t the end. Other people will certainly come here looking for trouble. It seems like the people from the Cultivation Realm really wants to get ugly.”

Sun Fei smiled bitterly and said, “It’s not just this time. I checked for information a few days ago. It seems like whenever the Six Realm Beginner Competition happens, people from the Cultivation Realm always find ways to make us suffer. They would often start a fight before the real competition began. At the worst, the Machine Field lost more than 20 people even before the start of the competition.”

Zhao Hai and the others’ expressions changed. They forgot to take note of this. They thought that since they were now in the Cultivation Realm, people would leave them alone. After all, they were here to attend the competition. It wouldn’t be great for the Cultivation Realm to be too excessive.

But now, upon hearing Sun Fei, they discovered that they had been naive. The Cultivation Realm’s people were more arrogant than they thought. Even those who were a stickler for the rules in the Cultivation Realm looked down on the Machine Field. In their minds, killing a few unremarkable people from the Machine Field was nothing.

The reason the Cultivators were rampant against the Machine Field’s participants was because they knew that the families wouldn’t dare wage war against their sects. Therefore, they held nothing back.

And now, Zhao Hai and the others were in the domain of the Cultivators. It wouldn’t be strange if the Cultivators were going to be impolite. It was hard to guess what kinds of things they would do.

Chapter 1205: Demonstration of Authority

While Zhao Hai and the others were speaking, they suddenly heard someone’s shout outside, “Machine Field thieves, come out here!”

Zhao Hai and the others were stunned. The loud voice had a hint of imposing aura in it, obviously coming from an expert. The expression on everyone’s faces changed. Then they stood up and went to the front courtyard.

When a team leader saw Zhao Hai’s movement, he immediately said, “Don’t move, you don’t have any business with this. Be good and just stay put.” The team leader didn’t go to the front courtyard and just looked at Zhao Hai and the others.

Upon seeing this person, Zhao Hai and the others paused. And since this was the rule, they just sat back down.

At this time, Ma Rulong’s voice was heard, “Who’s yelling here? Don’t you know that this is the Machine Field’s courtyard?”

The person outside loudly replied, “Is the Machine Field that prestigious? You actually dared to kill someone from the Seamount Faction for no reason? Come out here and give me an explanation.”

“Hahaha. Who does the Seamount Faction think they are? You’re not worth explaining to. This grandpa can kill whoever he wants!” Domineering, too domineering. As soon as Zhao Hai and the others heard Ma Rulong say this, they knew that a fight would happen soon. The other side needed to save their face.

Zhao Hai quickly released his spiritual force and before long his expression changed. He discovered that the courtyard has actually been surrounded. Zhao Hai turned his head to look at the team leaders whose expressions were the same. Naturally they also discovered the issue.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Xiong Li and the others and said, “Boss Xiong, get ready. Those people from the Seamount Faction has us surrounded. It seems like they that young man earlier wasn’t really the end. They’re going to attack us.” As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the other’s faces changed. But since they had considered this possibility, they nodded before they took their weapons out.

Sure enough, just as they were armed, the person outside shouted, “Good Machine Field, Good. But this isn’t your realm. You can’t just kill anyone in the Cultivation Realm. Everyone, I want these people from the Machine Field to know that we cannot be bullied. Attack them! Make sure that not even chickens or dogs survive.” Just as the man’s voice fell, a war cry was heard all around the courtyard. Then soon after that, the attackers began flooding in.

When the team leaders saw this, they knew that the situation wasn’t good. The other side was really prepared for this attack. It didn’t take long before the team leaders began to fight back.

When Zhao Hai saw the situation, he coldly snorted and then waved his hand. Liquid Silver appeared and then a 100-layer formation materialized. The formation turned into over ten thousand golden red arrows and then shot towards the attackers.

This move was the Ten thousand fiery arrows, however, this was different to Zhao Hai’s usual 100-layer formation spell. This specific one had more arrows and held more power.

The attackers didn’t expect to meet a rain of arrows just after entering the courtyard. They were immediately caught off-guard. The explosion caused by Zhao Hai’s ten thousand arrows quickly injured several people on the spot.

At this time, the other people in the courtyard responded. They were all skilled and experienced people, so their combat sense was very rich. Since people came to cause trouble, then they would have to be impolite. It didn’t take long before various attacks flew towards every direction.

Zhao Hai’s group of five composed one team as they attacked the enemies together. Once the exchange began, Zhao Hai and the others found out that their enemies weren’t weak. And most of the attackers were a bit stronger than them.

At this time, Ma Rulong moved to the front and then attacked their uninvited visitors. Explosions were soon heard, officially starting the clash between the two sides.

Zhao Hai looked around and found out the possibility that these attackers weren’t all from the Seamount Faction. There must be other people joining in. It was impossible for the Seamount Faction to have this much experts.

Although Ma Rulong’s previous behavior looked crude, Zhao Hai believed that the man wasn’t stupid. If the Seamount Faction was a huge sect, then Ma Rulong should have endured. However, he didn’t, which explains the strength of the faction.

But now, it seems like the Seamount Faction was itself being incited by another group. It might be everyone in this place planning to use this ruse to demonstrate their authority.

As Zhao Hai continued to observe, he discovered that Ma Rulong and the others had been tied down. Meanwhile, the people that Zhao Hai and the others were fighting seems to be holding back. Otherwise, the casualties here should be very huge. Instead, the Machine Field group had yet to suffer some losses.

Once he saw this, Zhao Hai was certain that the Seamount Faction had been incited by someone. However, it seems like they cannot act too excessively. They just want the Machine Field’s people to know their place. Besides this, it was possible that they were also here to probe the Machine Field’s participants.

After having thought through this point, Zhao Hai felt relieved. If they wanted to probe, then let them probe. Zhao Hai dealt with every attack coming his way, but he didn’t kill anyone. He understood that once he got ruthless, then the other party might return the gesture. This means that the Machine Field would suffer losses even after the competition began.

And just like what Zhao Hai thought, after the two groups clashed for about an hour, someone arrived. A long howl was first heard before a voice said, “Stop, everyone. Friend, this one is a member of the Six Realm Beginner Competition’s preparation committee, Fan Yi. Is this the residence of the Machine Field’s representatives?”

Ma Rulong knew that more trouble would come if this continued on, so he didn’t make another move as he replied, “This one is Ma Rulong, I lead the participants from the Machine Field.”

When Fan Yi heard Ma Rulong he quickly said, “So it is Master Skybreaker Blade Ma Rulong. This one has been disrespectful. People from the Seamount Faction, stop immediately. We’re all friends here.”

At this time, the person leading the attackers opened his mouth and said, “Brothers, stop.”

The people from the Seamount Faction also stopped. As for the team leaders, they proceeded to stop the participants from attacking. After that, they went to where Ma Rulong was in order to discuss something in secret.

Zhao Hai and the others went back to the ground. They looked all around them and saw that the fight destroyed the courtyard. Fortunately, the damage wasn’t that severe. Moreover, there weren’t many casualties, only very few participants died. There were also many people who were injured, but they wouldn’t be dying from their wounds.

After looking around him, Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “Good, Seamount Faction, good. I will not forget this. Just wait and see.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The actions of the Seamount Faction seems to be directed by someone. They came here to show their power and also probe our bottom line. Hehe, that person from the preparation committee came at a very good time. I think he’s just waiting, only coming out when it is time.”

Xiong Li and the others thought about it and immediately understood what Zhao Hai was saying. Their expressions turned difficult. Dongfang Yu coldly snorted and said, “Shameless. I didn’t expect the Cultivation Realm’s people to resort to these methods. Too shameless.”

Li Kuangren huffed angrily, but he didn’t rush out in order to fight the Seamount Faction. At this time, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “It looks like the Cultivators had found out that we’re quite strong. Therefore, they came here to see how strong we really were. Hmph. If they want to probe, then let them probe. When the competition begins, I’ll clean them up properly.”

Xiong Li and the others bitterly smiled. Of those present here, it seems like only Zhao Hai could say those words. During the earlier fight, all of them were exerting great effort to fend off the enemy. On the other hand, Zhao Hai accomplished this task with ease. They were once again reminded about their strength gap with Zhao Hai.

Although the fight was over, many people were still very alert and were prepared to fight against the Seamount Faction once more. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai and the others returned to their stone table. Zhao Hai took out some wine and food as the group proceeded to drink and eat.

Zhao Hai’s actions caused everyone in the courtyard to stare. Not only the participants, but even the team leaders were shocked. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai and the others to be this nonchalant about the current situation.

And just like what Zhao Hai thought, everything was just an act. Both sides wouldn’t dare to go all out. The Seamount Faction withdrew their troops while Ma Rulong and his group sent for people to repair the courtyard. Nothing noteworthy happened after that.

When Zhao Hai entered the Space that evening, Laura and the others immediately led him to the living room and showed him the video of Ma Rulong and Fan Yi’s conversation. There was nothing special about the recording, just Fan Yi being an ordinary peacemaker. He mediated for both sides and urged them to let matters go.

Although Ma Rulong knew what was exactly going on, the only thing he could do at this time was to swallow his anger. After everyone left, Ma Rulong smashed the table as he said to the Mage next to him, “Every time the Six Realm Beginner Competition happens, those bastards always come causing trouble. Aren’t they tired of using the same tricks? Damn, they are really looking down on us.”

The Mage beside him bitterly smiled and said, “Those Cultivators are used to being arrogant. They would never change their methods. To be honest, it’s good for us if they repeat this trick every time. This way they wouldn’t come here and give us a direct challenge.”

Ma Rulong coldly snorted, then he calmed down and said, “The participants of the Machine Field this time is the strongest we’ve had. There must be no incidents. Especially Zhao Hai, you need to make sure that he’s safe at all times.”

The Mage nodded, but then he said, “Or make sure that Zhao Hai doesn’t leave the courtyard. Just let him practice here.”

Ma Rulong shook his head and said, “No need, just send for people to protect him in secret. It wouldn’t be good if we restrict him. Think about what others would say if we did that, not to say Zhao Hai’s own thoughts. Zhao Hai’s strength is good, he will certainly get a good ranking in the competition. The Machine Field relies on him to get good resources.”

The Mage nodded and said, “Alright, but what about Streep and the others? Should we send people to protect them as well?”

Ma Rulong shook his head and said, “Streep’s strength can’t reach even half of Zhao Hai. I don’t know if it’s me going crazy, but I feel that Zhao Hai isn’t any weaker than me. We need to protect him.”

The Mage was startled, “Are you sure? Is Zhao Hai that strong?”

Ma Rulong sighed, “Let’s just hope I’m right. If he’s really that strong, then he would be a blessing for the Machine Field!”

Chapter 1206: Asking a Favor

Zhao Hai didn’t really expect Ma Rulong to have this high of an appraisal for him. He couldn’t help but smile bitterly. It seems like the Machine Field is truly placing their hopes on him. They wouldn’t have done this if Zhao Hai didn’t have any real skills.

Laura and the others looked at Zhao Hai and quickly knew what he was thinking. Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, it seems like you’re being treated as a precious gem by the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “The more they do that, the more in danger I will be. It seems like I’ll be in for quite some trouble. However, I must say, this place is really good for cultivation. The energy here is very abundant, much more than in the Machine Field.”

Margaret nodded, “I heard that the Cultivation Realm has a lot of spirit veins. Places with spirit veins have more abundant spiritual qi, sometimes a hundred times more than other places. If you can cultivate there, then you’ll be able to achieve twice the result with half the effort.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, we’ll have an opportunity later on. I believe that there are other places other than the Cultivation Realm that has spirit veins. We just don’t know where these veins are in the Machine Field.”

Margaret forced a smile and said, “The Machine Field has some spirit veins. However, they are very scarce. I’m afraid the amount can be counted using one hand. Moreover, the density in those veins fall short compared to veins found in the Cultivation Realm. If not for this, then the Cultivators would have already taken it from us. We will never be able to enjoy such luxury.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. After learning about the Machine Field’s situation, he couldn’t help but recognize how much worse it was compared to the Cultivation Realm. In the Cultivation Realm, the strength of each major sect wasn’t any weaker than the entirety of the Machine Field. For those in the Cultivation Realm, the Machine Field was a huge wasteland, a useless place. But even if the Machine Field was quite weak, once it retaliated, then it would bring forth heavy losses to the Cultivators. Because of this, nobody took control of the Machine Field.

If the Cultivation Realm really decided to end the Machine Field, then the Machine Field would have been destroyed 800 times over.

The Machine Field’s strength was equal to a sect in the Cultivation Realm. Yes, the Machine Field controls a bigger territory than the Cultivation Realm’s sects, but its territory had nothing of significant value.

After he thought of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. Then he turned his head to Margaret and said, “If, say, I win first place and get a large number of resource planets. Then wouldn’t the Cultivation Realm go to war with the Machine Field? If this really happens, and the Cultivation Realm and the Machine Field goes to war, then we might be bringing a calamity instead of a gift.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Margaret and the others immediately frowned. Their expressions turned difficult. They haven’t thought of this before. Now that Zhao Hai pointed it out, they couldn’t help but feel that there was a possibility of this happening.

Margaret turned anxious as he said, “Then what do we do? Brother Hai, will the Cultivation Realm really attack us?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, then he patted Margaret’s hand and said, “Alright, thinking about this at this time is useless. And even if this is the case, we wouldn’t have any ability to change anything. Then only thing we can do is take one step at a time.”

Margaret and the others nodded. Although their moods had turned heavy, it was just like what Zhao Hai said, they needed to do what they can. Currently, they don’t have any ability to change anything. The Machine Field wouldn’t listen to anything they say.

The group turned silent for some time before Margaret said, “Brother Hai, I want to ask for a favor.”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at Margaret in confusion as he asked, “What’s the problem? Do you really need to ask?”

Margaret didn’t smile and instead turned serious as she said, “Brother Hai, if the day comes where the Cultivation Realm really eliminates the Machine Field, then I hope that you can move the Ashley Family to the Space and give them their own background to settle in.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but frown. To be honest, this request made him feel awkward.

The Space was Zhao Hai’s biggest secret. Upon arriving at the World of Cultivation, Zhao Hai’s main goal was to keep the Space as secret as possible. But if he made the Ashley Family enter the Space, then this secret would be discovered. Who knows what would happen then.

Margaret waited for Zhao Hai’s response. She was also aware about how important the Space was for Zhao Hai. The Space was truly strange. It allowed Zhao Hai to develop his strength bit by bit. But if others were to know about it, then it would be troublesome for Zhao Hai. This would make it very difficult for him to gain a foothold in the World of Cultivation.

Margaret was afraid that Zhao Hai would decline. However, she didn’t force him. So she just sat there silently as her eyes began to tear up. Laura and the others looked at Zhao Hai and knew that he was currently feeling embarrassed. Actually, they didn’t want Zhao Hai to let the Ashley Family in. But everything depended on Zhao Hai in the end. So all of them were waiting for him to respond.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone before he turned to Margaret who was tearing up and then said, “Margaret, I can only promise to help the Ashley Family as much as I could. However, I cannot let them know that the Space exists.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, her face lit up, then she immediately said, “Alright. Brother Hai, rest assured, I won’t reveal anything. When the time comes, I’ll tell them that you want to relocate to another planet. Is that ok?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, in the next few days, take note of any special planets in the Machine Field, especially around Rainbow Meteorite Field and the Quicksand Starfield. Even if their environment is bad, we can just terraform it later on. We’ll make a base of operations there. This way, we can guarantee that the Space’s existence wouldn’t be leaked.”

When Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they paused for a moment before immediately agreeing. A flash of delight was seeing in their eyes, as though they had just found something amusing to do. Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai could only force a smile.

Meanwhile, Margaret’s heart was moved. She didn’t expect Zhao Hai to actually help her. Actually, looking for a planet suitable for a base wasn’t an easy thing to do.

The next morning, Zhao Hai went out of the Space and returned to his room. It must be said that his room was very neat. It was enough for a single person to live with and not something made for multiple people. It was very cozy.

When Zhao Hai came out, he discovered that Xiong Li and the others were already sitting in the stone bench and chatting. Zhao Hai walked over and said, “Brothers, you’re up early.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “We just got up. Little Hai, we’re planning to head out to explore, how about we go together? We can find a place to drink along the way.”

At this moment, Sun Fei chuckled as he said, “Boss Xiong, it seems like you don’t know much about the Cultivation Realm. If we talk about shops, then they have a lot. But as for restaurants, there’s actually very few of them around.”

Xiong Li asked, “Why is that?”

Sun Fei smiled and said, “People in the Cultivation Realm believe that consuming food produces impurities and isn’t helpful in cultivation. Therefore, a lot of people don’t eat food. Instead, they eat something called a fasting pill. This pill is very interesting. It allows you to not eat for several days. Naturally, this thing is flavorless and is just like any other pill. Since people from the Cultivation Realm liked to use these fasting pills, restaurants became rare. Especially in a big city like this. Only places where commoners live can we find restaurants. However, the Cultivation Realm has a rule that forbids commoners from living inside big cities. Because of this, it would be very difficult for us to find somewhere to drink in this city.”

Upon hearing Sun Fei, Xiong Li couldn’t help but stare. Then he angrily responded, “Your mother. What kind of rule is that? If they don’t like to eat and drink, then what is there to enjoy in life? The people in the Cultivation Realm are really weird.”

Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Boss Xiong, those who desire immortality will no longer drink. They also couldn’t eat large amounts of meat. Living like that is more painful than death. Such people will suffer for tens of thousands of years. Even if I have only ten years left to live, I would still be happier than them.”

Xiong Li and the others laughed. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, let’s head out and explore. However, we need to be careful. We’re currently inside the territory of the Cultivators. If those Cultivators wants to deal with us, then they would have a lot of methods to do it with. We need to endure, endure. Let’s just wait for an opportunity later on.”

Dongfang Yu nodded, then he sighed and said, “I just have to say, the Ascenders in the Cultivation Realm are just the same as us when they arrived here. But in the Cultivation Realm, the cultivation methods they use are much better than ours. This allowed them to be stronger. If we learn the same methods as them, I reckon we’ll be able to face them on equal grounds.”

When Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and the others, he saw them nodding in agreement. He couldn’t help but smile faintly before he leaned his head forward and then whispered, “Actually, if you want to practice cultivation methods, there’s a way to do that. In fact, right now is the best opportunity to do so.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others stared. Then their eyes shone as they moved their heads in as well. After that, Sun Fei asked in a hushed tone, “Big Brother Hai, what do you mean?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Don’t forget, the beginning stage of the Six Realm Beginner Competition is an elimination round. In this round, we can kill anyone we want. Some Cultivators will certainly bring their cultivation methods along with them. As long as we kill a few of them and grab their cultivation methods, then wouldn’t we be able to practice?”

Upon hearing what Zhao Hai said, everyone nodded. But then Xiong Li said, “That’s a good plan if it succeeds. But Little Hai, you need to think more into it. It’s useless. Those Cultivators have storage belts on their bodies. Moreover, their cultivation methods are inscribed inside jade slips with spiritual restrictions. If we aren’t masters in using spiritual force, then that jade slip will shatter. If what you said is that simple, then the Machine Field would have already been practicing cultivation methods.”

Dongfang Yu and the others heard this and nodded. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Naturally, I have a solution for this. Brothers, don’t worry about it. As long as we get a cultivation method, I’ll make sure that we can practice it. What do you think?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, the others couldn’t help but feel excited. Dongfang Yu immediately replied, “Are you telling the truth? Little Hai, you must know that the Cultivation Realm’s spiritual restrictions aren’t easily broken through. You might even injure yourself.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brothers, don’t worry, I can do it. Because of this, we need to kill as many Cultivators as possible in this elimination round. As long as we get their cultivation methods, then we can begin our practice.”

Everyone’s eyes shone. They saw the power of the Cultivators, but they don’t think that they were any worse than those people. Those cultivators had also ascended in the last five years. Thinking that those cultivators would be used as stepping stones for their future, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but feel excited.

Hearing that there was a possibility for them to practice the Cultivation Realm’s methods, Dongfang Yu and the others felt energized. They believed that they weren’t any different in calibre compared to the Cultivation Realm’s ascenders.

Zhao Hai looked at his brothers and then said, “Actually, the Machine Field’s method is also very good. However, the Machine Field focused on mechs and battleships. Because of this, research towards magic formations as well as training Mages and Warriors weren’t given priority.”

Sun Fei looked puzzled at Zhao Hai, he asked, “Brother Hai, are you sure? Can the Machine Field’s methods really compete against the Cultivation Realm’s methods?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Of course it can. Didn’t I just block Li Chuchen’s three swords? Little Fei, don’t you wonder why the formations I use are much better than ordinary formations?”

Sun Fei nodded and said, “Of course I wonder. Your 5-layer formations seem to be stronger than most 10-layer formations.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s actually a reason for that. First, I have very strong spiritual force. Spiritual force is the foundation of a Mage. If you have strong spiritual force, then your formations would be stronger as well. The second reason is the formation set that I use. The formation sets I use are mostly my own creations. These formation sets don’t only contain offensive and defensive formations, I also put in supporting formations that are usually used in mechs and battleships. A lot of people think that mixing supporting formations to formation sets would cause that formation set to become weaker. In fact, this isn’t the case. If you can use supporting formations the right way, you could vastly improve your formation set.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, everyone’s minds turned blank, especially Sun Fei. His face was looking at Zhao Hai in disbelief. He couldn’t wrap his head around what Zhao Hai just said.

Chapter 1207: Not Today

Sun Fei looked at Zhao Hai with his mouth open, he couldn’t say a word. It took a while before Sun Fei was able to return to clarity. He suddenly exclaimed out loud as he stood up. His two eyes were completely fixed on Zhao Hai. His mouth was moving up and down, mumblin incomprehensible sounds.

Dongfang Yu, who was sitting besides Sun Fei, patted him on the shoulder and then led him back down to take a seat. Then he said, “Little Fei, calm down. Little Hai told you this because he wanted to teach you. But don’t tell it to other people, or else Little Hai will be in trouble.”

Upon hearing Dongfang Yu, Sun Fei completely recovered. He let out a long breath, then he looked at Zhao Hai as he nodded and said, “Rest assured, Brother Hai, I will not tell anyone, even the people from the temple.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he patted Sun Fei on the shoulder. Then he said, “It’s no big deal. In fact, I would announce this discovery sooner or later. This is a huge benefit to the Machine Field’s Mages and Warriors. Presently, there are a lot of magic formations in the Machine Field. If we add them all up, nobody would be able to count them. This caused a problem where we don’t know which formation is compatible with which. And if we add supporting formations to the mix, then things would become more confusing.”

Everyone nodded. Even a Warrior like Xiong Li agreed. In the Machine Field, whether they be Warriors or Mages, they would have some understanding regarding magic formations. After all, the Machine Field relied on formations to support their way of life. It didn’t matter if it was a mech or a battleship, or it was an electric lamp or a computer, all of these things had magic formations inscribed in them. It would be very difficult if one doesn’t know anything about magic formations.

Zhao Hai then said, “Other than me, the only other person that is well-versed in magic formations in Little Fei. Since Little Fei is a fire Mage, I will use a normal 5-layer fire shield. Little Fei, take a look and find out what’s different about my formation.” After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand and a 5-layer formation appeared in front of him. And when it appeared, it didn’t absorb any fire element in the surroundings, causing the formation to look like a child’s toy.

Sun Fei was called Fire Saint because of his deep understanding with regards to fire element formations. So there was no need to wonder about his mastery about the 5-layer formation fire shield. Because of this, Zhao Hai showed him this basic magic formation to let him see what’s special about it.

A level 1 fire shield consists of five magic formations; a solidifying formation, a spirit formation, a fire element formation, a reinforcement formation, and a directional formation. The solidifying formation would be next to the reinforcement formation. The first formation would fix the formation into a shield shape while the latter would strengthen its form, making it stronger and defensively better. Meanwhile, the spirit formation had the most important function, which was to connect and help the formation in absorbing the surrounding spiritual qi, allowing the formation to truly materialize. As for the fire element formation, it was there to provide the elemental aspect of the formation.

Naturally, if the fire element formation was changed to say, a water element formation, then the formation would become a water shield. But if this part of the formation was swapped, the formation set wouldn’t be able to be used by fire element mages.

The directional formation had a simpler function. It didn’t facilitate in the energy consumption of the formation nor did it assist in the elemental aspect. Instead, it allowed the shield to be moved around. Otherwise, the fire shield would just stay in place.

However, Zhao Hai’s fire shield was somewhat different. It still had the same four formations; the solidifying formation, the spirit formation, the fire element formation, and the directional formation. What it didn’t have was the reinforcement formation. Instead, what Zhao Hai had was a formation that Sun Fei didn’t recognize.

Zhao Hai pointed at the new magic formation and said, “This magic formation isn’t something that is used by Mages. Instead, it is often seen on defensive formations in battleships. This formation is called the shipscale formation, since this formation can be seen outside the ships and looks like the scales of a fish. It’s main function is to increase the defensive capability of a battleship. This formation is much better compared to the reinforcement formation. It can increase defense by about three points.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei couldn’t help but stare. Three point increase in defense? What kind of logic is that? This was almost equivalent to a 7-layer formation set. However, 7-layer formation sets demand more spiritual force from a Mage. Increasing defense while still keeping the spiritual force requirement the same was a godsend to Mages.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and the fire shield immediately started the attract the energy around it. But since Zhao Hai was just demonstrating, the shield was very small, only about the size of his palm.

It was at this time that Sun Fei saw the clear difference in Zhao Hai’s fire shield. Ordinary fire shields used fire to cause an imposing image. However, Sun Fei and other Mages knew that these flames were the exact weakness of the formation.

The burning of these flames dispersed the energy of the formation and thus preventing it from achieving the best defensive effect. Zhao Hai’s shield looked very defensive, but not as imposing.

Zhao Hai’s fire shield just lit up with red light and didn’t emit any flame. This meant that it used most if not all of its energy in defense. This caused the formation to be more defensively effective.

Zhao Hai waved his hand once more as the shield disappeared. Then he said, “A lot of new formations had appeared in the past few years. The reason why people thought that supporting formations couldn’t be used alongside offensive and defensive formations was because past tests showed them that adding supporting formations reduces the power of formation sets. But after so many years of development, whether it be offensive, defensive, or supporting formations, there are now a lot more of them in existence. Take this shipscale formation as an example. It has only been developed in recent years and it is now starting to replace commonly used formations and is even being used by mechs. I believe it’s time for us to revisit the idea of adding supporting formations to our formation sets. This will certainly give us great benefits in the future.”

Sun Fei vigorously nodded, his expression showed that he was moved by Zhao Hai’s words. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, please give me that formation. I want to study it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I’ll give it to you. But not now, it’s already late. We still have to go out and play, right Boss Xiong?”

Xiong Li shook his head and said, “Let’s not head out today. Little Hai, I’m more curious about your magic formations. How long has it been since you ascended? How could you know more than Little Fei?”

Zhao Hai had already thought the answer for this, so when he heard Xiong Li he smiled and said, “You might not know, but back in the lower realms, I was already researching magic formations. However, the research of magic formations in the lower realms isn’t as comprehensive as the Machine Field. So after arriving at the Machine Field and learning about magic runes, my magic formation research leveled up.”

Xiong Li nodded, then he looked around them and then said, “Let’s head indoors. We won’t be heading out today. Little Hai, let’s talk more about your magic formations. Have you researched about magic formations in weapons?”

Upon hearing Xiong Li, Zhao Hai knew where the conversation was heading towards, he nodded and said, “I have, as long as it’s about magic formations, I’ve researched it. Boss Xiong, your two sledgehammers have about 70 formations inside them, yes?”

Xiong Li was shocked when he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately replied, “Correct, fantastic. I didn’t expect your research to reach this point. Let’s go inside and talk more about these formations. It would be great if you could improve our weapons.”

Zhao Hai gave a slight nod. For Xiong Li and the others, weapon magic formations are very handy. Like in mechs and battleships, these formations were mostly comprised of supporting formations. The formations inside Warrior weapons all had something to do with offense. The most important role of these formations was to amplify the attacks made by their users.

Because of Zhao Hai’s relationship with Liquid Silver, he was able to conduct research on formations used in weapons. And with Karen and the others as well as the Universal Scanner, Zhao Hai’s understanding of weapon magic formations wasn’t any less than his knowledge about formation sets. Therefore, he was happy to help Xiong Li and the others.

Once everyone had entered Xiong Li’s room, Xiong Li immediately took his chained sledgehammers out and then placed it on the ground before saying, “Little Hai, take a look.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he squatted and inspected Xiong Li’s hammers. The workmanship of the hammer was very good. The materials used in making it was also well selected. Zhao Hai could see in these hammers how much the Wu Family cares about Xiong Li. He used his spiritual force to inspect the hammers and saw the formations carved inside. These Formations were small and mithril was used as a conductor for spiritual qi. If others inspected Xiong Li’s hammers, then they might think that it was a perfect product. However, in Zhao Hai’s eyes, there were some flaws here and there, ranging from the arrangement of formations to the actual formations used.

Xiong Li and the others were anxiously looking at Zhao Hai. After some time, Zhao Hai got up and then said, “Boss Xiong, the materials used for your hammers are very good, everything is high-grade. Moreover, the way it was forged was skillfully done. However, there is still room for improvement. I can’t do it here. But after we return to the Machine Field, if you trust me, I can help you refine your hammers. I believe that after we are done, your offensive strength would increase from three to five points.”[1]

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, everyone took in a breath of cold air. Increasing offensive strength by three to five points? Wasn’t that an increase of 50%? This figure was too astonishing.

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you sure? Do you want me to ask the family to give you the blueprint of the weapon?”

* * *

I really don’t know what these ‘points’ are.

Chapter 1208: Secret of the Axe

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he shook his head and said, “It’s useless. I probably already know about the magic formations in your hammer. If others see them, then they may think that there’s nothing wrong. However, I can guarantee that my formation sets would definitely perform better. And Boss Xiong, sorry for this, but your hammer isn’t allowing you to exert all your power.”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “That’s true. My strength has improved a bit, so this hammer is no longer suitable for me. The family is making me a new one, but it isn’t ready yet.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. After we return to the Machine Field, I will make a better weapon for you. I believe it wouldn’t be any worse than the one your family made.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Of course, of course, hahaha. I believe you. Or I can tell tell the family to stop making my weapon.”

Upon hearing XIong Li, Zhao Hai immediately said, “No, don’t do it. Boss Xiong, don’t do that. You should know that a lot of formations used in your hammers are secret formations of the Wu Family. If they find out that you allowed me to make a weapon using their formations, then they might not be happy. We don’t want them to misunderstand and think that I stole their secret formations.”

Xiong Li nodded, “Alright, but when the new weapon comes, they will have to take this weapon away.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Just return it. When the time comes, I’ll just modify your new weapon. Don’t worry about it.” Xiong Li nodded, “Alright, then we can only do it like that.”

At this time, Dongfang Yu went forward as Xiong Li retreated. Then he took his fire dragon sword out and then handed it to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, take a look at mine.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before taking Dongfang Yu’s fire dragon sword. But just as Zhao Hai tried inspecting it with his spiritual force, he didn’t expect the fire dragon sword to emit a fierce flame to block his spiritual force. At the same time, the flame also proceeded to attack.

Zhao Hai stared, then he quickly released a defensive magic formation to block the fire. At the same time, he also withdrew his spiritual force, causing the fire dragon sword to calm down.

Dongfang Yu and the others stared at Zhao Hai, they didn’t know what was going on. Zhao Hai looked at the fire dragon sword before he turned to Dongfang Yu and said, “Second Brother, your fire dragon sword isn’t simple, it blocked my spiritual force. I didn’t expect it to be this great, there’s no need to modify it. It’s a divine weapon. I reckon you still couldn’t use all of its power?”

Dongfang Yu nodded as he took the fire dragon sword that Zhao Hai handed over. Then he sighed and said, “This fire dragon sword has been obtained by the Yan Family. Everyone who uses this sword needs to give it a drop of blood before they can be recognized as an owner. Because of this, no one else could use the sword before the owner dies. I always felt that this sword had a lot of abilities, so I wanted you to see them. However, I didn’t expect the sword to have the ability to defend itself. It’s unfortunate.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The sword is truly wonderful. If there’s an opportunity, I’d like to research it in the future. This way, I’ll be helpful to Second Brother.” Then after he said that, he turned to look at Li Kuangren.

Li Kuangren didn’t hesitate and quickly handed over his axe. Zhao Hai took the axe and immediately scanned it using his spiritual force. This time, there was no accident, his spiritual force penetrated smoothly and allowed Zhao Hai to see everything inside. But after a few moments, Zhao Hai was stunned before his expression changed. Then he looked up at Li Kuangren and said, “Third Brother, have you offended anyone from the Song Family?”

Li Kuangren stared, then he looked at Zhao Hai in confusion and said, “Offended anyone? I don’t think so.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s expression, Dongfang Yu knew that a problem had come up, so he immediately asked, “Little Hai, what is it? Is there a problem?” Zhao Hai let out a long breath and then said, “Third Brother’s axe has a fatal weak point. Once the axe is under great pressure, it will have a risk of exploding. Moreover, the power of the explosion is no less than a small nuclear bomb!”

“What!” Xiong Li and the others called out in alarm. They looked at the two-handed axe in Zhao Hai’s hands in disbelief. It seems like they saw a calamity or a savage beast.

Small nuclear bombs, to people of their level, was akin to an ultimate weapon. Even Cultivators would see an explosion of this magnitude as fatal, they would be very lucky if they were able to escape.

And now, Li Kuangren’s axe actually held a small nuclear bomb inside. This was too absurd!

Li Kuangren was also stunned.Then with blood red eyes, he said, “Those bastards, no wonder they took my axe back when I managed to get a place in the qualifiers. They told me that they would upgrade it. Shit, what an upgrade. Those bastards.”

When they heard Li Kuangren, Xiong Li and the others also had difficult expressions on their faces. If Li Kuangren’s axe explodes, then it would be impossible to escape from it. They looked at each other and could see a hint of shock in their eyes.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and then said, “We aren’t sure if this is meant for all of us or just Third Brother. This might mean that the Song Family has some spies in their internal circle. Moreover, it isn’t a low status spy.”

Things like what happened to the Zhang Family caused the Machine Field to be very sensitive. So when Zhao Hai discovered the mystery inside Li Kuangren’s axe, he immediately thought of this.

During the qualifiers, everyone in the Machine Field knew that Li Kuangren and Zhao Hai were close, and almost inseparable at times.

Just like the realm qualifiers, the first round of the Six Realm Beginner Competition is an elimination round. But unlike the realm qualifiers which didn’t allow the formation of teams, the Six Realm Beginner Competition allowed it.

Being able to form teams in the elimination round was very advantageous to Zhao Hai. The Brothers can form a team and move together. In this situation, if Li Kuangren’s axe explodes during a fight, then they may all be killed. Because of this, Zhao Hai thought of the possibility that the rigging of the axe was aimed at their group, not just Li Kuangren.

Upon hearing this, Xiong Li and the others nodded, they understood what Zhao Hai was implying. Their expressions couldn’t help but turn ugly.

Dongfang Yu appeased Li Kaungren before turning to Zhao Hai and saying, “I think it’s best if we tell our families about this as soon as possible. But Third Brother shouldn’t tell the Song Family, it might alert the spy inside.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “We still don’t know how many traitors the Machine Field has. If we pass this information to our families, then a spy might be able to pick it up. We should keep it a secret.” Dongfang Yu frowned and said, “So what should we do?”

Zhao Hai looked at the axe in his hands and then he turned to Li Kuangren and said, “Third Brother, I’ll need to deal with your axe. I’ll guarantee that I can give you a new one in a couple of days. Moreover, it’s an axe that suit you the most. What do you think?” Li Kuangren nodded and said, “Take them. I believe you.” Zhao Hai nodded then he sent the axe to the Space.

After dealing with the axe, Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “Let’s return to our rooms. Don’t tell anyone about this. We’ll slowly investigate this matter.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. Then Zhao Hai left the room along with Dongfang Yu and the others. Their expressions were difficult to look at, this matter caused their hearts to burn with anger.

When Zhao Hai returned to his room, he immediately entered the Space. Then he took out Li Kuangren’s axe to have it go through the Universal Scanner.

Laura and the others also went out and joined Zhao Hai beside the scanner. Once he arrived at the scanner, Zhao Hai placed the axe on a magic circle. The scanner started up and then swallowed the axe. A short while after that, the manufacturing method of the axe was printed out.

Then after a flash of light, a pile of materials appeared on a formation on the other side. These materials weren’t metallic in nature, it seems to be a pile of powder.

Zhao Hai knew that this pile contained the components of the nuclear bomb. He let out a long breath before taking the materials. Then he turned to look at Laura and the others and then said, “I didn’t expect something like this to come up. Interesting, very interesting.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you should remake the axe first. Will you add more materials?”

Zhao Hai read the manufacturing method for Li Kuangren’s axe, he shook his head and said, “There’s no need to add more. Third Brother’s axe is already made with good materials. Let’s head inside and discuss what magic formations to put inside.”

Laura and the others nodded and then walked indoors with Zhao Hai. Upon entering the living room, Laura and the others quickly took their computers up and made some analysis.

Li Kuangren’s offensive characteristics was akin to a tornado. He uses the enemy’s strength against them by using rotational motion. Because of this, the axe cannot be too light but cannot be heavy either, or else it would be difficult to control. Moreover, the requirements for compatible magic formations was quite high.

After some time, a plan was finally made. Then they took these plans and then had it run under the Universal Scanner. The scanner would arrange the most suitable formation set for Li Kuangren’s weapons.

Before this, Li Kuangren had 70 formations inside his axe, the same as Xiong Li’s sledgehammers. The difference between the two lies on the axe’s preference for sharpness and speed, compared to the sledgehammers’ preference for size and weight.

Once the scanner was done, Zhao Hai saw that the axe could be engraved with 80 formations, ten more than before. This would make Li Kuangren’s attacks more powerful while reducing the energy he needed for combat.

Chapter 1209: Weapon Shattering

Zhao Hai secluded himself inside his room for three days. Xiong Li and the others also didn’t disturb him. Conversely, they were defending the door to Zhao Hai’s room, they wouldn’t permit anyone to disturb Zhao Hai.

Naturally, their actions attracted Ma Rulong’s attention. Ma Rulong was the leader of their delegation and was very concerned about every participant. Moreover, Zhao Hai was a person he has been keeping tabs on.

So after seeing Zhao Hai secluding himself in his room for three days without going out, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but worry. He went to Zhao Hai’s room and then saw Xiong Li and the others sitting outside. They were whispering to each other and failed to notice him.

Ma Rulong stepped towards the group. Once Xiong Li and the others noticed Ma Rulong, they hastily stood up and bowed as they greeted, “We’ve seen Senior Ma.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai’s room and said, “What’s wrong with Zhao Hai? Why hasn’t he come out? Is there a problem?”

Xiong Li shook his head and said, “Senior Ma doesn’t need to worry. Little Hai is fine. There’s just something he needed to do so he secluded himself. I believe he will come out in a day or two, there’s no problem.”

Ma Rulong looked at Xiong Li and said, “Is he really alright? You can tell me if something happens.”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “Senior Ma can rest assured. If something happens, we will certainly inform you. There’s no need to worry.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he looked at Xiong Li and the others and said, “Alright. Try to stay in this place in the next few days. There are people who went out and got forced to accept a challenge issued by the Cultivators. They have a lot of methods to make you accept. Some even came back injured. So if you do go out, be extra careful, especially Zhao Hai. There are a lot of Cultivators who see him as a threat.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded, “We will. Senior Ma can rest assured. We’ll pay attention.” Ma Rulong nodded, then he left.

Just as Ma Rulong left, Xiong Li turned to the others and said, “It seems like those Cultivators really aren’t leaving us alone. Right, do you think we can go out when Little Hai is done?”

“Go out? Of course we’ll go!” Just as Xiong Li said his words, Zhao Hai’s voice was suddenly heard. Xiong Li and the others turned around and saw Zhao Hai smiling as he walked out of his room.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was out, Xiong Li and the others immediately surrounded him. All of them were looking at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Come in.” Then he went back inside his room with Xiong Li and the others following behind.

Upon entering the room, Zhao Hai closed the door before he waved his hand taking out a two-handed axe. The axe didn’t look any different than the one Li Kuangren used. It was completely identical to his previous weapon.

Zhao Hai handed the axe to Li Kuangren and then said, “Third Brother, try it. I managed to refine the axe. Although I didn’t add any materials to it, I managed to modify the formations inside.”

Li Kuangren nodded and took his axe. He tossed his axe in his hands before he nodded and said, “Good, it’s as heavy as before.” Then he began to input battle qi.

Just as battle qi entered the axe, it immediately shone. Li Kuangred stared before quickly withdrawing his qi, the radiance also vanished as he did that.

Li Kuangren began to funnel in battle qi once more and saw the axe light up. Li Kuangren’s eyes shone as he said, “Nice, this is very good. Fantastic. The amount of battle qi I need is less than before, and it seems like the effect is the same. Little Hai, am I right?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled and said, “Correct. What you feel is right. Your axe now needs only 70% of what you use before in order to achieve the same effect. So what do you think?”

Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Fantastic, fantastic! This will be very good for me. Thank you Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not only that, I also added a magical effect to your axe. Once it clashes with an opponent’s weapon, it would vibrate and shatter the enemy’s weapon.”

Li Kuangren stared, everyone’s expressions changed as well. Then at the same time they asked, “Shatter  the enemy’s weapon?”

Zhao Hai nodded as he smiled and said, “Right, it can shatter the enemy’s weapon. This feature used to only be found in mech weapons. This is due to the large amount of energy required to do it. Since mechs have energy batteries, this allowed them to have this feature. Battle qi is also a type of energy, so why can’t Warriors use this ability? Therefore, I researched magic formations and ended up with the one I put inside Third Brother’s weapon. Third Brother, try it.” Li Kuangren nodded, then he looked around the room, probably finding something to test this ability on.

Seeing Li Kuangren, Xiong Li said, “Third Brother, the things in this room can easily be cut off even if you don’t use battle qi. How about you try this.” After he said that, Xiong Li took out a weapon from his storage equipment.

In his hand was a heavy sword. It can be seen that it has been excellently worked on. Xiong Li smiled and said, “This is from a level 4 Warrior I killed before. To be honest, this weapon isn’t any worse than my hammers. Try attacking this one.”

Xiong Li gripped the sword hilt and then lifted it up. Li Kuangren nodded before funneling battle qi into his axe and then attacking the sword.

Xiong Li quickly detected his weapon shaking. He immediately poured in battle qi when the crash happened.

A bang was heard before the axe cut through the sword as though it was a piece of paper. A clang was then heard as the top half of the blade fell to the ground.

Everyone in the room looked at the sword in Xiong Li’s hand. Whatever Xiong Li was holding now could no longer be described as a sword. The only remaining part was ten centimeters of blade besides the hilt. As for the other half that hit the ground, it was less than ten centimeters long. Only this much remained, the other materials of the sword was vaporized.

Not wrong, vaporized. It wasn’t broken to pieces or smashed to bits. It was vaporized, turned into very fine metallic powder.

Upon seeing this result, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but breath in cold air. Li Kuangren stared at his axe, it seems like he saw a monster.

Hiss! The sucking of air was audibly heard as Xiong Li and the others finally recovered. Xiong Li held the sword up and looked at the fractured part. The portion of the blade looked like it has been dissolved, leaving a very neat cut into the sword. If he hadn’t tried this sword before, then he would have thought that he had taken out the wrong weapon.

“Hahaha”, Li Kuangren was beyond happy with his axe. His laughter lasted for some time, causing Xiong Li and Dongfang Yu to be envious.

After some time, Li Kuangren finally calmed down before storing his axe. Meanwhile Xiong Li and Dongfang Yu turned their heads towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai saw their expressions, he smiled faintly and said ,”I can also transform Boss Xiong’s Weapon. As for Second Brother Dongfang, I don’t think the fire dragon sword needs to be modified right now. Let’s wait until the secret of the sword becomes clear.”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “Alright, give it the weapon shattering ability as well. It’s very good.”

Dongfang Yu was somewhat depressed. However, after thinking that even Zhao Hai couldn’t read the fire dragon sword, he couldn’t help but feel hope.

It must be said that Sun Fei was the most depressed. He was a Mage so he couldn’t use any Warrior weapon. Zhao Hai looked at Sun Fei’s expression as he smiled and said, “Alright, Little Fei, there’s no need to be sad. I’ll organize a few formation sets for you in a couple of days. I believe they will be helpful to you.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei repeatedly nodded and said, “Alright, then it’s settled. Brother Hai, you need to hurry up.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I know. Right, how about we go out to play now?”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others paused. Xiong Li frowned and said, “Little Hai, do you really want to head out? You should know that there are a lot of Cultivators waiting for us outside. They’re especially attentive towards you. If you leave now, they will certainly bring you trouble.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course I know. However, we need to teach those fellows a lesson. Do they really think that the Machine Field is full of herbivores? Rest assured, if they dared to look for trouble, I’ll happily accommodate them.” Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others knew that persuading him otherwise was useless. Therefore, they just agreed to it before heading out of the courtyard.

As soon as they were out, Zhao Hai quickly felt someone following behind him. However, he wasn’t worried. He knew that the person behind him has been arranged by Ma Rulong. Therefore, he just ignored it and the group of brothers continued to walk down the street.

Ever since they came to Seamount City, they haven’t had the proper opportunity to explore the place. But even if they hadn’t come out, Zhao Hai was already familiar with the city’s streets.

The moment Zhao Hai and the others entered Seamount City, Laura and the others had already begun mapping the entire place. At this time, the entire city has already been mapped by the Space. In the last three days, besides practicing, Zhao Hai also took the time to familiarize himself with the city. Because of this, he knew every street in the city.

Xiong Li and the others were completely clueless about the place, so they just followed Zhao Hai as they proceeded to window-shop. Zhao Hai wasn’t just randomly wandering around, his main target was Seamount City’s market.

Seamount City’s market area was actually their business district. In this business district, not only were there shop fronts, there were also people who put up stalls. These people were Cultivators, but they were mostly rogue individuals. As for the shop fronts, they were mostly under the control of major powers.

It’s a custom in the Cultivation World that only Cultivators could enter a major city. No person who hasn’t cultivated was allowed to enter a major city.

Not everyone in the Cultivation Realm cultivated. At the current moment, people who haven’t cultivated still account for the majority of the population. However, the lives of practitioners weren’t as good as those back in the Machine Field.

The Machine Field’s science and technology was very advanced. The average person in the Machine Field had a home to stay in and entertainment to kill time with. As long as they were willing to work, then even if they didn’t practice, they would still live quite well.

Things were different in the Cultivation Realm. Almost all of the non-practitioners in the Machine Field were controlled by a major sect. These people couldn’t farm whatever they wanted. If a family has ten mu of land, then they would have to use 5 mu for plants that the sect needs and the other five for food. Naturally, the sect wouldn’t rob them of their harvests. There would be monetary rewards, moreover these rewards were often big.

However, if they didn’t look after their land, then they would be punished by the sect. Moreover, this punishment was heavy. Besides this, all non-practitioners would pray to the Sect, providing the Sect with faith power. If a sect discovers that a non-practitioner hasn’t been praying enough, the non-practitioner would be punished. Unlike non-practitioners in the Machine Field, non-practitioners in the Cultivators were like pigs in a pen. The had lives only a tad bit better than slaves.

Non-practitioners in the Machine Field only think of cultivation as a way of life. If one can practice then they would be congratulated. Not only the person, but their family would also benefit. Their living environment would be greatly improved and many others. But in the Cultivation Realm, not everyone can practice. In order to become a Cultivator, one needed to have a spiritual root.

Spiritual roots were like Mage talents or innate skills for Warriors. If you don’t have talent for magic, then you won’t be able to become a Mage. If you don’t have any innate skills, then you couldn’t learn strong martial techniques and reach a high level. Spirit roots were the same. If one didn’t have a spiritual root, then they wouldn’t be able to cultivate.

However, not everyone who can practice could enter sects. Take a small sect like the Seamount Faction, for example, their selection for disciples was very strict. If their talent for cultivation wasn’t good, and they didn’t have much potential, then it would be impossible for them to enter the sect. There were low-level cultivation methods that were circulated for free. But it can be said that these methods weren’t enough. People who practice these methods were called Rogue Cultivators.

Rogue Cultivators who managed to enter a sect were limited to a few lucky fellows. If a Rogue Cultivator wanted to join a sect, then they needed to successfully arrive at Qi Condensation stage. And by then, only small sects would accept them. But in order to cultivate, one would need pills and better cultivation methods. These things can only be bought in the city. And in order to buy these things, they would need crystal stones. To gain crystal stones, Rogue Cultivators would hunt and kill beasts, collect medicinal plants, mine for precious rocks, and so on. They would then go to markets to trade their stuff for crystal stones. In turn, these crystal stones would allow them to buy the cultivation materials they need.

Chapter 1210: Country Bumpkins?

There’s a saying in the Cultivation Realm, it goes.. “There are always treasures everywhere, but everything depends on your eyes being in the right place!” The sentence might sound ridiculous, but it was somewhat true.

Nobody in the Cultivation Realm would dare underestimate these stalls. This was because treasures were often seen on them! This treasure might not be a weapon or a magic artifact, it may be a plant or a piece of ore.

After all, these Rogue Cultivators weren’t as informed as sect disciples. Although they were also Cultivators, their knowledge about various treasures couldn’t compare to sect disciples. Because of this, there would be times where they get a treasure but were unable to identify it. In the end, they would just sell these items in their stalls.

This caused the stalls of the Rogue Cultivators to be a special sight in the Cultivation Realm. People in the Cultivation Realm would have no objection to Rogue Cultivators pitching up some stall on their own. On the contrary, they strongly supported them. The more stalls there were, the more treasures would appear in a certain city. For the people in the Cultivation Realm, treasures were one of the most important things in Cultivation.

Zhao Hai’s trip to the marketplace was mainly in order to pick up a treasure for himself. At the same time, he would also hunt for valuable plants and ores.

It has been some time since the Space got some new plants. Because of this, Zhao Hai plans to send a batch of new plants to the Space.

The group of brothers chatted as they proceeded forward. Xiong Li and the others were excitedly looking at the scenery. The clothing of the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm was different, making Xiong Li and the others extremely eye-catching. Everyone they pass by looked at them with expressions that was anything but friendly.

Sun Fei looked at the Cultivators in the surroundings before whispering to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, these guys don’t look very friendly. What do we do?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Don’t worry. If they dared to make a challenge, I’ll clean them up.”

Sun Fei looked at Zhao Hai’s confidence and didn’t say anything. He was well aware that Zhao Hai was strong and that the two of them weren’t on the same level. Zhao Hai managed to block three swords from Li Chuchen. Because of this, Sun Fei didn’t see any problems from what Zhao Hai said.

The group walked for about half an hour before they could finally see a bustling marketplace in the distance. Moreover, the sound of bargaining was already audible.

Upon seeing this scene, everyone couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai. They weren’t familiar with Seamount City, so they just followed Zhao Hai as he led them to take a few turns. Xiong Li unwittingly asked, “Little Hai, what’s that?” Zhao Hai already became the center of the group. Although he was ranked fourth according to seniority, he was the strongest among them all. In this world that spoke with strength, the strongest would naturally be the center.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The marketplace. This is where people from the Cultivation Realm buys their items. Let’s go, maybe we can see something good.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but smile bitterly. Dongfang Yu looked depressingly at Zhao Hai and said, “There’s certainly things that are good here. However, this isn’t the Machine Field. They don’t accept machine coins. And we don’t any crystal stones.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Don’t worry about it. If you fancy something, I’ll buy them for you. I have enough crystal stones for all of us.” The Space was able to make crystal stones. With the amount already mined inside the Space, Zhao Hai could be considered as a wealthy man in the Cultivation Realm.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but gawk. Xiong Li confusedly looked at Zhao Hai as he asked, “Where did you get crystal stones? Those things are strategic resources in the Machine FIeld. Don’t tell me the Ashley Family gave some to you? Are they that rich?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “There’s no need to worry about where I got them. In any case, it’s good that we have crystal stones. It’s time to let the Cultivation Realm know that we’re filthy rich.”

Zhao Hai looked very much like a rich young master right now, causing Xiong Li and the others to laugh. However, their actions caused the surrounding Cultivators to get angry.

People from the Cultivation Realm looked down on the people from the Machine Field. In their opinion, those from the Machine Field held lower status than them, even inferior compared to non-practitioners who were living like pigs in a pen. They felt disgusted to see these people from the Machine Field in their city laughing and being wild.

Actually, talking out loud wasn’t a problem. There were no rules disallowing loud chatter in the streets, after all, this was a normal occurrence. However, if those being loud were from the Machine Field, the Cultivators seem to find fault in it.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about them as he led his group towards the market. Upon entering the area, Xiong Li and the others gawked. There were stalls everywhere, much more than what they expected.

Shop fronts in this place seem to disappear due to the sheer volume of stalls being set up in the streets.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the spectacle as he just proceeded to go forward. Xiong Li and the others immediately went and followed behind. However, their arrival became the focus of attention in the market. Everyone looked at them while whispering. Naturally, these people knew who Zhao Hai and the others were.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind this kind of attention. As long as someone was wearing Mage robes in the Cultivation Realm, this situation would always happen. This was because there were very few people from the Machine Field here.

There were quite a few cultivators who would go to the Machine Field in order to look for something. On the other hand, not a lot of people from the Machine Field could go to the Cultivation Realm. First, it was because the transmission formation couldn’t be used at will. Only spaceships could permit their travel, and even then it was very difficult to get into one. Secondly, people from the Machine Field would get discriminated once they go to the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, only an extreme few from the Machine Field would go to the Cultivation Realm. It can be said that the Cultivators wouldn’t see someone from the Machine Field for years. But now, there was a group of people from the Machine Field. It was no wonder why the Cultivators were somewhat curious.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it as his eyes proceeded to sweep the stalls. But disappointingly, there were nothing special in the stalls. Majority of those displayed were beast skins or beast bones. These things were completely useless for Zhao Hai. What Zhao Hai needed was a live beast, not parts of a dead one.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai discovered a stall in the corner. And unexpectedly, the stall was manned by a small child. The child looked more than ten years old and was quite mature for his age. There were some items in his stall that looked very simple. But on a rag on the ground lay a plant. This plant was in a small tile pot. However, the plant’s trunk looked dry, it also had a few leaves left. It can be said that the plant was half-dead.

Zhao Hai proceeded to walk to the stall and examined the potted plant. Although the plant looked half-dead, Zhao Hai could sense a strong life force coming from it. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to buy the plant.

Zhao Hai looked at the child and said, “What plant is this? How many crystal stones for it?”

The child stared at Zhao Hai, but after he heard his question, the child immediately answered, “I don’t know what plant it is. I dug it from the foot of a mountain. If you want it, I can sell it for ten crystal stones.”

To be honest, 10 crystal stones wasn’t cheap, especially for a half-dead plant. And even if Zhao Hai can feel the life force inside this plant, other people couldn’t. Zhao Hai had the Space that had an affinity for plants. This also explained why this child has been here for days not being able to sell the plant.

But without hesitation, Zhao Hai took out ten crystal stones and handed it over to the child. Then he carefully inspected the plant. This plant was a small tree about a meter high. It still had a few scattered leaves remaining. It’s trunk was very dry, looking much like the face of an old person. It wasn’t attractive at all.

However, this feature made the plant special. Generally, plants of this size wouldn’t have a lot of cracks on their trunks. But this specific plant seem to have weathered through life for countless years. It was truly strange.

A short while after Zhao Hai began inspecting the plant, an arrogant voice was suddenly heard, “I want this tree, how many stones?” Zhao Hai turned around to see a young man dressed in Cultivator clothes. The young man had an extremely arrogant look on his face.

The Cultivator robes he wore was very well made. His hair was in a ponytail while a fan was held in one of his hands. The young man looked like a son of a wealthy family.

The child looked at the young master as he awkwardly said, “I’m sorry, this tree has been sold to this gentleman. He has already given me his payment.”

The Cultivator turned his head to Zhao Hai when he heard the child. He coldly snorted and then said with disdain, “Machine Field bumpkin, state your price. I want that tree.”

Zhao Hai looked at the young cultivator as he smiled faintly and then sent the plant to the Space. Then he calmly replied, “I’m sorry, it’s not for sale.”

When the young man saw Zhao Hai putting the plant away, his eyes couldn’t help but shrink. This slight reaction couldn’t be hidden from Zhao Hai. This caused Zhao Hai to confirm that the plant was certainly special. Otherwise, this young man wouldn’t have been so adamant to buy it.

Upon hearing that Zhao Hai was not willing to sell, the young man’s expression changed. Then he gave out a strange smile as he asked once more, “You’re really not selling it?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m not selling.”

The young man suddenly laughed and said, “Machine Field bumpkin, you actually dared to come to the Cultivation Realm to steal our treasures. I don’t know if you’re dumb or you just want to die. You better surrender that tree to me today, or else, hehe. I will let you know that the Cultivation Realm isn’t for people like you.”

Chapter 1211: Ghost Dao Cultivator

As soon as Xiong Li and the others heard the young man, they quickly knew that it was impossible for this interaction to turn friendly. Zhao Hai looked at the young man as he smiled and said, “What? You can’t buy it from me, now you plan to snatch it? You think you can do that?”

The young man laughed and said, “You’re asking me if I can do it? You really think I can’t take it away from you? Do you Machine Field bumpkins really think that you’re on equal grounds with Cultivators? Give me the plant now and I’ll keep your corpse intact.”

Goodness, they would still kill the person, but they would keep their corpse intact. This was probably the craziest statement that one could make.

Zhao Hai looked at the Cultivator as he smiled and said, “Mister, please tell me who you are. Maybe I can look at your background and decide to let you go. Otherwise, you can’t blame be for being impolite.”

The young man looked at Zhao Hai as though he was an idiot. He suddenly laughed and then coldly looked at Zhao Hai as he said, “You’re dead country bumpkin. I’ll tear you to shreds.” Zhao Hai just smiled and then said, “Then please.” Then he flew towards outside the city along with Xiong Li and the others. The Cultivator saw this and also followed behind.

Seamount City wasn’t a big city and the Seamount Faction that was in charge of this city wasn’t a big influence. It can be said that if it weren’t for the support of the big sects in the Cultivation Realm, then they wouldn’t have dared to provoke the delegates from the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai and the others quickly flew to a barren hill just outside the city. The group stood on the sky atop the hill. The Cultivator looked at Zhao Hai and then sneered, “You’re quite good in choosing a place to be buried in.” Zhao Hai looked at the Cultivator, then he coldly smiled and said, “Rest assured, after you die, I will turn you into a good and obedient Undead. Being able to fight for me is an honor.”

The Cultivator coldly snorted and said, “Courting death!” He waved his hand as the fan flew out and then spew out black gas. As the gasses got out of the fan, they quickly formed into malicious ghosts that threw themselves towards Zhao Hai.

The Cultivator looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I’ll make you taste the might of my Ten Thousand Ghosts Fan. I will make you understand the difference between the Cultivation Realm and the Machine Field. Then I will refine you to become a living soul for my fan.”

Zhao Hai coldly smiled as he waved his hand and then released a 50-layer formation. This formation immediately exploded and became several hundred white arrows. Zhao Hai waved his hand once more, causing the arrows to fly towards the malicious ghosts.

The Cultivator smirked, he didn’t take Zhao Hai’s magic seriously. In his opinion, magic cannot compare to his skill. Because of this, he had the malicious ghosts continue flying towards Zhao Hai.

However, what happened next surprised the young man. Once Zhao Hai’s white arrows hit the ghosts, the ghosts suffered an extremely heavy injury. The ghosts wailed pitifully as their bodies continue to shrink. They became more and more transparent as their yin energy was cut short.

Any Cultivator that knew about malicious ghosts would quickly know what was happening. This was a sign that the malicious ghosts were heavily injured and was quickly losing their strength.

First level malicious ghosts were called Ghost Servants. Their attacking strength was small and they were quite weak. If one wanted to use first level malicious ghosts to deal with an enemy, then they would have to depend on numbers to do so. Without thousands of first level malicious ghosts at your command, then one wouldn’t be able to properly fight.

Second level malicious ghosts were slightly stronger, but not substantially. No ghosts were very useful alone before the fifth level.

There were a lot of methods to upgrade malicious ghosts. Besides making them absorb yin energy, malicious ghosts could also devour other malicious ghosts to get stronger. This way, one would be able to train higher-leveled ghosts. However, this method would cause the user to lose a lot of their ghosts.

One method for malicious ghosts to level up quickly was providing them with blood meal!

Blood meal, as the name suggests, was food composed of flesh and blood. This was a very special method that works very well in improving the power of malicious ghosts. However, those who use this method weren’t good people. Users of these methods tend to be the worst individuals.

There are two types of blood meals. The first type was blood meals made from beasts while the other type was blood meals made from people. These two types were very different. Blood meals made from beasts could also increase the strength of a malicious ghosts, but it also reduces their wisdom. In other words, malicious ghosts fed with the flesh and blood of beasts would get stronger quickly but in turn they would become stupid. They would become wild beasts and act according to their instincts. They would only be able to understand simple orders.

On the other hand, malicious ghosts fed with blood meals made from people would not only get stronger fast, they would also become smarter. This was especially true if a ghost was fed with blood meals made with a cultivator’s flesh and blood.

Feeding ghosts with blood meals made from monster beasts was the most common practice in the Cultivation Realm. There were a lot of places in the Cultivation Realms were beasts were kept just for this purpose. This was also very normal practice for Ghost Dao cultivators.

However, there were some Evil Cultivators that would use the other method to make their malicious ghosts stronger. They would feed their malicious ghosts with living people. There was a rumor that the Devil Realm had pens with living people in it. These pens would breed people for the consumption of the ghosts.

The Cultivator that Zhao Hai was fighting right now used the second method to rear his malicious ghosts. Therefore, he had spent quite a lot of effort in his ghosts. If the people from the Cultivation Realm were to find out about his practice, then he would no doubt be executed.

Because of this, upon seeing that his precious ghosts were being heavily injured, the Cultivator was quite distressed. If the level of these ghosts fell, then how long would it take for them to regain their strength?

With this thought in mind, the Cultivator quickly put away his fan as his face turned ugly. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Good, good. You actually dared to hurt my ghosts, I’ll turn you into blood meal!”

Zhao Hai looked at the Cultivator, then he shook his head and said, “Why do Cultivators talk too much? It’s incredible. Before you fight, do you invite your enemies for a glass of wine, then have a tea party before you quarrel for an hour and then fight? If that’s the case, then I really admire you people.” Xiong Li and the others laughed.

Hearing that he was being ridiculed by Zhao Hai, the Cultivator’s face turned dark. Then he coldly snorted and said, “You have a sharp tongue. Now, go die!” He waved his hand, taking a sword out. He pinched his hand as he performed a sword art to attack Zhao Hai.

The sword was made very strangely. The sword body was like a snake and its handle was its tail. It’s whole body was black, it looked terribly gloomy.

Zhao Hai discovered that this Cultivator’s strength was much less compared to Li Chuchen. Although the sword looked aggressive, it actually failed to seal up all of Zhao Hai’s escape routes. If Zhao Hai didn’t want to face this attack, then he could just easily avoid it.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as a 50-layer formation appeared in front of him. Then the formation opened up as a giant light sword appeared. This light sword proceeded to welcome the Cultivator’s sword.

The Cultivator coldly snorted, then he activated his secret art. The sword elongated and was also wrapped with a layer of dark mist. The sword looked ethereal as thought it became the dark mist itself. It’s form was now akin to a ghost.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the young man’s sword changing into yin energy. Zhao Hai was using light element magic, an element that specifically targeted yin energy. In this clash, Zhao Hai had the upper hand. Therefore, he held no fear.

As the light sword and the yin sword clashed, a bang was heard as an explosion occurred. The Cultivator’s expression changed. When the dust settled, Zhao Hai’s light sword vanished. Although the Cultivator’s sword was still there, the dark mist surrounding it was gone. It had returned to its previous form.

The Cultivator had an ugly face as he retrieved his snake sword. The sword was a medium grade artifact. These things were quite rare in the Cultivation Realm. Being able to clash with a light element sword was not a problem. However, the piece of soul that he attached to the soul has been heavily damaged. At this point, it was already impossible for him to control the sword as smoothly as before.

The Cultivator didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this formidable. Even after the snake sword appeared, the other party was still alright. This was very surprising.

The Cultivator quickly moved as a banner appeared in his hand. As he swung the banner, the skies quickly turned dark as dark mist surrounded Zhao Hai.

Then he waved his hand, causing five black flags to appear. Another wave of his hand made four of the flags shoot out in all directions. The young man then waved the remaining flag in his hand. The flag became larger and then the dark mist proceeded to attack Zhao Hai and the others.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted. Then he waved his hand causing a 100-layer light element formation to appear. Then with him at the center, a blast of light erupted outwards.

This light element formation composed 100-layers, not 50. As the white light exploded outwards, the dark mist cast by the Cultivator quickly vanished. The Cultivator let out a miserable grunt, his expression turned very ugly.

Zhao Hai knew that the other party’s soul has been damaged, so how could he let go of this opportunity. He quickly sent over a wind-assisted ice blade. Then he sent his ten thousand flying arrows, then another barrage of metal arrows, then a stealthy darkness arrow.

Zhao Hai’s barrage of attacks caused the Cultivator to be caught off-guard. The Cultivator practiced the ghost dao, so when the dark mist dissipated, he quickly took out a ghostface shield to defend. The defensive capability of this shield was quite high. It blocked three of Zhao Hai’s spells. However, it failed to see Zhao Hai’s darkness arrow. The arrow broke through the defense and then shot towards the Cultivator’s throat!